<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ursula K Le Guin on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/ursula-k-le-guin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ursula K Le Guin on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/ursula-k-le-guin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Roadside Picnic by Boris and Arkady Strugatsky</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-roadside-picnic-by-boris-and-arkady-strugatsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-roadside-picnic-by-boris-and-arkady-strugatsky/</guid>
      <description>Roadside Picnic by Boris and Arkady Strugatsky     Red Schuhart is a stalker, one of those young rebels who are compelled, in spite of extreme danger, to venture illegally into the Zone to collect the mysterious artifacts that the alien visitors left scattered around. His life is dominated by the place and the thriving black market in the alien products. But when he and his friend Kirill go into the Zone together to pick up a &amp;ldquo;full empty,&amp;rdquo; something goes wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiration from Fictional Worlds</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/inspiration-from-fictional-worlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/inspiration-from-fictional-worlds/</guid>
      <description>My last semester was extremely busy. So busy that I spent my commute on the train sleeping everyday instead of my usual reading. I&amp;rsquo;ll admit, most of my reading is done when I&amp;rsquo;m on the train. So other than the occasional manga or cookbook, I hardly read the last couple months of last year. Which is devastating.
This year (like every year), I resolved to read more. I started out the year reading two non-fictional books about personal finance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>