<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Filofax on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/filofax/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Filofax on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:30:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/filofax/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 18:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-13/</guid>
      <description>Man, this was the most productive week I&amp;rsquo;ve had since Reading Week! I&amp;rsquo;m super happy with my level of productivity. I got a lot done and I still managed to have a large amount of free time all to myself. On Tuesday, I got to hang out with a friend for two hours and I still got stuff done.
On Thursday, I went on a Kill la Kill marathon. My friends have been bugging me about watching it and since the finale was Thursday night, I spent the entire day catching up on the series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 05:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-12/</guid>
      <description>Wow I am so not proud of myself at all lately. Ugh. School. Please be done and over with!
The pictures aren&amp;rsquo;t great because I didn&amp;rsquo;t take them in &amp;ldquo;natural light&amp;rdquo; like I usually do and it&amp;rsquo;s currently 11:07 PM. Still Sunday, so I&amp;rsquo;m technically not late!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #11</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 15:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-11/</guid>
      <description>This was supposed to be &amp;ldquo;paper week&amp;rdquo; but that didn&amp;rsquo;t work out at all. I am so dreading this paper. I got some of it done but not enough. I&amp;rsquo;m seriously just not motivated to do this paper at all. I kinda want to curl up into a ball and cry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Planning Just Doesn’t Work For Me</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/digital-planning-just-doesnt-work-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 16:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/digital-planning-just-doesnt-work-for-me/</guid>
      <description>I grew up on the Internet. At the end of elementary school, I already had my own e-mail, posted on forums, ran my own forums, learned HTML and PHP, created my own websites, went on YouTube daily, etc. I was a little late to the first touch screen smartphones (just got one almost one year ago) but I had my iPod touch for years and that was all I needed. I played games, listened to music, and downloaded apps like crazy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #10</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 23:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-10/</guid>
      <description>Last week was supposed to be busy week but not much happened really, on the productive front anyway. My friend was running in our student election on campus and I swear, I lost weight just by walking around taking down posters after the election was over and walking around with him while he tried to persuade the general public to vote for him. It was a great experience but man, I did not accomplish as much as I wish I did!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #9</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 21:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-9/</guid>
      <description>Week of February 23, 2014 &amp;#8211; March 1, 2014. I have a tendency of not using my planner when I have a busy week. There are a lot of unfinished tasks (and tasks that were finished but not marked as finished) this week. That should not be the case at all. As soon as there&amp;rsquo;s a lull in my life, that&amp;rsquo;s the time when I whip out my planner. I need to fix that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #8</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 20:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-8/</guid>
      <description>Week of February 16, 2014 &amp;#8211; February 22, 2014. This was reading week. Unfortunately I did absolutely nothing at all this week, other than watching the Figure Skating events at the Winter Olympics in Sochi. My week basically revolved around figure skaters and procrastinating on all of my responsibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #7</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 20:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-7/</guid>
      <description>Week of February 9, 2014 &amp;#8211; February 15, 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #5</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 21:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-5/</guid>
      <description>Last week mostly consisted of me working on my computer science assignment and studying for my exam that was on last Friday. Most of the other tasks I delegated to myself didn&amp;rsquo;t really get accomplished. At the end of the week, I think I did alright on the exam. I&amp;rsquo;m still working on that assignment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #4 (Late)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 21:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 06:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-3/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d rather not talk about my productivity level from last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 02:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-2/</guid>
      <description>My second week in my shiny new Filofax! I just realized my major design flaw with my inserts: did not label the times for the weekly part of the inserts. It&amp;rsquo;s okay though, I&amp;rsquo;m not so busy that I don&amp;rsquo;t have time to scribble them in.
A note about how I write stuff down:
Half-filled square: Attempted task but did not finish.
Striked out: Task no longer needs to be done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Holidays 2013</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/christmas-holidays-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 18:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/christmas-holidays-2013/</guid>
      <description>My exams ended relatively early last semester. That meant more time for a break! I didn&amp;rsquo;t do terribly a lot over through break though. Definitely was not as productive as I would have liked to be.
Finished watching and reading Shingeki no Kyojin
Shingeki no Kyojin is an anime. The Internet has been basically exploding over it (my part of the Internet anyway). My friends in real life also freak out over it and so much so that I just had to see what they were on about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 04:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/my-week-1/</guid>
      <description>I just moved into my shiny new Filofax: a personal sized Woodlands named Ainsley. I spent the day before Christmas Eve and Christmas Eve printing out my custom inserts. I&amp;rsquo;m not 100% happy with them. Good thing I didn&amp;rsquo;t print out the whole year and only printed this a semester worth of them. So this is my first week using them! Not a lot happened (besides from parties and the like) so there&amp;rsquo;s not a lot written in there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>