<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>University on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/university/</link>
    <description>Recent content in University on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 16:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/university/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 16:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-14/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
I came to school on a reading day because I have a group project to work on. The meeting doesn’t start for another hour so I’m just going over my AI notes because I need to catch up on the material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 02:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-13/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
Team messy notes 2015. My mind was blown away during this lecture. Honestly, some of the algorithm solutions for simple problems like finding the two closest points in a plane, are extremely interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 15:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-12/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
It’s early morning and I’m trying to do some of my assignment that I should have started over the weekend but I was working on a group project instead. I really should learn to manage my time better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally Imported Those Old Posts</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 19:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</guid>
      <description>So now that I&amp;rsquo;ve moved hosts, I decided to do some spring cleaning (fall cleaning?). Right now, my databases are a mess. I have a lot of databases that aren&amp;rsquo;t used and databases that are waiting to be used. I still had my old blog database, back from when Brokenphrases was my main blog. So, I decided to to import all those pages and posts here.
Now my blog post archive is pretty much complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 15:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-11/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
I came to school three hours early today (I start at 10) so I can get a head start on the exercises we’re doing today in tutorial. It’s just so awkward when the TA asks for the answer and no one speaks up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 02:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-10/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
Finished making presentation index cards. I’m really bad when it comes to public speaking so I need to prep a lot. Most group presentations I‘ve had involved “just winging it” and that never goes well for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 03:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-9/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
I’m feeling super down for some reason right now and I can’t really pinpoint what it is. It feels like there’s a dark cloud looming over my head. I tried to make my notes look extra neat, neater than usual, as that usually helps me calm down whenever I do feel like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 03:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-8/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
My super messy notes (right) vs the rewritten version (left). During a lecture, neat and legible notes are the last things on my mind. Okay, sometimes I zone out and look down at my paper and think, “Wow, this looks horrible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: My DIY Planner</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 00:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-7/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
Some pictures of my diy planner, taken with a potato. I borrowed inspiration from diyfish inserts. Whenever I open it up, I can see my whole month and reoccurring tasks right in front of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: The Rebel</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 06:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-6/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
In bed with Camus. A penpal recommended this book to me and he expects a nice, long essay about it. Okay, I think (and hope) that was a joke but I really want to be able to understand this so we can have a meaningful conversation about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incoming Mail #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/incoming-mail-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 21:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/incoming-mail-1/</guid>
      <description>This is a new segment, where I post the things that I received in the mail! Since the beginning of the year, I&amp;rsquo;ve acquired some penpals and started buying more things online. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I&amp;rsquo;ll separate the things I buy from my penpal letters but I don&amp;rsquo;t think I buy that much to warrant it. Today, I only have purchases to show you. On to the post!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Switching to Foundation</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 01:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-5/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
I’m taking a “zero day” from studying but that doesn’t mean you have to stop learning! I decided to work on my blog and switch frameworks from Bootstrap to Foundation, mostly because Boostrap has the potential to get really bloated and I find that Foundation is more intuitive and their documentation is great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: School Supplies Haul</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 20:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-4/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
Here’s a picture of all the school supplies I bought for this year (and hopefully years to come). I didn’t spend a lot compared to previous years and I’m so happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Convolutions, Please…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 06:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-3/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
I’m in the middle of trying out studyign{.tumblelog}’s method of taking textbook notes for my algorithm design class.
This was seriously a hard section to wrap my head around. Each step of computing a convolution makes sense but the big picture escapes me right now, especially since it involves complex numbers, which I haven’t touched those in years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Lunch Food</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post-2/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
Lunch break with cantaloupes and warm pandesal with cheese. I usually don’t like eating at my desk when it comes to breads, especially crumbly breads like pandesal but I was totally craving it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Scientific Papers</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 03:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/tumblr-post/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
 
I forgot where I heard this tip but it’s good to read papers that are in your field in your spare time. I spent like an hour looking for PDFs that I didn’t have to pay to read when I remembered that my university library provides free access to databases and databases of papers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Using Staedtler Triplus Fineliners</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/using-staedtler-triplus-fineliners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/using-staedtler-triplus-fineliners/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
My Staedtler Triplus Fineliners always ran out quickly so I stopped using them. Seeing how popular Staedtler is, I gave them another chance and they look awesome. Except I’m still worried they might run out fast on me again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1/? Favourite Pages From My Notebooks</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/1-favourite-pages-from-my-notebooks-on-the-left-is-a-list-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 23:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/1-favourite-pages-from-my-notebooks-on-the-left-is-a-list-of/</guid>
      <description>1/? Favourite pages from my notebooks
On the left is a list of options courses I can pick from for my concentration and my schedule for the next two semesters. On the right is all of the course requirements for my degree and the courses I’m taking to fulfil them. I can’t believe I’m already halfway through my degree! Also, I love writing in monochrome. Boring, I know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Planner for 2015</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/diy-planner-for-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 02:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/diy-planner-for-2015/</guid>
      <description>2015.08.12 &amp;#8211; Working on my DIY planner while watching my brother playing GTAV in the living room. This time, I’m not using my Filofax because I can’t dedicate that much time to cutting up that much paper. As always, my pages are heavily inspired by DIYfish’s Life Mapping System inserts. I just love being able to see my monthly view and (half of) my weekly view at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Week of Half-Way Year</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/first-week-of-half-way-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 04:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/first-week-of-half-way-year/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m now in my third year of university. That&amp;rsquo;s an extremely scary thought for me, haha. High school seems like it was just yesterday (to be fair, it was only two years ago). Despite this being my third year, this is technically my middle year. I switched majors which added year to my degree. I&amp;rsquo;ve already done two years and after I finish this year, I have two more years to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/random-tumblr-posts-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 02:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/random-tumblr-posts-3/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Implied misogynistic content, alluding to the USBC shootings, and mentions of rape.
I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I&amp;rsquo;ve made on Tumblr.
 I was listening to an episode of the Internet Box, which was recorded around the time when Andrew got a Tumblr and started stirring the pot with the social justice fan community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/random-tumblr-posts-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 02:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/random-tumblr-posts-2/</guid>
      <description>I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I&amp;rsquo;ve made on Tumblr.
 In Mass Effect 4 I just want to talk more. I want to learn more about their cultures and I want to do stuff for them, even if it’s just talking them through decisions and not going to the ends of the universe for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/random-tumblr-posts-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/random-tumblr-posts-1/</guid>
      <description>Ugh I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible.
 I had a dream where I literally just lived out my entire day, down to sitting in lecture being bored and taking notes.
You don’t even know how disappointed I am when I woke up knowing that I had to do it all over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurriedly Catching Memories</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/hurriedly-catching-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 01:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/hurriedly-catching-memories/</guid>
      <description>Writing stuff down in a list because I&amp;rsquo;m so tired but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to forget.
 Pizza 73 is no longer a thing. They took it out of our food court on campus to replace it with Tim&amp;rsquo;s. The lack of pizza on campus makes me sad! The Korean place omg. We waited for like three waves of full length lines until the order was ready. Ok. I&amp;rsquo;ve never gotten shushed before, oops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Monday After is Always the Worst</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/the-monday-after-is-always-the-worst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 23:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/the-monday-after-is-always-the-worst/</guid>
      <description>The Monday after reading week is always the worst, that is. I told my friend who is from the States that I had reading week and she had no idea what it is. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty much a Canadian/Commonwealth countries thing where we get a couple days off in the middle of the semester. I heard from the grapevine that reading week started because mid-semester is a period when too stressed out students tend to commit suicide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No, I Don’t Actually Do Anything With My “Free Time”</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/no-i-dont-actually-do-anything-with-my-free-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 05:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/no-i-dont-actually-do-anything-with-my-free-time/</guid>
      <description>When I tell people I’m only taking three courses they immediately ask if I have a job
I would like one because money but at the same time I don’t tell them that I’m on academic probation
If I don’t get a GPA of 2.0 or higher I WILL get kicked out of university and it will be hard as fuck to get back in
I don’t want to get a job because I don’t want to risk it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 Resolutions</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/2014-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 06:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/2014-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>Write a blog post every week
Writing a blog post every day is pretty much impossible for me. However, I still want to post regularly. Posting weekly sounds pretty doable for me. There are 168 hours in a week. If I can&amp;rsquo;t fit in at least one blog post in there, I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to rethink my current time management system.
Spend less than 30 minutes on YouTube everyday</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘Twas the Night Before the Last Final….</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/twas-the-night-before-the-last-final/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 05:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/twas-the-night-before-the-last-final/</guid>
      <description>And all though the house
Not a creature was stirring
Not even a certain university student who should be cramming.
Today was everything but studying. I had the intentions of doing so. I even planned out my day! Then things happened. Those things consist of: music and Ray. I spent most of my day hanging out on Last.fm. Then I went to make a quick tweet about how much I hate recursion, for when I actually decided to crack open my textbook for two seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Finals Down, One More to Go</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/2-finals-down-one-more-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 01:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/2-finals-down-one-more-to-go/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m done all the finals that I&amp;rsquo;m mostly concerned about. Ok, I&amp;rsquo;m also concerned about CPSC 231 but not as much as I was about the other two. The main reason why I&amp;rsquo;m concerned about it? I don&amp;rsquo;t want to let senpai down. Lame, I know. Super lame. But I don&amp;rsquo;t want to look like an idiot in front of him! It&amp;rsquo;s a super easy course and if I screw it up, it&amp;rsquo;s super embarrassing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not So Subtle</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/not-so-subtle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 07:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/not-so-subtle/</guid>
      <description>That moment when your TA is looking at you not so subtly. Or maybe I just have sucky peripheral vision. WOW I really hope the latter is not the case. Man, my heart is so doki doki when I think about him. Much dork. :(</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2013 Semester in Review</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/fall-2013-semester-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 06:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/fall-2013-semester-in-review/</guid>
      <description>This semester went by really quickly. I never once thought, &amp;ldquo;wow I want this semester to be over.&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m not joking, really! I really enjoyed it. Then again, it could be due to the fact that I only took three courses this semester: introduction to Python, Russian literature in translation, and linear algebra. They were all pretty fair courses. I already had some programming experience (once you are exposed one programming language, it&amp;rsquo;s easier to read other languages), my Russian professor was quite easy, and I knew most of the content in linear algebra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having an Off Day</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/having-an-off-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 06:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/having-an-off-day/</guid>
      <description>Today I do something new. This is my writing. I did not intend to post it on my blog but then I realized I released all of my feelings here. Feels good I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doki Doki Senpai</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/doki-doki-senpai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 04:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/doki-doki-senpai/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday1 I chatted a bit with my senpai. He was so adorable. :( Now I&amp;rsquo;m sure he does not have feelings for me which is both a relief and a disappointment at the same time. Relief because lol that could get too complicated and a disappointment because he&amp;rsquo;s so cute. D:
However, today I did talk to him. I asked him how his weekend was. Apparently it was bad. He spent the whole weekend writing an eleven page paper about network systems and stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doki Doki Goes the Heart</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/doki-doki-goes-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 02:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/doki-doki-goes-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>My heart hasn&amp;rsquo;t gone doki doki in a while. The last time I can remember is when I was in my freshman year of high school when I was crushing on my first boyfriend1. This was, of course, before last Friday.
On Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays I have my first class with three of my friends. We all have a break after the class so we eat together. Last Friday, we decided to eat in the ICT building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missed a Day</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/missed-a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 00:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/missed-a-day/</guid>
      <description>Even though yesterday technically has a post, I did not post it until today. Therefore, I missed a day. Being the procrastinator that I am, I usually leave these blog posts until around 11:00pm at night, when I&amp;rsquo;m lying in bed. However, last night I was not lying in bed. Instead, I was seated in front of my brother&amp;rsquo;s laptop, trying to finish an essay. My essay was not due today but I ended up staying up until 3:30 in the morning working on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Not Good at Writing</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-not-good-at-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 06:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-not-good-at-writing/</guid>
      <description>Moments like these, I question my desire to go to graduate school. I have a paper to write by Friday. I was told to basically start over and I&amp;rsquo;m stuck. It&amp;rsquo;s on a novel and we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to pull out symbols for it and I&amp;rsquo;m just drawing a blank. My prof started connecting some of them and I tried to follow suit but they&amp;rsquo;re too far fetched. I&amp;rsquo;m really frustrated and I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Far, So Good</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/so-far-so-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 03:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/so-far-so-good/</guid>
      <description>I am almost done my first month of my second year at university! It&amp;rsquo;s been an interesting year leading up to now. I got into university, turned 18, hated engineering with a passion, sucked at engineering with a passion, went to the Philippines, switched majors (in a transition major right now until I can switch into computer science please don&amp;rsquo;t ask me what it is), got a job as a cashier at Walmart over the summer (don&amp;rsquo;t ask me about that either please), got my courses for this semester dropped, went to fix my schedule, found out it wasn&amp;rsquo;t actually fixed and didn&amp;rsquo;t find out until a few days into the first week, and went to go fix it yet again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Bad for the Environment</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-bad-for-the-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 20:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-bad-for-the-environment/</guid>
      <description>These days, most people are going paperless. With things like &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; and thousands of web and mobile apps that can do almost anything you want, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be hard. However, I&amp;rsquo;m going the opposite way. I&amp;rsquo;m going back to paper.
Why on earth would I possibly want to do this? Easy. Smartphones, while useful, also carry a lot of temptations. Sure, you can have 10 note-taking, productivity, schedule apps but you also have an Internet browser, a music player, and quite possibly, a nice library of games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Needs One Topic Blog Posts?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description>I quit Tumblr for Lent. It&amp;rsquo;s only been a couple of days, and I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated so many Tumblr blog posts in my mind and it&amp;rsquo;s kinda driving me crazy. So crazy to the point where a Tumblr and serious blog crossover is inevitable. Tumblr posts are mostly Twitter-like in nature, except ten times the sarcasm, ten times the ironic usage of poor grammar and spelling, and ten times that length.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Semester: Tougher Than I Thought It Would Be</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/second-semester-tougher-than-it-would-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/second-semester-tougher-than-it-would-be/</guid>
      <description>My New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolutions aren&amp;rsquo;t going so well. I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I&amp;rsquo;ve broken at least half of them already! But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I&amp;rsquo;m giving up on them. I&amp;rsquo;m starting fresh this week, and I will get stuff done.
This week is going to be tough. I have two midterms on subjects that I have absolutely no idea on what&amp;rsquo;s going on. I didn&amp;rsquo;t study as much as I wanted to on the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Resolutions for 2013</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/13-resolutions-for-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 22:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/13-resolutions-for-2013/</guid>
      <description>A new year, a new set of resolutions, probably another year where said resolutions are never fulfilled. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t hurt to at least dream, yeah? Usually most people do these resolution posts on the first day of the year, but I do mine second! No, I was busy with the opening of my new blog, go check it out. On with the post!
1. Post more I hate how this has to be a resolution, but yes, I want to post more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Through It</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/getting-through-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 22:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/getting-through-it/</guid>
      <description>Christmas break is here and so is a new layout. It&amp;rsquo;s not my own, but I was just enamored by it&amp;rsquo;s simplicity. Enjoy! Whew, I finally made it through my very first semester in university. I must say, it was quite a ride. I&amp;rsquo;m glad I got through it. Finals are behind me and now I can just relax. Even though I do want to take this time to chill out and slow down the pace, I also want to be productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procrastination Nation</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/procrastination-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 20:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/procrastination-nation/</guid>
      <description>Two blog posts in a week?? Is this even possible? I&amp;rsquo;m probably dreaming but it&amp;rsquo;s happening. For real.
Whenever I first get on the computer, I find myself starting out pretty darn focused. I open up Blackboard, see what&amp;rsquo;s new, check my falling grades, cry, start on my assignments, etc. Then suddenly it&amp;rsquo;s 1 in the morning (I&amp;rsquo;m exaggerating, the latest I&amp;rsquo;ve started homework was like 10pm&amp;hellip; Still pretty bad though).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s That Time of Year Again</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/its-that-time-of-year-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 18:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/its-that-time-of-year-again/</guid>
      <description>Usually I bring a textbook with me on the train to study from but today I had only one lecture and I definitely forgot to bring one. So I decided it would be good to write a blog post for once because I really do miss writing these things.
Christmas is indeed in the air! Last week in the food court on campus, Christmas carols were playing and a Santa was walking around asking for donations for some charity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busy Weekends</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/busy-weekends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 21:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/busy-weekends/</guid>
      <description>I have a whole load of things to do this weekend. Not sure if I&amp;rsquo;ll actually get around to doing those said things. But at least my midterms are finally over! But finals start up in two weeks. Huh. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve made a list of things I need to, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t really seem like that much but considering my procrastination habits, it is quite a lot. Weekends are for relaxing, not for drowning myself in tears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Don’t Know</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-dont-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 06:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-dont-know/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been really unmotivated lately. I should be busy with school, but I really am not. Little things keep on discouraging me and causes me to lose sight of the end goal. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with me. I keep telling myself, &amp;ldquo;This is your future at stake! Do you really want to be working 2 or 3 part time jobs?&amp;rdquo; But even so, it does nothing. I&amp;rsquo;m at the point where I seriously think, even for a second, to hell with society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day One of University</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/day-one-of-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/day-one-of-university/</guid>
      <description>Today was my first day of orientation week! While it was fun, I found that it was lacking a bit somehow. I guess I&amp;rsquo;ll just have to see how it&amp;rsquo;ll pan out for the rest of the week. Hopefully it&amp;rsquo;ll be better than today.
It was hectic. I left the house at 7:24 got on the train around 7:40 and got there around 8:20. I was early but apparently too early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Last Day of Freedom</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/my-last-day-of-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 16:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/my-last-day-of-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow I start university. Thank goodness for Labour day. I&amp;rsquo;ve never really understood what Labour day is. All I know is that it delays school by one more day and that&amp;rsquo;s all I need to know to be thankful for it. To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m not at all that excited to be honest. Technically, classes don&amp;rsquo;t start until next week so that&amp;rsquo;s delayed even further.
This week is all orientation. Basically, just having fun and getting to know the campus and mingling with other potential classmates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparation</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/university-and-connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 04:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/university-and-connections/</guid>
      <description>These summer months has been filled with e-mails from my university and just me chatting on the Internet. As September is coming closer everyday, I&amp;rsquo;m getting pretty excited, nervous, and really bummed out. This morning, I received an e-mail listing all of the things I should get done before school starts. Most of them are finished, but there are three major things that I can&amp;rsquo;t actually do just yet.
My picture ID</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally, I Know!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/finally-i-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 04:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/finally-i-know/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finally been officially accepted into the engineering program at my local university!! I&amp;rsquo;m super crazy excited for university. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to start a new clean slate. New school supplies (I admit, I enjoy this part the most), new subjects, new campus, new professors, new schedule, new everything. Speaking of schedules, I&amp;rsquo;ve had my schedule done since May but I was hesitant to post it, seeing as I wasn&amp;rsquo;t 100% sure I was going to be accepted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>