<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The White Book by Han Kang</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-white-book-by-han-kang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-white-book-by-han-kang/</guid>
      <description>The White Book by Han Kang     From the author of The Vegetarian and Human Acts comes a book like no other. The White Book is a meditation on colour, beginning with a list of white things. It is a book about mourning, rebirth and the tenacity of the human spirit. It is a stunning investigation of the fragility, beauty and strangeness of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Snow Country by Yasunari Kawabata</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-snow-country-by-yasunari-kawabata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-snow-country-by-yasunari-kawabata/</guid>
      <description>Snow Country by Yasunari Kawabata     At an isolated mountain hot spring, with snow blanketing every surface, Shinamura, a wealthy dilettante, meets Komako, a lowly geisha. She gives herself to him fully and without remorse, despite knowing that their passion cannot last and that the affair can have only one outcome. In chronicling the course of this doomed romance, Kawabata has created a story for the ages–a stunning novel dense in implication and exalting in its sadness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Men Without Women by Haruki Murakami</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-men-without-women-by-haruki-murakami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-men-without-women-by-haruki-murakami/</guid>
      <description>Men Without Women by Haruki Murakami     Across seven dazzling tales, award-winning internationally best-selling author Haruki Murakami brings his powers of observation to bear on the lives of men, who, in their own ways find themselves alone. Some a trapped indoors, some in their own heads; they are chauffeured around in cars by silent women or haunted by the ghosts of women they once knew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Thousand Cranes by Yasunari Kawabata</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-thousand-cranes-by-yasunari-kawabata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-thousand-cranes-by-yasunari-kawabata/</guid>
      <description>Thousand Cranes by Yasunari Kawabata     While attending a traditional tea ceremony in the aftermath of his parents’ deaths, Kikuji encounters his father’s former mistress, Mrs. Ota. At first Kikuji is appalled by her indelicate nature, but it is not long before he succumbs to passion—a passion with tragic and unforeseen consequences, not just for the two lovers, but also for Mrs. Ota’s daughter, to whom Kikuji’s attachments soon extend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Roadside Picnic by Boris and Arkady Strugatsky</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-roadside-picnic-by-boris-and-arkady-strugatsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-roadside-picnic-by-boris-and-arkady-strugatsky/</guid>
      <description>Roadside Picnic by Boris and Arkady Strugatsky     Red Schuhart is a stalker, one of those young rebels who are compelled, in spite of extreme danger, to venture illegally into the Zone to collect the mysterious artifacts that the alien visitors left scattered around. His life is dominated by the place and the thriving black market in the alien products. But when he and his friend Kirill go into the Zone together to pick up a &amp;ldquo;full empty,&amp;rdquo; something goes wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World by Haruki Murakami</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-hard-boiled-wonderland-and-the-end-of-the-world-by-haruki-murakami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-hard-boiled-wonderland-and-the-end-of-the-world-by-haruki-murakami/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Spoilers abound!
  Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World by Haruki Murakami     Hyperkinetic and relentlessly inventive, Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World is Haruki Murakami&amp;rsquo;s deep dive into the very nature of consciousness.
Across two parallel narratives, Murakami draws readers into a mind-bending universe in which Lauren Bacall, Bob Dylan, a split-brained data processor, a deranged scientist, his shockingly undemure granddaughter, and various thugs, librarians, and subterranean monsters collide to a dazzling effect.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>