<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: 168 Hours by Laura Vanderkam</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-168-hours-by-laura-vanderkam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-168-hours-by-laura-vanderkam/</guid>
      <description>168 Hours by Laura Vanderkam     There are 168 hours in a week. This is your guide to getting the most out of them.
It&amp;rsquo;s an unquestioned truth of modern life: we are starved for time. We tell ourselves we&amp;rsquo;d like to read more, get to the gym regularly, try new hobbies, and accomplish all kinds of goals. But then we give up because there just aren&amp;rsquo;t enough hours to do it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Mrs. Dalloway</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-mrs-dalloway-by-virginia-woolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-mrs-dalloway-by-virginia-woolf/</guid>
      <description>Mrs. Dalloway by Virginia Woolf     Mrs. Dalloway was the first novel to split the atom. If the novel before Mrs. Dalloway aspired to immensities of scope and scale, to heroic journeys across vast landscapes, with Mrs. Dalloway Virginia Woolf insisted that it could also locate the enormous within the everyday; that a life of errands and party-giving was every bit as viable a subject as any life lived anywhere; and that should any human act in any novel seem unimportant, it has merely been inadequately observed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: BUtterfield 8 by John O&#39;Hara</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-butterfield-8-by-john-o-hara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-butterfield-8-by-john-o-hara/</guid>
      <description>BUtterfield 8 by John O&amp;#39;Hara     &amp;ldquo;Ligget was precisely the sort of person who, if he hadn&amp;rsquo;t married Emily, would be just the perfect person for Emily to snub.
 This book captivated me. From the moment Gloria stepped on to the page, I was hooked. This young and feisty woman is surprisingly progressive for her time: sleeping around, smoking, staying up all hours of the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The War of the Worlds by H.G. Wells</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-war-of-the-worlds-by-h-g-wells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-war-of-the-worlds-by-h-g-wells/</guid>
      <description>The War of the Worlds by H.G. Wells     The suburbs of north London are an unlikely spot from which to witness the total breakdown of society, and yet in 1897-8 that is what happened—at least in the imagination of H.G. Wells. In The War of the Worlds Martians lands in Woking, and then make their way remorselessly towards the capital, wreaking chaos, death, and destruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Beauty and Sadness by Yasunari Kawabata</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-beauty-and-sadness-by-yasunari-kawabata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-beauty-and-sadness-by-yasunari-kawabata/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This post contains sensitive themes. Read at your own risk.
  Beauty and Sadness by Yasunari Kawabata     Love as sickness and immorality, sex as entrapment and revenge—these are the themes that the Nobel Prize-winning author of Snow Country dramatizes with such coolly mesmerizing power in this novel. At its heart is is a destructive love affair between a married writer and a teenage girl that continues to haunt both of them more than twenty years after their last embrace—and whose lingering bitterness poisons everyone around them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Deep Work by Cal Newport</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-deep-work-by-cal-newport/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-deep-work-by-cal-newport/</guid>
      <description>Deep Work by Cal Newport     Deep work is the ability to focus without distraction on a cognitively demanding task. It&amp;rsquo;s a skill that allows you to quickly master complicated information and produce better results in less time. Deep work will make you better at what you do and provide the sense of true fulfillment that comes from craftsmanship. In short, deep work is like a super power in our increasingly competitive twenty-first century economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Definitely Maybe by Arkady and Boris Strugatsky</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-definitely-maybe-by-arkady-and-boris-strugatsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-definitely-maybe-by-arkady-and-boris-strugatsky/</guid>
      <description>Definitle Maybe by Arkady and Boris Strugatsky     Boris and Arkady Strugatsky were the greatest science fiction writers of the Soviet era: their books were intellectually provocative and riotously funny, full of boldly imagined scenarios and veiled—but clear—social criticism. Which may be why Definitely Maybe has never before been available in an uncensored edition, let alone in English.
It tells the story of astrophysicist Dmitri Malianov, who has sent his wife and son off to her mother’s house in Odessa so that he can work, free from distractions, on the project he’s sure will win him the Nobel Prize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The White Book by Han Kang</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-white-book-by-han-kang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-white-book-by-han-kang/</guid>
      <description>The White Book by Han Kang     From the author of The Vegetarian and Human Acts comes a book like no other. The White Book is a meditation on colour, beginning with a list of white things. It is a book about mourning, rebirth and the tenacity of the human spirit. It is a stunning investigation of the fragility, beauty and strangeness of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Snow Country by Yasunari Kawabata</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-snow-country-by-yasunari-kawabata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-snow-country-by-yasunari-kawabata/</guid>
      <description>Snow Country by Yasunari Kawabata     At an isolated mountain hot spring, with snow blanketing every surface, Shinamura, a wealthy dilettante, meets Komako, a lowly geisha. She gives herself to him fully and without remorse, despite knowing that their passion cannot last and that the affair can have only one outcome. In chronicling the course of this doomed romance, Kawabata has created a story for the ages–a stunning novel dense in implication and exalting in its sadness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Men Without Women by Haruki Murakami</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-men-without-women-by-haruki-murakami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-men-without-women-by-haruki-murakami/</guid>
      <description>Men Without Women by Haruki Murakami     Across seven dazzling tales, award-winning internationally best-selling author Haruki Murakami brings his powers of observation to bear on the lives of men, who, in their own ways find themselves alone. Some a trapped indoors, some in their own heads; they are chauffeured around in cars by silent women or haunted by the ghosts of women they once knew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Thousand Cranes by Yasunari Kawabata</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-thousand-cranes-by-yasunari-kawabata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-thousand-cranes-by-yasunari-kawabata/</guid>
      <description>Thousand Cranes by Yasunari Kawabata     While attending a traditional tea ceremony in the aftermath of his parents’ deaths, Kikuji encounters his father’s former mistress, Mrs. Ota. At first Kikuji is appalled by her indelicate nature, but it is not long before he succumbs to passion—a passion with tragic and unforeseen consequences, not just for the two lovers, but also for Mrs. Ota’s daughter, to whom Kikuji’s attachments soon extend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Roadside Picnic by Boris and Arkady Strugatsky</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-roadside-picnic-by-boris-and-arkady-strugatsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-roadside-picnic-by-boris-and-arkady-strugatsky/</guid>
      <description>Roadside Picnic by Boris and Arkady Strugatsky     Red Schuhart is a stalker, one of those young rebels who are compelled, in spite of extreme danger, to venture illegally into the Zone to collect the mysterious artifacts that the alien visitors left scattered around. His life is dominated by the place and the thriving black market in the alien products. But when he and his friend Kirill go into the Zone together to pick up a &amp;ldquo;full empty,&amp;rdquo; something goes wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World by Haruki Murakami</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-hard-boiled-wonderland-and-the-end-of-the-world-by-haruki-murakami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-hard-boiled-wonderland-and-the-end-of-the-world-by-haruki-murakami/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Spoilers abound!
  Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World by Haruki Murakami     Hyperkinetic and relentlessly inventive, Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World is Haruki Murakami&amp;rsquo;s deep dive into the very nature of consciousness.
Across two parallel narratives, Murakami draws readers into a mind-bending universe in which Lauren Bacall, Bob Dylan, a split-brained data processor, a deranged scientist, his shockingly undemure granddaughter, and various thugs, librarians, and subterranean monsters collide to a dazzling effect.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>