<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #63</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-63/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-63/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 You meet an interesting person of the opposite sex at a club. Suddenly, they start acting as if they&amp;rsquo;re a character in a novel you&amp;rsquo;ve read, and they are firmly convinced that they ARE that character. First, which character is it, and second, how do you react?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Mrs. Dalloway</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-mrs-dalloway-by-virginia-woolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-mrs-dalloway-by-virginia-woolf/</guid>
      <description>Mrs. Dalloway by Virginia Woolf     Mrs. Dalloway was the first novel to split the atom. If the novel before Mrs. Dalloway aspired to immensities of scope and scale, to heroic journeys across vast landscapes, with Mrs. Dalloway Virginia Woolf insisted that it could also locate the enormous within the everyday; that a life of errands and party-giving was every bit as viable a subject as any life lived anywhere; and that should any human act in any novel seem unimportant, it has merely been inadequately observed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #62</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-62/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-62/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you take notes about the book you are reading as you read?
 I only really do this for non-fiction books. Sometimes I take pictures of quotes that really stick out to me. One of these days I will actually capture these quotes and compile them into one place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: BUtterfield 8 by John O&#39;Hara</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-butterfield-8-by-john-o-hara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-butterfield-8-by-john-o-hara/</guid>
      <description>BUtterfield 8 by John O&amp;#39;Hara     &amp;ldquo;Ligget was precisely the sort of person who, if he hadn&amp;rsquo;t married Emily, would be just the perfect person for Emily to snub.
 This book captivated me. From the moment Gloria stepped on to the page, I was hooked. This young and feisty woman is surprisingly progressive for her time: sleeping around, smoking, staying up all hours of the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #61</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-61/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-61/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you subscribe to any book subscription boxes?
 Nope! I don&amp;rsquo;t like spending money to take a chance on a book. These days I just go to the library so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to risk my money on a book I might not like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The War of the Worlds by H.G. Wells</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-war-of-the-worlds-by-h-g-wells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-war-of-the-worlds-by-h-g-wells/</guid>
      <description>The War of the Worlds by H.G. Wells     The suburbs of north London are an unlikely spot from which to witness the total breakdown of society, and yet in 1897-8 that is what happened—at least in the imagination of H.G. Wells. In The War of the Worlds Martians lands in Woking, and then make their way remorselessly towards the capital, wreaking chaos, death, and destruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #60</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-60/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-60/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you do collaborations with brands or other bloggers? Which collaboration was your favorite and why?
 Nope. Once I interviewed a blogger, Graeme Inge, a software engineer and author. Does that count as a collaboration? Other than that, I usually stick to my own bubble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Beauty and Sadness by Yasunari Kawabata</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-beauty-and-sadness-by-yasunari-kawabata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-beauty-and-sadness-by-yasunari-kawabata/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This post contains sensitive themes. Read at your own risk.
  Beauty and Sadness by Yasunari Kawabata     Love as sickness and immorality, sex as entrapment and revenge—these are the themes that the Nobel Prize-winning author of Snow Country dramatizes with such coolly mesmerizing power in this novel. At its heart is is a destructive love affair between a married writer and a teenage girl that continues to haunt both of them more than twenty years after their last embrace—and whose lingering bitterness poisons everyone around them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #59</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-59/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-59/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Recommend one horror novel for nonhorror readers.
 Mary Shelley&amp;rsquo;s Frankenstein. I can only say that because that&amp;rsquo;s the only horror novel that I&amp;rsquo;ve ever read. But it&amp;rsquo;s a classic for a reason. It&amp;rsquo;s also interesting how the original story is as there&amp;rsquo;s been so many interpretations and spin offs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Deep Work by Cal Newport</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-deep-work-by-cal-newport/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-deep-work-by-cal-newport/</guid>
      <description>Deep Work by Cal Newport     Deep work is the ability to focus without distraction on a cognitively demanding task. It&amp;rsquo;s a skill that allows you to quickly master complicated information and produce better results in less time. Deep work will make you better at what you do and provide the sense of true fulfillment that comes from craftsmanship. In short, deep work is like a super power in our increasingly competitive twenty-first century economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #58</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-58/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-58/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you were to dress up as a literary figure {author or character} for Halloween, who would it be?
 Hmm&amp;hellip; That&amp;rsquo;s a good question. I would totally dress up as Anne Shirley from Anne of Green Gables. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I could pull off the red hair though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WIP Wednesday: Snowfall Mittens</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/wip-wednesday-snowfall-mittens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/wip-wednesday-snowfall-mittens/</guid>
      <description>WIP stands for a &amp;ldquo;work in progress.&amp;rdquo; As an avid crafter, I always have at least one WIP!
  Yarn: Loops and Threads Urban (Rust) Pattern: Snowfall Mittens    Snowfall Mittens    I have finished one half of my Christmas present to one of my cousins. I&amp;rsquo;ve had this yarn sitting in my stash for a long time (I bought it a year and a half ago).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Definitely Maybe by Arkady and Boris Strugatsky</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-definitely-maybe-by-arkady-and-boris-strugatsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-definitely-maybe-by-arkady-and-boris-strugatsky/</guid>
      <description>Definitle Maybe by Arkady and Boris Strugatsky     Boris and Arkady Strugatsky were the greatest science fiction writers of the Soviet era: their books were intellectually provocative and riotously funny, full of boldly imagined scenarios and veiled—but clear—social criticism. Which may be why Definitely Maybe has never before been available in an uncensored edition, let alone in English.
It tells the story of astrophysicist Dmitri Malianov, who has sent his wife and son off to her mother’s house in Odessa so that he can work, free from distractions, on the project he’s sure will win him the Nobel Prize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #57</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-57/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-57/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 You are suddenly transported into a future time in which (horrors!) books are unknown. How would you explain books, and how wonderful they are, to the people of that time?
 UH. That&amp;rsquo;s so hard, especially since I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand what is considered as horror.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The White Book by Han Kang</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-white-book-by-han-kang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-white-book-by-han-kang/</guid>
      <description>The White Book by Han Kang     From the author of The Vegetarian and Human Acts comes a book like no other. The White Book is a meditation on colour, beginning with a list of white things. It is a book about mourning, rebirth and the tenacity of the human spirit. It is a stunning investigation of the fragility, beauty and strangeness of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #56</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-56/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 It&amp;rsquo;s getting close to Halloween. If you HAD to read one of these two genres, which would you prefer urban fantasy, or horror, and why?
 I have no idea. I don&amp;rsquo;t read either, honestly. I think the last horror story I read was Frankenstein.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Snow Country by Yasunari Kawabata</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-snow-country-by-yasunari-kawabata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-snow-country-by-yasunari-kawabata/</guid>
      <description>Snow Country by Yasunari Kawabata     At an isolated mountain hot spring, with snow blanketing every surface, Shinamura, a wealthy dilettante, meets Komako, a lowly geisha. She gives herself to him fully and without remorse, despite knowing that their passion cannot last and that the affair can have only one outcome. In chronicling the course of this doomed romance, Kawabata has created a story for the ages–a stunning novel dense in implication and exalting in its sadness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #55</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-55/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-55/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you sneak a peek at the number of views your posts have gotten?
 Nope! I don&amp;rsquo;t think anyone except for my friends reads my blog or people who somehow stumble upon on my blog from Google. I don&amp;rsquo;t really care that much about view count.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Men Without Women by Haruki Murakami</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-men-without-women-by-haruki-murakami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-men-without-women-by-haruki-murakami/</guid>
      <description>Men Without Women by Haruki Murakami     Across seven dazzling tales, award-winning internationally best-selling author Haruki Murakami brings his powers of observation to bear on the lives of men, who, in their own ways find themselves alone. Some a trapped indoors, some in their own heads; they are chauffeured around in cars by silent women or haunted by the ghosts of women they once knew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #54</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-54/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you like to finish one book before starting the next or do you read several at once?
 I&amp;rsquo;m notorious for reading several books at once but eventually it turns into reading one book at a time. I have a ton of books I&amp;rsquo;ve started only to drop for another book instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #53</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-53/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What author do you not read and why?
 Right off the top of my head, I don&amp;rsquo;t read Jodi Picoult anymore. I used to really like Jodi Picoult after reading My Sister&amp;rsquo;s Keeper and I went on a binge just reading work after work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Thousand Cranes by Yasunari Kawabata</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-thousand-cranes-by-yasunari-kawabata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-thousand-cranes-by-yasunari-kawabata/</guid>
      <description>Thousand Cranes by Yasunari Kawabata     While attending a traditional tea ceremony in the aftermath of his parents’ deaths, Kikuji encounters his father’s former mistress, Mrs. Ota. At first Kikuji is appalled by her indelicate nature, but it is not long before he succumbs to passion—a passion with tragic and unforeseen consequences, not just for the two lovers, but also for Mrs. Ota’s daughter, to whom Kikuji’s attachments soon extend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #52</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-52/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Have you ever visited the location of a book you have read?
 I&amp;rsquo;m Canadian and I rarely go out of my city. I have been the Philippines before and once spent a week in New York City. Not many books take place in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Roadside Picnic by Boris and Arkady Strugatsky</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-roadside-picnic-by-boris-and-arkady-strugatsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-roadside-picnic-by-boris-and-arkady-strugatsky/</guid>
      <description>Roadside Picnic by Boris and Arkady Strugatsky     Red Schuhart is a stalker, one of those young rebels who are compelled, in spite of extreme danger, to venture illegally into the Zone to collect the mysterious artifacts that the alien visitors left scattered around. His life is dominated by the place and the thriving black market in the alien products. But when he and his friend Kirill go into the Zone together to pick up a &amp;ldquo;full empty,&amp;rdquo; something goes wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #51</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-51/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you have a YouTube channel? If so, do you post book review vlogs?
 I technically have a YouTube channel. It&amp;rsquo;s more a hub for past course projects. I don&amp;rsquo;t post any videos on it. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I would ever do book review vlogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #50</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-50/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Where do you post your reviews besides your blog? Please list them all so perhaps we can find some new sites.
 Almost always I post my reviews on Goodreads. I think my profile is private but here is a link to my profile anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #49</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-49/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-49/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you follow other book blogs and if so, who are your top 3 bloggers?
 Not really. I follow a blog that does book reviews ocassionally but I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say they are a book blog.
Jane at Janepedia is that blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #48</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-48/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Can you say this about yourself? Nothing makes me happier than sitting down with a good book.
 Not even close.
Some things that make as happy or happier:
 Eating really good food Having a meaningful conversation with a friend Sitting in the field in my father&amp;rsquo;s homeland looking up a starry sky Listening to a good song in the window seat of a train watching the city pass by Playing a video game and being absorbed in a virtual world Falling asleep to the sound of rain Singing along to my favourite songs Watching a good TV series that can make me sob Walking along the river on a sunny day Going to a concert Playing with really cute babies Dog spotting around the city Etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World by Haruki Murakami</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-hard-boiled-wonderland-and-the-end-of-the-world-by-haruki-murakami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-hard-boiled-wonderland-and-the-end-of-the-world-by-haruki-murakami/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Spoilers abound!
  Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World by Haruki Murakami     Hyperkinetic and relentlessly inventive, Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World is Haruki Murakami&amp;rsquo;s deep dive into the very nature of consciousness.
Across two parallel narratives, Murakami draws readers into a mind-bending universe in which Lauren Bacall, Bob Dylan, a split-brained data processor, a deranged scientist, his shockingly undemure granddaughter, and various thugs, librarians, and subterranean monsters collide to a dazzling effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #47</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-47/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Have you ever had a bookish, nocturnal dream? If so, please share the story. If not, have you ever had a daydream related to books? If so, please tell us about it.
 Strangely enough, I can&amp;rsquo;t think of any bookish dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #46</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-46/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you agree or disagree with this statement: A blogger&amp;rsquo;s first name should be in a prominent place on his/her blog.
 I definitely agree! Even if the name is an alias, putting a name to the blog can do wonders in making a blog feel more personable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #45</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-45/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-45/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What&amp;rsquo;s your proudest blogging milestone or achievement?
 I think the fact that I&amp;rsquo;ve had a blog for so long is an achievement. I&amp;rsquo;ve been blogging since 2007, so I&amp;rsquo;ve been blogging for over ten years now. I remember blogging on a platform called Mibba.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #44</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-44/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-44/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Does a cluttered blog have you not returning? By cluttered I mean too many columns, small type, too many photos, difficult to follow, etc.
 Interestingly, I rarely visit blogs anymore. I only ever really visit a blog when a blog I am subscribed to pops up on my RSS reader and I feel compelled to comment on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #43</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-43/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you were stranded on a deserted island, which ONE book could you not live without?
 OH MAN. This is such a hard question. Would I bring my favourite book, Vilette by Charlotte Brontë? I&amp;rsquo;ve only read it once, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I could read it more than a couple of times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #42</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-42/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you have an Instagram account? If so, do you only follow book folks?
 I do have an Instagram account! Shameless plug, @edelgraceme.
The people I follow are usually my friends. Sometimes I follow some comic artists because I enjoy some humor every now and then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #41</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-41/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 For all of you worker bees out there! How do you balance having a day job/career and managing your blog at night? Is it hard or easy to do, and what do people in your work life think of your blogs?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #40</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-40/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-40/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 You have just won a $100.00 Visa gift card. Will you spend the entire amount on a rare collector&amp;rsquo;s edition you have always wanted, or buy several newlypublished books? Explain your choice.
 For a hot moment, I wanted to buy all the editions of Vilette by Charlotte Brontë that I could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #39</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-39/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What author have you read the most in the past two years?
 Not including manga artists, that would by Ursula K. Le Guin.
I just happened to come across Le Guin by chance. I was itching to read some sci-fi but I was daunted by all the thick hardcover volumes at my local library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #38</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-38/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What do you think your blog says about you?
 Not a lot, that&amp;rsquo;s for sure. I think because my blog is so all over the place in topics, I think that reflects a bunch of different aspects of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #37</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-37/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you remember the first book you read by yourself?
 Nope. Not at all. I&amp;rsquo;m not even going to attempt to try to figure this out. I can see picture books in my mind but damn&amp;hellip; That was such a long time ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #36</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-36/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What were your worst movies based off of books?
 WARNING: Spoilers for My Sister&amp;rsquo;s Keeper by Jodi Picoult.
When I go to see a movie based off a book, I don&amp;rsquo;t go in with high expectations. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t a Harry Potter nerd by any stretch of imagination so those movies didn&amp;rsquo;t bother me despite their departures from the source material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #35</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-35/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Could you ever pick a favorite book or is it like choosing your favorite child?
 I don&amp;rsquo;t like comparing books to children. It&amp;rsquo;s impossible for me to be impartial to a book. Every book deserves to be judged, simply because it exists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #34</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-34/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you ever feel like you have emerged better for reading a book?
 There are times when I have felt like I had the potential to be better after reading a book. Very rarely does it actually come into fruition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #33</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-33/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Have you ever thought of writing a respectful, but angry letter to an author to ask them WHY they killed off one of your favorite characters in a novel?
 My initial reaction was no but when I thought about it, there has only been one favourite of mine character who was killed off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #32</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-32/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you organize your books for review? Does it work for you or have you had to change it?
 I just write reviews of books as I read them. No organization needed. Everything goes into one category: &amp;ldquo;Book&amp;rdquo; and then it gets the tag &amp;ldquo;review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #31</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-31/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Is there a fictitious town in a book that you would love to live in? What makes it appealing?
 This is a good question. The first town I thought of is Avonlea, Prince Edward Island. Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been having Anne of Green Gables on my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #30</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-30/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you overextend yourself with too many reviews because you can&amp;rsquo;t pass up a book in hopes you will get them all done or do you carefully plan and be sure you can fulfill the deadlines for all the promised reviews?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #29</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-29/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How many book clubs do you belong to? If you do belong to an inperson book club, do you have meetings in the day or evening? Do you meet at someone&amp;rsquo;s house or meet at a local restaurant or coffee house?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Its Monday What Are You Reading #1 &#43; Weekly Recap</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/its-monday-what-are-you-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 13:27:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/its-monday-what-are-you-reading/</guid>
      <description>BookDate has a weekly running event where we all post what we&amp;rsquo;re reading this week!
What I read Last Week I finally finished reading David Allen&amp;rsquo;s Getting Things Done! I&amp;rsquo;ve always heard about the infamous GTD method and finally decided to read the book. I am not sure if I want to write a review for it yet because I can&amp;rsquo;t really judge how well the process works before I actually implement it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #28</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-28/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 When meeting with friends, do your discussions usually turn to books?
 Not really. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve had any conversations with friends about books. Actually, the last conversation that comes to mind is around when Ursula K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #26</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-26/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you enjoy reading retellings of, or &amp;lsquo;sequels&amp;rsquo; to, classic novels? Why or why not?
 I can&amp;rsquo;t think off the top of my head of any retellings of classic novels that I&amp;rsquo;ve read before. I&amp;rsquo;ve read plenty of retellings of myths and fairy tales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #25</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-25/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Off the book topic&amp;hellip;do you use a mouse pad? If so, what is on it?
 I do not use a mouse pad! I don&amp;rsquo;t even own a mouse pad. I just use whatever surface I&amp;rsquo;m using for a mouse pad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #24</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-24/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you read hardcovers with the dust jacket on or off? Why or why not?
 Sometimes, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a choice. A good number of books I read are from the library. If a hardcover has a dust jacket, it&amp;rsquo;s gauranteed that the dust jacket is taped to the covers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Sky is Yours by Chandler Klang Smith</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-the-sky-is-yours-by-chandler-klang-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-the-sky-is-yours-by-chandler-klang-smith/</guid>
      <description>The Sky is Yours by Chandler Klang Smith     A sprawling, genre-defying epic set in a dystopian metropolis plagued by dragons, this debut about what it’s like to be young in a very old world is pure storytelling pleasure
In the burned-out, futuristic city of Empire Island, three young people navigate a crumbling metropolis constantly under threat from a pair of dragons that circle the skies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #23</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-23/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Have you ever found yourself acting like a favorite character in a novel? If so, which one?
 Not at all! The only time I find myself acting like anyone other than myself is if I&amp;rsquo;m acting like my friends as a result of months of exposure to their quirks and traits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Unreal and the Real by Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-the-unreal-and-the-real-vol-1-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-the-unreal-and-the-real-vol-1-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</guid>
      <description>The Unreal and the Real Volume One: Where on Earth     For fifty years, National Book Award winner Ursula K. Le Guin’s stories have shaped the way her readers see the world. Her work gives voice to the voiceless, hope to the outsider, and speaks truth to power. Le Guin’s writing is witty, wise, both sly and forthright; she is a master craftswoman.
This two-volume selection of almost forty stories taken from her eleven collections was made by Le Guin herself, as was the organizing principle of splitting the stories into the nominally realistic and fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Knitting Sutra by Susan Gordon Lydon</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-the-knitting-sutra-by-susan-gordon-lydon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-the-knitting-sutra-by-susan-gordon-lydon/</guid>
      <description>The Knitting Sutra     When Susan Gordon Lydon was coping with a broken arm, her craft took on new significance. While knitting was essential to strengthening her hands, it also provided her with a newfound sense of peace and creativity. Immersed in brilliant colors, textures, and images of beautiful sweaters, Lydon found healing and enlightenment in a way she had never imagined. Capturing this journey of discovery, The Knitting Sutra recounts her remarkable membership in a community of craftswomen around the world, from sweater makers in Scotland to Navajo weavers, and the adventures that her craft led her on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #22</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-22/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you prefer to blog about (a) specific book genre(s), or do you have an eclectic blog?
 I read a lot of genres and therefore my blog reflects that. So yes, I have an eclectic blog! When I pick books to read, I don&amp;rsquo;t consciously pick something by the genre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiration from Fictional Worlds</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/inspiration-from-fictional-worlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/inspiration-from-fictional-worlds/</guid>
      <description>My last semester was extremely busy. So busy that I spent my commute on the train sleeping everyday instead of my usual reading. I&amp;rsquo;ll admit, most of my reading is done when I&amp;rsquo;m on the train. So other than the occasional manga or cookbook, I hardly read the last couple months of last year. Which is devastating.
This year (like every year), I resolved to read more. I started out the year reading two non-fictional books about personal finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Vegetarian by Han Kang</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 04:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</guid>
      <description>Yeong-hye and her husband are ordinary people. He is an office worker with moderate ambitions and mild manners; she is an uninspired but dutiful wife. The acceptable flatline of their marriage is interrupted when Yeong-hye, seeking a more &amp;#8216;plant-like&amp;rsquo; existence, decides to become a vegetarian, prompted by grotesque recurring nightmares. In South Korea, where vegetarianism is almost unheard-of and societal mores are strictly obeyed, Yeong-hye&amp;rsquo;s decision is a shocking act of subversion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: God in Pink by Hasan Namir</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-god-in-pink-by-hasan-namir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 22:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-god-in-pink-by-hasan-namir/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Topics of sexuality, religion, and spoilers for the book is mentioned in this blog post.
 A revelatory novel about being queer and Muslim, set in war-torn Iraq in 2003. Ramy is a young gay Iraqi struggling to find a balance between his sexuality, religion, and culture. Ammar is a sheikh whose guidance Ramy seeks, and whose tolerance is tested by his belief in the teachings of the Qur&amp;rsquo;an. Full of quiet moments of beauty and raw depictions of violence, God in Pink poignantly captures the anguish and the fortitude of Islamic life in Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #21</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-21/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Name a book that changed your life.
 Busting out the big questions. This is a hard one to answer. I think that I&amp;rsquo;m still trying to find it. I have my favourite books but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure of their impact on my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #20</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 07:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-20/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you are at a really good point in a book and the phone rings or the door bell rings, do you stop reading or let the phone or door bell go unanswered?
 Honestly, I would get up and check them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Vital Signs by Tessa McWatt</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</guid>
      <description>After thirty years of marriage, producing three now-grown children, Mike and Anna have settled into entrenched domesticity. She is skillful and poised and still beautiful, an instructor of English at the city college. He is a successful graphic artist on the verge of retirement, his awards and ambitions and accomplishments largely behind him. Though the couple’s erotic life has dimmed somewhat, he still considers her ravishing.
But their apparent balance is thrown asunder when Anna breaks the normal silence of their breakfast table with uncontrollable babble about hummingbirds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #19</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 07:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-19/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you organize your blog in terms of what is in your side bar? Do you have categories and defined sections in your side bar?
 At the moment, my side bar is laid out by links to my favourite bloggers, categories, monthly archives, and recent comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Frankenstein by Mary Shelley</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 06:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</guid>
      <description>To many readers, who have perhaps known Frankenstein only at second hand, the original may well come as a surprise. When Mary Shelley began it, she was only eighteen, though she was already Shelley&amp;rsquo;s mistress and Byron&amp;rsquo;s friend. In her preface she explains how she and Shelley spent part of a wet summer with Byron in Switzerland, amusing themselves by reading and writing ghost stories. Her contribution was Frankenstein, a story about a student of natural philosophy who learns the secret of imparting life to a creature constructed from bones he has collected in charnel-houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #18</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-18/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you could have lunch with any living authors and/or book bloggers, who would you choose and why?
 Oh man, the living restriction is a tough one. If language wasn&amp;rsquo;t a barrier, I would definitely have lunch with Haruki Murakami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Nine Island by Jane Alison</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</guid>
      <description>Nine Island is an intimate autobiographical novel, told by J, a woman who lives in a glass tower on one of Miami Beach’s lush Venetian Islands. After decades of disaster with men, she is trying to decide whether to withdraw forever from romantic love. Having just returned to Miami from a monthlong reunion with an old flame, “Sir Gold,” and a visit to her fragile mother, J begins translating Ovid’s magical stories about the transformations caused by Eros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #17</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 07:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-17/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do your bookshelves have books ONLY or do you also have bookish items on the shelves?
 I have books, bookish items, and non-bookish items on my shelves. Actually my shelves are in a pretty sorry state. There is a lot of clutter on them and they&amp;rsquo;re usually my go to place to put things when I have no idea where to put them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #15</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hope-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hope-15/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 When you feature a book in your posts, do you include a book cover?
 I definitely try my best to do so. It seems a little weird to write a blog post about a book without featuring the cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #14</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-14/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you could meet one author, dead or alive, who would it be? Submitted by Kristin @ Lukten av Trykksverte
 I am in love with the Brontë sisters. Their lives intrigue me a great deal and the sense of mystery surrounding them is too much for me to take at times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Birthday of the World and Other Stories by Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</guid>
      <description>For more than four decades, Ursula K. Le Guin has enthralled readers with her imagination, clarity, and moral vision. The recipient of numerous literary prizes, including the National Book Award, the Kafka Award, and five Hugo and five Nebula Awards, this renowned writer has, in each story and novel, created a provocative, ever-evolving universe filled with diverse worlds and rich characters reminiscent of our earthly selves.
Now, in The Birthday of the World, this gifted artist returns to these worlds in eight brilliant short works, including a never-before-published novella, each of which probes the essence of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-13/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you visit every listed blog in the linky list when you are participating in a meme? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 I try to! But I don&amp;rsquo;t always manage to do so. I usually do my blog hopping on the train to/from work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Gamelife by Michael Clune</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</guid>
      <description>You have been awakened.
Floppy disk inserted, computer turned on, a whirring, and then this sentence, followed by a blinking cursor. So begins Suspended, the first computer game to obsess seven-year-old Michael, to worm into his head and change his sense of reality. Thirty years later he will write: &amp;ldquo;Computer games have taught me the things you can&amp;rsquo;t learn from people.&amp;rdquo;
Gamelife is the memoir of a childhood transformed by technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 06:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-12/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you handle negative comments left on your blog? Submitted by Maria @ A Night&amp;rsquo;s Dream of Books
 Thankfully, I haven&amp;rsquo;t encountered this problem before. 🙂 And if I have, obviously I must have handled it well because it didn&amp;rsquo;t make a lasting impression on me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Reivew: Manga Classics – Emma by Stacy King</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-reivew-manga-classics-emma-by-stacy-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 21:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-reivew-manga-classics-emma-by-stacy-king/</guid>
      <description>Just in time for the 200th Anniversary, Manga Classics: Emma brings Jane Austen&amp;rsquo;s classic tale of youthful folly and romantic exuberance to a modern audience with this beautiful, new manga adaptation. The impulsive match-making of Emma Woodhouse delivers both humor and heartache through the gorgeous artwork of manga-ka Po Tse (Manga Classics: Pride and Prejudice). &amp;#8211; Manga Classics editions feature classic stories, faithfully adapted and illustrated in manga style, and available in both hardcover and softcover editions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #11</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-11/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you read a lot of diverse or own voices books? Why or why not? Submitted by Kitty @ Vicarious Bookworm
 Hmm&amp;#8230; I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what this question means so I&amp;rsquo;m going to take a stab at it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Amity by Nasreen Pevjak</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-amity-by-nasreen-pevjak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-review-amity-by-nasreen-pevjak/</guid>
      <description>Amity provides a window to the wreckage caused by wars—the destruction and displacement that leave pain and life-long psychological disorders, here specifically within the contexts of Yugoslavia’s dissolution and Iran’s revolution.
Payvand, an Iranian refugee and activist, still plagued with nightmares, meets a Ragusa, a Yugoslavian refugee whose pockets are loaded with stones as she prepares to walk into the water and end her life, a life that has become intolerable since the loss of those most dear to her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #10</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-10/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How far in advance do you read the books you have scheduled for review?
 I don&amp;rsquo;t read books &amp;ldquo;ahead of time.&amp;rdquo; I just read books with no schedule in mind and review them as I go. I guess this question is geared towards the more veteran book bloggers who recieve copies of books to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #9</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-9/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 When you start reading a novel, do you prefer to be plunged right into the action, or do you prefer a slower, more descriptive introduction to the plot and characters? Submitted by Maria @ [
 
Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #8</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-8/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you feel about books with multiple narrators? Submitted by Eli @ The Book Supplier
 I definitely don&amp;rsquo;t mind them nor do I have a preference towards them. My opinion isn&amp;rsquo;t fresh as I haven&amp;rsquo;t read a book with multiple narrators in a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #7 (02/17-02/23)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-7-0217-0223/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-7-0217-0223/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Can you read and watch TV or listen to the radio at the same time? Submitted by Elizabeth @ [Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews]()
 Nope! Unless we&amp;rsquo;re talking about dry, academic textbooks. I can read the words but nothing will go into my head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it Possible to Read Too Much?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/is-it-possible-to-read-too-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 02:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/is-it-possible-to-read-too-much/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m in a weird place where I&amp;rsquo;m reading a lot but I&amp;rsquo;m unsure if I&amp;rsquo;m feeling depressed because I&amp;rsquo;m reading too much or I&amp;rsquo;m reading too much because I&amp;rsquo;m feeling depressed.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought of books as an escape. That sounds a little too negative but I enjoy experiencing a story that I would probably never experience myself. Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve gravitated to historical fiction because it&amp;rsquo;s just so different and unknown territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #6 (02/10-02/16)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-6-0210-0216/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 20:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-6-0210-0216/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What is your favorite Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day read? Submitted by Kristin @ Lukten av Trykksverte
 Is it okay for me to say that I don&amp;rsquo;t have any&amp;#8230;? I don&amp;rsquo;t really read anything specifically for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. I also don&amp;rsquo;t recall any Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day themed books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #5 (02/03-02/09)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-5-0203-0209/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-5-0203-0209/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Read or Clean? Read or Bake? Read or Make Dinner? What would be your choice? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 There are quite a lot of questions for today!
 Read or Clean? If I play my cards right, both!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #4 (01/27-02/02/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-4-0127-02022017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-4-0127-02022017/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How many books have you statted but just couldn&amp;rsquo;t finish? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 How many? As in, a specific number? Too many to count. Actually, that&amp;rsquo;s not accurate. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know the answer to that question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #3 (01/20-01/26/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-3-0120-01262017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-3-0120-01262017/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What was the one time you thought the movie was better than the book? Submitted by Tomi @ A Bookworm&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Life
 Okay, this is a really tough one. I am sure I have watched plenty of book movies but I haven&amp;rsquo;t always read the book counterpart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Read: Mary and The Wrongs of Woman by Mary Wollstonecraft</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-read-mary-and-the-wrongs-of-woman-by-mary-wollstonecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 03:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-read-mary-and-the-wrongs-of-woman-by-mary-wollstonecraft/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished reading Mary and The Wrongs of Woman by Mary Wollstonecraft. I received this book from a friend of my mothers. I actually received multiple books from my mother&amp;rsquo;s friend, many of them classics such as Villette by Charlotte Bronte, Emma by Jane Austen, Frankenstein by Mary Shelly (who is, by the way, the daughter of Mary Wollstonecraft), etc. I managed to find many books that I enjoyed from her gift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favourite Book of 2016</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-favourite-book-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 02:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-favourite-book-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>This is very long overdue but I was blog hopping and came across The Daily Prophecy ran by Mel. Her latest post was a quick survey of all the books she read in 2016. At the end of her post, she posed the question:
 What is the best book you read in 2016?
 This is a very tough question for me to answer. I read a couple of very good books this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #2 (01/13-01/19/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-2-0113-01192017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop-2-0113-01192017/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Is everyday a reading day for you? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 I&amp;rsquo;m trying to make it a habit of reading everyday. Realistically though, I only really read during the work week. Those days I specifically block out times for myself dedicated for reading: on the way to and from work (since I take public transportation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #1 (01/06-01/12/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-blogger-hop/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Where&amp;rsquo;s your favourite place to read? Submitted by Ronyell @ Rabbit Ears Book Blog
 I will be honest&amp;#8230; I don&amp;rsquo;t think I have a favourite place, as long as I&amp;rsquo;m reading. In terms of places where I usually read is on the bus or when I&amp;rsquo;m eating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Work…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/back-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 03:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/back-to-work/</guid>
      <description>The holidays are officially over, for I went back to work today. It was a bit of a slow day. I got my internship extended, however they basically treated me as a new hire since my contract ended in December. So I&amp;rsquo;m starting from scratch, essentially. I had no laptop, no e-mail, no account to login into any computer connected to the company&amp;rsquo;s network&amp;#8230; Kinda rough.
However, I did manage to do some small tasks that didn&amp;rsquo;t require the use of a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 Reading Resolutions</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/2017-reading-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 05:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/2017-reading-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>This year I told myself I would read at least 25 books. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like a lot but when you consider my reading history the past couple of years, that&amp;rsquo;s a big number.
 2015: 7 books + 3 graphic novels = 10 books 2014: 19 books + 20 graphic novels = 39 books 2013: 40 books + 30 graphic novels = 74 books 2012: 18 books  As you can see, not great numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Library #13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/at-the-library-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 04:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/at-the-library-13/</guid>
      <description>I recently made a trip to the library. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I managed to grab.
Buried in Books: A Reader&amp;rsquo;s Anthology by Julie Rugg
There are quite a lot of books on my to-read list that I don&amp;rsquo;t recall exactly why they&amp;rsquo;re on the list. But I trust myself if a book is on the list. I actually culled off the more obvious ones but the ones that stayed are ones that really interest me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Just Culled My Book Wish List</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-just-culled-my-book-wish-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 02:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-just-culled-my-book-wish-list/</guid>
      <description>On Goodreads, my &amp;ldquo;want-to-own&amp;rdquo; shelf used to have 127 books in it. Now it has five.
Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been bit by the konmari bug. I&amp;rsquo;ve konmari&amp;rsquo;d my wardrobe and my books so far. I&amp;rsquo;m still stuck on the books. I decided it would be fitting to prevent my book collection from growing back to it&amp;rsquo;s ridiculous size and get rid of anything that doesn&amp;rsquo;t spark joy on my book wish list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Library #12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/at-the-library-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 04:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/at-the-library-12/</guid>
      <description>I recently resolved not to take out any library books unless they were on my to read list. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I took out on my latest trip to the library!
Speak by Laurie Halse Anderson
I don&amp;rsquo;t remember why or how this book got onto my to read list but I know that it&amp;rsquo;s been on the list for quite a while. I was glad to see the book sitting on the shelf since I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading: The Secret Diaries of Charlotte Brontë</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/reading-the-secret-diaries-of-charlotte-bronte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/reading-the-secret-diaries-of-charlotte-bronte/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m extremely fond of Charlotte Brontë. Villette is easily my favourite novel and I hold it very close to my heart. A couple week ago I finally got around to reading Jane Eyre and it did not disappoint. The other members of the Brontë family are not to be overlooked either. I enjoyed Emily&amp;rsquo;s Wuthering Heights and all of Anne&amp;rsquo;s books are in my to read list. So when I stumbled upon The Secret Diaries of Charlotte Brontë by Syrie James in the library, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist picking it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Books Every Man Should Read</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/100-books-every-man-should-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 01:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/100-books-every-man-should-read/</guid>
      <description>The Art of Manliness put out this list of books. I am not a man but we&amp;rsquo;ll see how I do with this list. Turns I&amp;rsquo;ve only read 8% of this list. Out of the books I want to read from this list, I&amp;rsquo;ve read 24%. Not any better, but hey. I&amp;rsquo;m really trying to cull the books I want to read though. I will never be able to read everything I want to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comics Aren’t Just Kids Stuff!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 01:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</guid>
      <description>I initially started writing this post in 2012. I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through and cleaning out my drafts and decided this one was worthy of continuing and actually publishing.
Comics are usually written off as being childish or something only nerds can enjoy. But, I&amp;rsquo;m not here to argue whether comics are legitimate literature or not. I&amp;rsquo;m here to point out some of my favourite web comics. I don&amp;rsquo;t know where it started but I got bored one day and eventually ended up on a web comics site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wanting to Write</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/wanting-to-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 02:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/wanting-to-write/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to document my life in a journal. There is something awfully romantic about keeping an account of your day to day life. I just read a book, Fairyland by Alysia Abbott, about a woman who grew up with a single gay father in the &amp;lsquo;80s. She reconstructed both her and her father&amp;rsquo;s life through his journals and their letters to each other. I find it so beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Boyfriend/Crush #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-boyfriend-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 07:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/book-boyfriend-1/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ve been in a really &amp;ldquo;bookish&amp;rdquo; mood lately. Mostly because I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on getting my book database up and running. I was pretty nostalgic over the idea of &amp;ldquo;book blogs&amp;rdquo; and my unsuccessful attempt at a book blog still haunts me today. I decided: I shall blog about books. Book reviews will belong in my book database but anything else will go here. So what exactly is a book blog post that isn&amp;rsquo;t a review?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Another Love Story</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/not-another-love-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 23:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/not-another-love-story/</guid>
      <description>In a way, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to read stories about (romantic) love anymore. Too much emphasis is put on love, whether it be on screen, in print, or just in life in general. Not that I&amp;rsquo;m saying that love isn&amp;rsquo;t important, because it is important. How a character approaches love can speak volumes about their personality. But I just don&amp;rsquo;t want it to be the main plot, or even a sub-plot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be My Dearest, First on Earth</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/be-my-dearest-first-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 18:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/be-my-dearest-first-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>I’m still waiting to fall in love with a book. I want to open it and never want to put it down ever again. I want to find myself in it. I want it to drag out the dark from inside of me and then I want it to tell me that it’s okay and to list all the things that are good about me. I want to read it and never look at life and humanity the same way again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Needs One Topic Blog Posts?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description>I quit Tumblr for Lent. It&amp;rsquo;s only been a couple of days, and I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated so many Tumblr blog posts in my mind and it&amp;rsquo;s kinda driving me crazy. So crazy to the point where a Tumblr and serious blog crossover is inevitable. Tumblr posts are mostly Twitter-like in nature, except ten times the sarcasm, ten times the ironic usage of poor grammar and spelling, and ten times that length.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Resolutions for 2013</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/13-resolutions-for-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 22:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/13-resolutions-for-2013/</guid>
      <description>A new year, a new set of resolutions, probably another year where said resolutions are never fulfilled. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t hurt to at least dream, yeah? Usually most people do these resolution posts on the first day of the year, but I do mine second! No, I was busy with the opening of my new blog, go check it out. On with the post!
1. Post more I hate how this has to be a resolution, but yes, I want to post more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lent is Over</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lent-is-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 06:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lent-is-over/</guid>
      <description>Lent is over. I haven&amp;rsquo;t visited Room 304 or Goodreads in over 40 days. Geez, I have a lot of catching up to do. I did read over those 40 days but definitely not a lot. I&amp;rsquo;ve been swamped with school work and going to sleep at midnight every night doesn&amp;rsquo;t leave much time for reading.
So, I&amp;rsquo;ve resorted to audiobooks. Yeah, yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;lazy way of reading&amp;rdquo; but I&amp;rsquo;ve been craving some sort of world that I can delve into and just absorb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Easter!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-easter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 22:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-easter-2/</guid>
      <description>Lent is finally over. :) My journey with no interent was&amp;hellip; Not very successful but I managed to go by with minimal (emphasis on minimal) internet. I mostly dedicated myself to YouTube on the &amp;ldquo;play all&amp;rdquo; function so that was interesting. It&amp;rsquo;s weird because I had the strongest urge to blog throughout the forty days. Very odd, I thought I would just forget about it but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t the case at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Riddance</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/good-riddance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 21:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/good-riddance/</guid>
      <description>Finally, my final exams are over! I only wrote math and chemistry but I studied my butt off for both of them. Yesterday I had chemistry. It was mad hard but I have to admit that I studied math more than I did for chemistry. I did go to a diploma prep for chemistry which somewhat helped. Math was super easy but I&amp;rsquo;m still worried over it. Super easy could mean that it was really super easy or that I just thought it was easy when in reality, I did everything wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post of the New Year!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/first-post-of-the-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2012 18:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/first-post-of-the-new-year/</guid>
      <description>Most people&amp;rsquo;s first post of the year is on the first, but no, I&amp;rsquo;m unique and I&amp;rsquo;ll have mine six days later. I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy studying and working on Room 304. I&amp;rsquo;m actually being productive. Okay, yesterday and the day before I didn&amp;rsquo;t study at all and now I&amp;rsquo;m freaking out because I have a test on Monday. What do I do about it? I post on my blog. Oh the life of a procrastinator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Reading in 2011</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-reading-in-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 00:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-reading-in-2011/</guid>
      <description>Whoot~ I got 94% on my chem test! However, I wrote a physics test today and I just know that didn&amp;rsquo;t go very well. I have a math test tomorrow so as soon as I finish writing this post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to go study.
Last year around this time, I set a goal for myself: read 100 books before 2011 ends. I&amp;rsquo;m an avid manga reader and I can finish one volume of manga in an hour so a week into the challenge I found that I was already a quarter of the way through the challenge (keep in mind this was during winter break, haha).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates…and Calling All Bookworms!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/updates-and-calling-all-bookworms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 22:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/updates-and-calling-all-bookworms/</guid>
      <description>Updates:
I finally have some content up! 22 new icons and 2 new layouts. Go check it out! (2011 note: these links do not work)
Calling All Bookworms:
Summer is almost over and I have read about 120 books. Whoot! It may seem impossible but it isn&amp;rsquo;t. Very few of the books I&amp;rsquo;ve read stand out in my mind. If you&amp;rsquo;re a bookworm, check out these books!
Snitch by Alison Van Diepen</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>