<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Concerts on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/concerts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Concerts on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/concerts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Concert Bucketlist</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/concert-bucketlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/concert-bucketlist/</guid>
      <description>So this year I went to a bunch of concerts. Two of those concerts (Alexisonfire and Coheed and Cambria) were big wish listers for me and this got me thinking. What other artists do I want to see live?
L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel I know for sure that I want to see L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel live in concert. L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel is a band I got into around junior high. Thanks to the power of the Internet, I know approximately the first time I fell in love with L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Album Reaction: Vaxis - Act I: Unheavenly Creatures by Coheed and Cambria</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/album-reaction-vaxis-act-i-unheavenly-creatures-by-coheed-and-cambria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/album-reaction-vaxis-act-i-unheavenly-creatures-by-coheed-and-cambria/</guid>
      <description>Vaxis - Act I: Unheavenly Creatures    Track Listing
 Prologue The Dark Sentencer Unheavenly Creatures Toys Black Sunday Queen of the Dark True Ugly Love Protocol The Pavillion (A Long Way Back) Night-Time Walkers The Gutter All on Fire It Walks Among Us Old Flames Lucky Stars  DISCLAIMER: This is a reaction blog post which is mostly incoherent rambling and (you guessed it) real-time reactions to the songs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Coheed and Cambria</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-coheed-and-cambria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-coheed-and-cambria/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is not a concert review and really is just me rambling about a band I like
Last Saturday, I went to go see Coheed and Cambria live. Coheed and Cambria is a progressive rock band. Prog rock is a genre that&amp;rsquo;s hard to define without hearing it. The way I see it, prog rock is definitely a more artsy genre. It&amp;rsquo;s usually complex musically and lyrically incorporating several genres such as jazz and pop but still maintaining an aggressive and heavy rock sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Alexisonfire and Billy Talent</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-alexisonfire-and-billy-talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-alexisonfire-and-billy-talent/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is not a concert review and this post contains swearing
One of the things on my 25 before 25 bucket list was to go see a concert. The last concert I went to when I made my bucket list was the Japanese band Lix at an anime convention back in 2012 (but that slipped my mind when I wrote it and I said the last concert I went to was a My Chemical Romance concert).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Chemical Romance in Concert</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-chemical-romance-in-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-chemical-romance-in-concert/</guid>
      <description>Last night, I had my very first concert experience. That&amp;rsquo;s right, I saw My Chemical Romance. It was amazingly awesome. For some reason though, I expected it to be much more&amp;hellip; Epic. A lot of people here on Mibba describe their first concert like it was the best orgasm of life.
But for me, it was kinda awkward and surreal. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe that the band was really in front of me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>