<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Concert Bucketlist</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/concert-bucketlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/concert-bucketlist/</guid>
      <description>So this year I went to a bunch of concerts. Two of those concerts (Alexisonfire and Coheed and Cambria) were big wish listers for me and this got me thinking. What other artists do I want to see live?
L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel I know for sure that I want to see L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel live in concert. L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel is a band I got into around junior high. Thanks to the power of the Internet, I know approximately the first time I fell in love with L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week in Music #3: 2018/10/19 - 2018/10/26</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-3/</guid>
      <description>Last.fm is a website that can keep track of users and their listening habits. I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to music with Last.fm since 2010 and am slightly obsessive over my music stats. These stats are for my listening from the past week.
 My week for October 19, 2018 to October 26, 2018
Top 10 Artists   Top 10 Artists     Coheed and Cambria (-) Even though I&amp;rsquo;ve been making a conscious decision to not listen to as much Coheed and Cambria, I&amp;rsquo;m still listening to them quite a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week in Music #2: 2018/10/12 - 2018/10/19</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-2/</guid>
      <description>Last.fm is a website that can keep track of users and their listening habits. I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to music with Last.fm since 2010 and am slightly obsessive over my music stats. These stats are for my listening from the past week.
 My week for October 12, 2018 to October 19, 2018
Top 10 Artists   Top 10 Artists     Coheed and Cambria (-) I&amp;rsquo;m still riding that Coheed and Cambria hype.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week in Music #1: 2018/10/05 - 2018/10/12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-1/</guid>
      <description>Last.fm is a website that can keep track of users and their listening habits. I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to music with Last.fm since 2010 and am slightly obsessive over my music stats. These stats are for my listening from the past week.
 My week for October 5, 2018 to October 12, 2018
Top 10 Artists   Top 10 Artists    It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that Coheed and Cambria has been pretty much all that I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Album Reaction: Vaxis - Act I: Unheavenly Creatures by Coheed and Cambria</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/album-reaction-vaxis-act-i-unheavenly-creatures-by-coheed-and-cambria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/album-reaction-vaxis-act-i-unheavenly-creatures-by-coheed-and-cambria/</guid>
      <description>Vaxis - Act I: Unheavenly Creatures    Track Listing
 Prologue The Dark Sentencer Unheavenly Creatures Toys Black Sunday Queen of the Dark True Ugly Love Protocol The Pavillion (A Long Way Back) Night-Time Walkers The Gutter All on Fire It Walks Among Us Old Flames Lucky Stars  DISCLAIMER: This is a reaction blog post which is mostly incoherent rambling and (you guessed it) real-time reactions to the songs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Coheed and Cambria</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-coheed-and-cambria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-coheed-and-cambria/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is not a concert review and really is just me rambling about a band I like
Last Saturday, I went to go see Coheed and Cambria live. Coheed and Cambria is a progressive rock band. Prog rock is a genre that&amp;rsquo;s hard to define without hearing it. The way I see it, prog rock is definitely a more artsy genre. It&amp;rsquo;s usually complex musically and lyrically incorporating several genres such as jazz and pop but still maintaining an aggressive and heavy rock sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Alexisonfire and Billy Talent</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-alexisonfire-and-billy-talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-alexisonfire-and-billy-talent/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is not a concert review and this post contains swearing
One of the things on my 25 before 25 bucket list was to go see a concert. The last concert I went to when I made my bucket list was the Japanese band Lix at an anime convention back in 2012 (but that slipped my mind when I wrote it and I said the last concert I went to was a My Chemical Romance concert).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Guitar: Week 1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/learning-the-guitar-week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 01:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/learning-the-guitar-week-1/</guid>
      <description>I have been following Justin Guitar&amp;#8216;s lesson plans for learning the guitar.
This week I went through the first 15 beginner&amp;rsquo;s course lessons, BC-101 to BC-115. I learned the basics of choosing a guitar, posture, etc. In terms of actually playing, I learned the D chord, A chord, and E chord. The first two chords were incredibly &amp;ldquo;easy.&amp;rdquo; The chord that really stumped me was the E chord. I could not press down on the strings hard enough so that it didn&amp;rsquo;t sound muted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Listened To: Electra Heart by Marina and the Diamonds</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-listened-to-electra-heart-by-marina-and-the-diamonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-listened-to-electra-heart-by-marina-and-the-diamonds/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Lyrics relating to suicide is mentioned in this post.
Another disclaimer: I&amp;rsquo;m not good at writing reviews but I do like expressing my opinions. This is in no way a professional review but rather how I personally feel about this album.
I know Marina and the Diamonds&amp;rsquo; album Electra Heart is one of her personally least favourite works but I like it a lot. Many people think Electra Heart represents an alter-ego but it&amp;rsquo;s rather a personality that Marina holds in disdain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bought Some New Music!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/bought-some-new-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 03:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/bought-some-new-music/</guid>
      <description>Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Spotify a lot. I only ever use it when I&amp;rsquo;m at my computer. When I&amp;rsquo;m on the go, I turn to my trusty iPod classic. Since I use the free version of Spotify (now that I have a job, I can&amp;rsquo;t say that I&amp;rsquo;m a broke college student anymore but I can say that I&amp;rsquo;m still cheap), being able to choose what I listen to is a must and Spotify mobile doesn&amp;rsquo;t have that ability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/random-tumblr-posts-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/random-tumblr-posts-1/</guid>
      <description>Ugh I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible.
 I had a dream where I literally just lived out my entire day, down to sitting in lecture being bored and taking notes.
You don’t even know how disappointed I am when I woke up knowing that I had to do it all over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Approaching this Blog &amp; R.I.P hide</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/on-approaching-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 16:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/on-approaching-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Suicide content warning.
My philosophy with this blog has always been to approach in a very casual and informal way. I was inspired by a blog to do so, but I don&amp;rsquo;t quite remember what site it was exactly (I&amp;rsquo;m tempted to say it was 6birds, but I&amp;rsquo;m not entirely sure). I try to have this mindset whenever I need to write a blog post. Even so, I don&amp;rsquo;t entirely feel free in writing whatever I want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Started to Play TCGs Again</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-started-to-play-tcgs-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 05:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-started-to-play-tcgs-again/</guid>
      <description>Since I gave up Tumblr for Lent, I realized how much free time I had on my hands without Tumblr. I decided, why not get back into TCGs? And so I did.
TCG stands for &amp;ldquo;Trading Card Game.&amp;rdquo; There are TCGs around the Internet that you can join as long as you yourself have a bit of space on the Internet. The goal of the game is basically to collect all the cards that are available in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musical Finds</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/musical-finds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 06:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/musical-finds/</guid>
      <description>Man, lately I&amp;rsquo;ve just been scouring the Internet (okay, YouTube) for new music. I&amp;rsquo;m so hungry for new music! Anyway, here are my findings.
Buhar Jerreau
These guys are at the top of my list at the moment. They&amp;rsquo;re a hip-hop/rap group of three guys from Kazakhstan. According to translations of their lyrics, I find them to be extremely talented at song writing. I really am in love with the beats of their songs (I don&amp;rsquo;t know rap lingo&amp;hellip;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tagalog and Translated English Lyrics: “Panginoon” by Yeng Constantino</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/tagalog-and-translated-english-lyrics-panginoon-by-yeng-constantino/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 00:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/tagalog-and-translated-english-lyrics-panginoon-by-yeng-constantino/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: I&amp;rsquo;m not fluent in Tagalog but I am Filipino. English is my first language. This translation is improvised in some parts and relied heavily on Google Translate and my (very limited) existing knowledge of the language.
I love Yeng Constantino (Filipino singer). I put this song at the very front of my Filofax to remind me of two things: to be proud of being Filipino and to keep my mind focused on God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But Seriously Though. AJ is perfect.</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/but-seriously-though-aj-is-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 19:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/but-seriously-though-aj-is-perfect/</guid>
      <description>AJ reminds me of Kemal. As much as I&amp;rsquo;d hate to say it, that&amp;rsquo;s the number one reason why I find AJ so attractive. He&amp;rsquo;s like the Korean version of Kemal. Also, I&amp;rsquo;d rather fangirl over AJ than be madly crushing on a guy who probably thinks I&amp;rsquo;m an idiot and who I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in almost a year.
However, I saw Kemal on campus a while ago and I realized how much they don&amp;rsquo;t really look like each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But Seriously Though. U-KISS</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/but-seriously-though-u-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 03:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/but-seriously-though-u-kiss/</guid>
      <description>Okay I admittedly watch too many videos on YouTube when I should be doing school things but I really like looking for videos of U-KISS. I find it to be so embarrassing that I am a fan. I have to watch metal1 music videos afterwards to regain my manliness get rid of that sickly sweet aftertaste in my mouth that I get when I look, hear, or even think about at U-KISS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving L’Arc~en~Ciel</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/loving-larcenciel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/loving-larcenciel/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret to many people that L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel is my favourite band. No, not one of my favourite bands, but my favourite band. Previously, my favourite band had been Green Day, from about grade four to junior high school. They were a great band for me at the time but they didn&amp;rsquo;t have a timeless feel to them. After listening to L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel, I quickly dumped them.
When I was in junior high I even wrote an essay about how L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel had impacted my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Afterman: Ascension (A Reaction)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/the-afterman-ascension-a-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 02:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/the-afterman-ascension-a-reaction/</guid>
      <description>Track Listing
 The Hollow Key Entity Extraction I: Domino The Destitute The Afterman Mothers of Men Goodnight, Fair Lady Key Entity Extraction II: Holly Wood The Cracked Key Entity Extraction III: Vic The Butcher Key Entity Extraction IV: Evagaria The Faithful Subtraction  WARNING: Reaction blog posts are probably not blog posts at all but rather, a mass wall of incoherent garble of text. This probably belongs on something like Tumblr but it was too long and you know Tumblr kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Songs I’ve Been Playing on Repeat</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/three-songs-ive-been-playing-on-repeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/three-songs-ive-been-playing-on-repeat/</guid>
      <description>These past two months or so have been great for new music. G-Dragon&amp;rsquo;s comeback and news of Coheed and Cambria&amp;rsquo;s new album. So many good things are happening! Lately, there has been three songs that I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing over and over again.

A gif made by vitadolce-moderato.   The first one worth mentioning is G-Dragon&amp;rsquo;s new ballad, That XX. For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, G-Dragon is a South Korean artist part of the boy group BIG BANG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Discoveries #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/youtube-discoveries-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 21:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/youtube-discoveries-1/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Sunadokei by L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel
Fave song atm: Somebody to Love by CLUBSODA
Fave musician(s) atm: Uhh&amp;hellip; I actually have no idea
 Just so you all know, I waded through 7000+ forums posts to find all the YouTube links I wanted to post here. Then I realized I could have used the search function. OTL Anyway, on to the post. Warning, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot here. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you&amp;rsquo;d want to read it all but yeah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIR EN GREY WHY</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/dir-en-grey-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 10:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/dir-en-grey-why/</guid>
      <description>A couple days ago, the Diru fandom on Tumblr was freaking out. I checked the DIR EN GREY tag just to be in the loop. Lo and behold, I see screenshots of this. I immediately went to the official website and there it was. The background was slowly fading in and out with different pictures and the timer slowly ticked away.
First, I freaked out. I went on Twitter, saw @DEG_CANADA&amp;rsquo;s tweet about the countdown and key smashed like there was no tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last.FM Stats</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/last-fm-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 19:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/last-fm-stats/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Hit in the USA by Beat Crusaders
Fave song atm: Somebody to Love by CLUBSODA
Fave musician(s) atm: I actually have no idea
 My Last.FM stats as of July 2012. I use Last.FM a lot, without my knowledge basically. Whenever I open up iTunes, Last.FM secretly scrobbles my music as I listen. Also, whenever I plug my iPod in, I get a dialog box that asks if I want to scrobble everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roentgen: A Beautiful &amp; Lost Era</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/roentgen-a-beautiful-lost-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 11:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/roentgen-a-beautiful-lost-era/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: The Sharpest Lives by MCR
Fave song atm: Scream by 2NE1
Fave musician(s) atm: 2NE1 &amp;amp; BIGBANG
 Okay, I love Hyde. I always have. There&amp;rsquo;s something about him that I just can&amp;rsquo;t ignore. However, I just wish I could bring back the Roentgen era. Variety is good and experimenting is all well and nice but&amp;hellip; Roentgen. I miss you.
VAMPS was an iffy time for me. I was fully into L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel and obsessing over everything Laruku related.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Current ATM Playlist</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-current-atm-playlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 09:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-current-atm-playlist/</guid>
      <description>I usually create an &amp;ldquo;ATM&amp;rdquo; playlist that features all the songs I want to listen to on repeat. Here they are as of June 15, 2012.
 Koishikute (cover) by Aokicchi
Koishikuteeeee. This girl has a pretty voice.
 Bad Boy by BIGBANG
I really like it when GD sings okay.
 Last Farewell by BIGBANG
I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be without you girl~ Found by GD making mistakes lol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MONSTER by BIGBANG</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/monster-by-bigbang/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 05:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/monster-by-bigbang/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: MONSTER by BIGBANG
Fave song atm: Scream by 2NE1
Fave musician(s) atm: 2NE1 &amp;amp; BIGBANG
 What a coincidence, the song just came up on my iPod. Anyway, a couple days ago I finally decided that I would watch BIGBANG&amp;rsquo;s new music video, MONSTER. I must admit, lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to more and more K-pop these days. I&amp;rsquo;m just craving more new DIR EN GREY, however they are not inhuman and can&amp;rsquo;t churn out albums out of their asses every day of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chaos</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/chaos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 03:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/chaos/</guid>
      <description>This morning was a great morning! Most band practices aren&amp;rsquo;t that exciting but this one was pretty good. We played the opener and the second song of the show. In marching band, the members run around a football field making pretty shapes while playing their instruments. Those 11 minutes of organized chaos is what we call a show. At my highschool we have a marching band. I&amp;rsquo;m in band but I don&amp;rsquo;t march because of money and time issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You, You, Only You</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/you-you-only-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 06:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/you-you-only-you/</guid>
      <description>I never finished the DIR EN GREY meme. I’ll finish it sooner or later. I haven’t posted in a while either. Oh no! Well, better late than never.
I rediscovered this podcast I downloaded when I just started listening to Japanese and Korean music. All Rock and No Talk by xxthrowdownxx I think it was. So yeah, I was listening to volume 12 and came across a pleasant gem.
Stand By Me by The Brilliant Green.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIR EN GREY Challenge: Day 17</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 23:22:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-17/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Hoshizora by L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel
Fave song atm: Blame it On the Girls by Mika
Fave musician(s) atm: SCREW
 Favourite interview.
I don&amp;rsquo;t read interviews except for the ones that happen to appear on my Tumblr dashboard. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a couple interviews on YouTube but most of them were outdated or boring.
The one I remember the most though is Toshiya talking about what Diru means to him. I can&amp;rsquo;t recall the details but it was clearly evident that he loves the band dearly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIR EN GREY Challenge: Day 16</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 21:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-16/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Thriller by Michael Jackson
Fave song atm: Ophelia by L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel
Fave musician(s) atm: Michael Jackson
 Your favourite Dir en grey lyric and translation.
Oh God. Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me this. Brb I&amp;rsquo;ll be hunting through lyric sites forever. Anyway, immediately, 我、闇とて。。。 came in my head. Here is the translation:
_It&amp;rsquo;s easy to stop breathing&amp;hellip;but I just want to feel you just a little more
Will you allow me to live?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIR EN GREY Challenge: Day 15</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 00:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-15/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: CLEVER SLEAZOID by DIR EN GREY
Fave song atm: Au Revoir by MALICE MIZER
Fave musician(s) atm: MALICE MIZER
 Your first Dir en grey PV.
JEALOUS. I was so hooked on that PV. All the members were just eerily beautiful (especially Toshiya, I loved his costume) and the beginning sounded like one of the Filipino songs my mom sang on karaoke for parties. Crappy quality was crappy though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIR EN GREY Challenge: Day 14</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 23:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-14/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Existence by L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel
Fave song atm: Honey Vanity by Közi
Fave musician(s) atm: Közi
 Your first Dir en grey song.
The Pledge (Acoustic Version). The first day should have made it clear. Although I sound mad, I&amp;rsquo;m really not. A lot of these questions are overlapping. It&amp;rsquo;s just annoying to have to repeat myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIR EN GREY Challenge: Day 13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 18:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/dir-en-grey-challenge-day-13/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: 我、闇とて。。。 by DIR EN GREY
Fave song atm: Eyes on Me by Faye Wong
Fave musician(s) atm: Yeng Constantino
 Your favourite Dir en grey era.
Hrmm. I&amp;rsquo;d say the current era and the MOAB and UROBOROS era. This era seems very natural to me and the two previous eras just naturally lead up to it. It was inevitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Were Born Ready!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/they-were-born-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 22:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/they-were-born-ready/</guid>
      <description>Over a week ago I went to the Stampede grounds to see Showbands Live. Showbands Live is an annual marching band competition. Every year there are the regulars (The Stetsons Calgary Showband, The Red Deer Royals, and Bishop Grandin Marching Ghosts). Last year I was part of the Ghosts and I wanted to support them and see them compete. This year there were a lot of American bands that were participating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Canada Day!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-canada-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 16:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-canada-day/</guid>
      <description>Like the title says, happy Canada day! Today Prince William and Kate are in Canada as we speak celebrating with us. My family doesn&amp;rsquo;t really do anything special for Canada day except for wearing red all day. Last year I spent Canada day in the States actually because of marching band. We were practicing on a football field and on the large scaffolding where the band directors stood, we hung a huge Canadian flag on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Chemical Romance in Concert</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-chemical-romance-in-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-chemical-romance-in-concert/</guid>
      <description>Last night, I had my very first concert experience. That&amp;rsquo;s right, I saw My Chemical Romance. It was amazingly awesome. For some reason though, I expected it to be much more&amp;hellip; Epic. A lot of people here on Mibba describe their first concert like it was the best orgasm of life.
But for me, it was kinda awkward and surreal. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe that the band was really in front of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed Racer</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/speed-racer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 06:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/speed-racer/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Tada, Hitotsu no Koi &amp;#8211; Koizora OST
So I&amp;rsquo;ve been obssessed with Koizora lately. The movie, drama, manga, novel, AND the soundtrack. Oh jeez. No matter what form of media it&amp;rsquo;s in, it never ceases to make bawl my eyes out. Plus, in the drama, Seto Koji is pretty hot. *cough*
Today was pretty good. I went to the mall and caused some shenanigans. I bought a visa gift card and I&amp;rsquo;m going to use it to buy iPod toch apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovelie</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lovelie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 18:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lovelie/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday I got to see Alice in Wonderland! I absolutely loved it. Tim Burton makes amazing movies. Edward Scissorhands, Corpse Bride, The Nightmare Before Christmas&amp;hellip; Holy cheese he is a genious! And Helena Carter is such a great actress. She did the Red Queen so well! Johnny Depp, pssh. He was a good Hatter though.
After the movie, we went to Zellers! There was some toys on display and Cloud touched one of them and then it started to sing and dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretty Men</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-like-men-who-look-like-girls-o_o/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 05:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-like-men-who-look-like-girls-o_o/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Fuyu Tokyo &amp;#8211; Lareine
Alright, so I was writing this, finished, about to press add news, and then Safari closed on me. FML.
Anyway, on to the blog post. I want to be like a doll. Sit there and look cute and pretty while wearing pretty dresses. The pretty Victorian porcelain dolls, not the disproportionate Barbie dolls. No, this isn&amp;rsquo;t weird at all. Me and Cloud were talking about Mana-sama from Malice Mizer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because I met you in a dream, that dream will cruelly disappear</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/because-i-met-you-in-a-dream-that-dream-will-cruelly-disappear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 19:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/because-i-met-you-in-a-dream-that-dream-will-cruelly-disappear/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s this one VK (visual kei) band, Versailles. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard of them, but haven&amp;rsquo;t necessarily listened to them. I found this one PV, Serenade &amp;#8211; Versailles, which is simply amazing.
Jasmine You passed away a couple of months ago. Even though I don&amp;rsquo;t listen to Versailles, I was deeply troubled by this news. Jasmine is so beautiful and an amazing bassist. It struck me for the second time that yes, even famous people die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Day~!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/green-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/green-day/</guid>
      <description>Well I should be fixing up my speech. Haha. But I could just wing it. I could talk about Green Day with my eyes closed. Personally, I rather it was that way. I fail at speeches so I need the piece of paper in front of me to read off from!
So my homework of today consists of downloading Green Day songs, looking up lyrics, song meanings, watching interviews, music videos, and crazy random shit that they always seem to be doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Michael Jackson</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/more-michael-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 21:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/more-michael-jackson/</guid>
      <description>Alright, I uploaded 1 story and 2 poems. Good that I got SOME content on. Haha. I&amp;rsquo;m working on a new fanfic and obviously my Michael Jackson tribute set.
My progress:
-Icons 65&amp;frasl;100
-Layouts 5&amp;frasl;10
-Headers 5&amp;frasl;10
Those are just the things I already started. Oh wow. I am SO fast. Good thing I have a year to do this.
Anyway. The Michael Jackson memorial was so sad. I bawled. Especially during when Paris, Marlon, and Brook Shields said their little speeches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/michael-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 21:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/michael-jackson/</guid>
      <description>Okay, so I&amp;rsquo;m going to rant about Michael Jackson. Here&amp;rsquo;s a journal entry I made a couple days ago at my DeviantArt account.
&amp;ldquo;I have been mourning for days now. No joke. Downloading MJ songs, watching tributes, joining Facebook fan pages, watching lives, reading articles, and whatever.
He&amp;rsquo;s such a beautiful man even with the white make up and the plastic surgery. You see him smile, and you think &amp;ldquo;Awww.&amp;rdquo; Haha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Parties, Food, School, and . . . Michael Jackson!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lake-parties-food-school-and-michael-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 02:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lake-parties-food-school-and-michael-jackson/</guid>
      <description>Some updates&amp;hellip; Alright, I&amp;rsquo;ve got the basic Nav links up. Sadly, I forgot the Affies and Linkage&amp;hellip; links. TT_TT I&amp;rsquo;ll fix it later (read the last paragraph). I got my Twitter up, my stats counter, and a new C-BOX! What am I missing? Oh right, actual content! Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, I&amp;rsquo;m working on it&amp;hellip;
Now back to real life&amp;hellip; Yesterday I went to a party for the end of the year. Okay, it was more like a BBQ but it still counts, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Again!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/absolute-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 04:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/absolute-again/</guid>
      <description>My skool is posted on a band&amp;rsquo;s website! That&amp;rsquo;s never happened before. In the picture, the first school listed is my school. It was career day today and the day ended with the Absolute Presentation. I remember the presentation form last year. Last year was better but mainly because the band was better (Colin Lingren is amazing). But apparently the band that came to our school was better in terms of success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Phase?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/a-phase/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 03:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/a-phase/</guid>
      <description>I think I&amp;rsquo;m going through a Japanese band phase. I think it really started with the theme songs for Gundam Seed Destiny, then Naruto, then Inu Yasha, then Bleach, and then Full Metal Alchemist. FMA mostly. If it wasnt for FMA I would have NEVER heard of L&amp;rsquo;Arc~En~Ciel.
L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel is my number one fave Japanese band and my number one fave song by them is Link (which is the opening theme song for the FMA the Movie: The Conqueror of Shamballa).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Love This Band</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-love-this-band/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-love-this-band/</guid>
      <description>L&amp;rsquo;Arc En Ciel
they are so cool
they may be Japanese but they are stll awesome
they&amp;rsquo;ve been around as longs as Green Day has (but Green Day&amp;rsquo;s older)
they&amp;rsquo;re all 39 but they look like they&amp;rsquo;re 20
i cant stop listeing to them, and my brother thinks its annoying i only know some songs by them&amp;hellip;but my favourite is Link
Link (Live)
this is taken from an anime festival in 2005, and they&amp;rsquo;re preforming Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity Dreams</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/celebrity-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 08:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/celebrity-dreams/</guid>
      <description>I had a dream, that Gerard Way and Amy Lee were at my church and they fighting over who was a better singer. It was so weird. Then suddenly, Gerard got naked. One second he had clothes, the next he didn&amp;rsquo;t. He just magically got naked and strangely, Amy wasn&amp;rsquo;t bothered with it.
I also had a dream that Billie Joe Armstrong murdered someone and got into jail and went all crazy up in the mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Chemical Romance on Much on Demand</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-chemical-romance-on-much-on-demand/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-chemical-romance-on-much-on-demand/</guid>
      <description>Note: This post has been edited from its original for spelling, grammar, and less cringe. Why did I use ellipses so much back then?
I&amp;rsquo;m excited, even though I&amp;rsquo;m nowhere near Toronto. Just on the other coast&amp;hellip; The last time they were on Much on Demand (MOD) was on th 11th of May&amp;hellip; It was a Friday&amp;hellip;.. *sigh* I&amp;rsquo;m very excited.. And Kelly Clarkson was on MOD a few moments ago&amp;hellip; She&amp;rsquo;s funny&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teenagers</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/teenagers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 16:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/teenagers/</guid>
      <description>Note: This post has been edited from its original for spelling, grammar, and less cringe.
Much Music just premiered the music video Teenagers by My Chemical Romance like, a minute ago&amp;hellip; It was good video&amp;hellip; Good song, but where&amp;rsquo;s the usual &amp;ldquo;theatrical&amp;rdquo; video??? Whatever, it was still good as always&amp;hellip; Teenagers is my brother&amp;rsquo;s favourite song because, in his words, &amp;ldquo;teenagers really do scare me&amp;hellip; Like you.&amp;rdquo; And then I&amp;rsquo;m like &amp;ldquo;Uh&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not a teenager&amp;hellip; Yet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>