<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiration from Fictional Worlds</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/inspiration-from-fictional-worlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/inspiration-from-fictional-worlds/</guid>
      <description>My last semester was extremely busy. So busy that I spent my commute on the train sleeping everyday instead of my usual reading. I&amp;rsquo;ll admit, most of my reading is done when I&amp;rsquo;m on the train. So other than the occasional manga or cookbook, I hardly read the last couple months of last year. Which is devastating.
This year (like every year), I resolved to read more. I started out the year reading two non-fictional books about personal finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Another Love Story</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/not-another-love-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 23:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/not-another-love-story/</guid>
      <description>In a way, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to read stories about (romantic) love anymore. Too much emphasis is put on love, whether it be on screen, in print, or just in life in general. Not that I&amp;rsquo;m saying that love isn&amp;rsquo;t important, because it is important. How a character approaches love can speak volumes about their personality. But I just don&amp;rsquo;t want it to be the main plot, or even a sub-plot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversations Over Text Messages</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/conversations-over-text-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/conversations-over-text-messages/</guid>
      <description>Long weird sappy feelings. So much sap and cheese and this sounded better in my head because I kinda read it in a certain way. Man, I just don’t know. Also, for the love of gulay, the end of a line does not mean &amp;ldquo;pause.&amp;rdquo; Punctuation means &amp;ldquo;pause.&amp;rdquo; Yes, you’re supposed to run out of breath (I&amp;rsquo;m kinda slightly asthmatic though, so).
i’m sorry,
but i won’t ever text you again</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scarf</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/the-scarf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 23:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/the-scarf/</guid>
      <description>The sun cleared up his eyes and I was instantly lost.
Even when his head turned towards mine
I could not and would not tear mine away from his.
That colour!
I had never experienced it before.
Warm and clear.
I could see forever in his eyes.
I could feel his disappointment
when he looked into mine: an endless dirt pit.
But he smiled at me then, a sweet crooked grin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prompt #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/prompt-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 04:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/prompt-1/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what to write about in my blog right now. At first I was like &amp;ldquo;post everyday!&amp;rdquo; but when I got to it, I drew a blank. Not to mention, the 500 words requirement overwhelms me. What can I write about for 500 words??That&amp;rsquo;s why I already missed more than four days of posting. A &amp;ldquo;blog post idea&amp;rdquo; list would be very hand right now. I gotta start writing down said ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Not Good at Writing</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/im-not-good-at-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 06:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/im-not-good-at-writing/</guid>
      <description>Moments like these, I question my desire to go to graduate school. I have a paper to write by Friday. I was told to basically start over and I&amp;rsquo;m stuck. It&amp;rsquo;s on a novel and we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to pull out symbols for it and I&amp;rsquo;m just drawing a blank. My prof started connecting some of them and I tried to follow suit but they&amp;rsquo;re too far fetched. I&amp;rsquo;m really frustrated and I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>