<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>High School on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/high-school/</link>
    <description>Recent content in High School on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 16:59:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/high-school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Last Day of Freedom</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-last-day-of-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 16:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-last-day-of-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow I start university. Thank goodness for Labour day. I&amp;rsquo;ve never really understood what Labour day is. All I know is that it delays school by one more day and that&amp;rsquo;s all I need to know to be thankful for it. To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m not at all that excited to be honest. Technically, classes don&amp;rsquo;t start until next week so that&amp;rsquo;s delayed even further.
This week is all orientation. Basically, just having fun and getting to know the campus and mingling with other potential classmates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Easter!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-easter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 22:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-easter-2/</guid>
      <description>Lent is finally over. :) My journey with no interent was&amp;hellip; Not very successful but I managed to go by with minimal (emphasis on minimal) internet. I mostly dedicated myself to YouTube on the &amp;ldquo;play all&amp;rdquo; function so that was interesting. It&amp;rsquo;s weird because I had the strongest urge to blog throughout the forty days. Very odd, I thought I would just forget about it but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t the case at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Sucks the Life Out of You</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/it-sucks-the-life-out-of-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 01:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/it-sucks-the-life-out-of-you/</guid>
      <description>Today, my high school hosted a blood donation centre. I wanted to donate blood because, well, it&amp;rsquo;s for a good cause, right? I drank tons of water the day of and the day before so in my morning classes I was going to the washroom a whole lot. So, I went to donate blood during lunch time. I filled out a form, got a drop of blood tested for my iron level, answered some questions (sexual history, travelling, and any other things that could influence whether or not my blood is good to donate or not).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beginning of the End</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/the-beginning-of-the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 23:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/the-beginning-of-the-end/</guid>
      <description>January was a mostly boring month. Filled with studying, tears, gaming, eating, sleeping, more tears, and a bit more studying. The only exciting day was yesterday, which was the first day of the semester. The last semester of high school. Oh, the end is near.
One of my the girls in my section told me that there was band practice the morning of the first day of semester. I went to school at seven and&amp;hellip; No band practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Riddance</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/good-riddance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 21:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/good-riddance/</guid>
      <description>Finally, my final exams are over! I only wrote math and chemistry but I studied my butt off for both of them. Yesterday I had chemistry. It was mad hard but I have to admit that I studied math more than I did for chemistry. I did go to a diploma prep for chemistry which somewhat helped. Math was super easy but I&amp;rsquo;m still worried over it. Super easy could mean that it was really super easy or that I just thought it was easy when in reality, I did everything wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/merry-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 21:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/merry-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was my last day of school. It was pretty pointless as it was a half day and each class was half an hour long. We also had band practice in the morning! Thankfully it was cut short because the band teachers had to go carol with the other teachers at the front of the school. They actually sounded pretty good. I was expecting horrible off key belting and such but no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Reading in 2011</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-reading-in-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 00:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-reading-in-2011/</guid>
      <description>Whoot~ I got 94% on my chem test! However, I wrote a physics test today and I just know that didn&amp;rsquo;t go very well. I have a math test tomorrow so as soon as I finish writing this post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to go study.
Last year around this time, I set a goal for myself: read 100 books before 2011 ends. I&amp;rsquo;m an avid manga reader and I can finish one volume of manga in an hour so a week into the challenge I found that I was already a quarter of the way through the challenge (keep in mind this was during winter break, haha).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chaos</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/chaos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 03:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/chaos/</guid>
      <description>This morning was a great morning! Most band practices aren&amp;rsquo;t that exciting but this one was pretty good. We played the opener and the second song of the show. In marching band, the members run around a football field making pretty shapes while playing their instruments. Those 11 minutes of organized chaos is what we call a show. At my highschool we have a marching band. I&amp;rsquo;m in band but I don&amp;rsquo;t march because of money and time issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s December…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/its-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 02:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/its-december/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it is finally December!
The first day of December was okay. In math I got my last unit test back. 91%! But then I got my quiz back. 64%! My marks have such variety, don&amp;rsquo;t they? I felt like my math teacher was giving me disappointed looks all through class because I did so bad on this quiz. This unit we&amp;rsquo;re doing, permutations and combinations, is really weird for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Smells Like Highschool</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/it-smells-like-highschool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 15:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/it-smells-like-highschool/</guid>
      <description>Last week we got our yearbooks from last year. I dislike the fact that they give it out in the new school year since not all of those who graduated can come back and sign the yearbooks of those who were left behind. But I guess it takes a while to get all of the pictures, design each of the pages, send it to the company, physically make it, and then ship it back to us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Weekend!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/long-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 06:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/long-weekend/</guid>
      <description>I understand that it is almost Thanksgiving in the States so others have long weekends as well. But our reasons for the long weekend are because of parent teacher interviews tomorrow and Rememberance day the after.
Speaking of Rememberance day, today was the Rememberance celebration at my school. Since I go to a Catholic school, the celebration is held at the church behind the school. It&amp;rsquo;s a short walk across the field and into the parking lot but it was chilly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belated Happy Thanksgiving!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/belated-happy-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 05:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/belated-happy-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was Thanksgiving in Canada land. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to post because of our super long but extremely satisfying dinner. Turkey, ham, and pasta for all! Not to mention that there was no school yesterday.
I said I was going to create passwords and give them out but that never really happened. It will happen sometime this week when I get around to it.
Today was rather interesting. Everyone was talking about post post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Remember the 21st night of September?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-september/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 23:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-september/</guid>
      <description>I love the song September by Earth Wind and Fire, so I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t help myself. On the 21st I sang the song throughout the whole day. I was tempted to go and play the song on my flute because I learned it, but I forgot where the music for the song went. Oh well. So, do you guys remember what happened on the 21st night of September?
Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;ve been contemplating this for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile for the Camera!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/smile-for-the-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 03:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/smile-for-the-camera/</guid>
      <description>So I have vowed to write at least something everyday for this school year to document my final year in high school. Some of it will be published, some not. I also know most people don&amp;rsquo;t like &amp;ldquo;this is what I did this whole entire day&amp;rdquo; kind of posts but it is my blog, and well, I&amp;rsquo;ll blog whatever I want. :]
To start things off, today was rather ordinary. I woke up painfully early at six in the morning (well, it&amp;rsquo;s early if you&amp;rsquo;ve been sleeping in until noon for two months) because I heard my mom cooking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Were Born Ready!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/they-were-born-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 22:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/they-were-born-ready/</guid>
      <description>Over a week ago I went to the Stampede grounds to see Showbands Live. Showbands Live is an annual marching band competition. Every year there are the regulars (The Stetsons Calgary Showband, The Red Deer Royals, and Bishop Grandin Marching Ghosts). Last year I was part of the Ghosts and I wanted to support them and see them compete. This year there were a lot of American bands that were participating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1 of Summer School</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/day-1-of-summer-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 01:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/day-1-of-summer-school/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I started summer school. I said before that I had to take Religion 35 because it&amp;rsquo;s required to graduate and I have no room in my schedule for it next year. So, yesterday I woke up at 6:30 AM sharp, ate my breakfast, changed, and dashed out the door. Usually the first day of school isn&amp;rsquo;t intimidating but for some reason, the first day of summer school was extremely nerve wrecking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Easter!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 00:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-easter/</guid>
      <description>I said it! Even though it was yesterday, happy Easter! I&amp;rsquo;m a Christian, so yes, Jesus Christ has risen from the dead! ^o^
Ah, so many things have happened since my last blog post. I don&amp;rsquo;t even remember half of it, haha.
On the 24th of March, instead of having a band practice, we had a concert! We got to wear the tuxedos! I always feel like a man in uniform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Just a Loner</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/im-just-a-l-o-n-e-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 20:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/im-just-a-l-o-n-e-r/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: You Rock My World &amp;#8211; Michael Jackson
Mood: Accomplished, bored.
Fanlisting for Outsider&amp;rsquo;s Loner is now open! Go check it out, and if you are a fan of the song, please join! Click here!
Ahh, I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing too much gaming lately. Even though I&amp;rsquo;m only about 20 hours in on Dissidia: Final Fantasy, I love it! Like Cloud always says, I never want the game to end! It takes a long time to finish the game anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnomnom</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-think-everybody-should-join-band/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 04:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-think-everybody-should-join-band/</guid>
      <description>Today was pretty fun!! I found out that I lost 13 pounds, that I fail at trying to bench press, and that I can jump! And a lot of band things happened today.
So today was Marina&amp;rsquo;s (colour guard and clarinet) 16th birthday! And Andrew Lumapas came!! He&amp;rsquo;s for sure my hero. His YouTube vids are EPICALLY AMAZING. So amazing that I have to use all caps. Go check out his YouTube account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maayong Pasko!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/maayong-pasko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 18:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/maayong-pasko/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas, guys!! I hope all of you have an amazing Christmas! I&amp;rsquo;m getting an iPod Touch FTW! I&amp;rsquo;m excited. Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;m on my brother&amp;rsquo;s new PSP! It&amp;rsquo;s kinda hard to type on this thing&amp;hellip; &amp;gt;_&amp;lt; Soooo my birthday is coming up! I am also excited for that! sorry for the short post&amp;hellip; Everyone have a good day! =]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything At Once</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/give-me-everything-at-once/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 21:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/give-me-everything-at-once/</guid>
      <description>We have a new affiliate, Sute/Himitsu-Sasshi. I adore her website! I&amp;rsquo;m so glad she is an affiliate ^^
And I&amp;rsquo;m making a new layout! Whoot! It features BGHS Marching Band. Oh of course. Haha. It&amp;rsquo;s so colourful, I love it! I&amp;rsquo;m also putting band quotes in the background. Yay!
What else, what else? I have Hallelujah in my head. We have to learn a whole new song by next week for soe District anniversay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grey Cup!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/grey-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/grey-cup/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s watching the Grey Cup next week?
To those who don&amp;rsquo;t know.
Grey Cup: The championship of the CLF (Canadian Football League). The Grey Cup game is the centre of a larger week of festivities put on by the host cities, including concerts, gala events, and autograph sessions. Also an important part of the event in the halftime show which in recent years has included major Canadian and international musical acts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>