<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Religion on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/religion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Religion on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 03:27:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Needs One Topic Blog Posts?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description>I quit Tumblr for Lent. It&amp;rsquo;s only been a couple of days, and I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated so many Tumblr blog posts in my mind and it&amp;rsquo;s kinda driving me crazy. So crazy to the point where a Tumblr and serious blog crossover is inevitable. Tumblr posts are mostly Twitter-like in nature, except ten times the sarcasm, ten times the ironic usage of poor grammar and spelling, and ten times that length.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Charter for Compassion (TL;DR Everyone Needs to Get Along)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/the-charter-for-compassion-tldr-everyone-needs-to-get-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 05:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/the-charter-for-compassion-tldr-everyone-needs-to-get-along/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a Catholic, I&amp;rsquo;m always working towards understanding my faith, living my faith, properly representing my faith, and lately: being in harmony with those who do not share my faith. A couple of years ago, I was an ignorant little brat, believing myself better than others who didn&amp;rsquo;t actually identify as Catholic despite going to a Catholic school. That mentality quickly faded away once high school began but that didn&amp;rsquo;t mean that I became &amp;ldquo;any less Catholic.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried my best to keep a delicate balance between my more secular values and my, well, not so secular values. It&amp;rsquo;s hard. I still try to do this today. More often than not, my secular values seem to dominate over everything else but I still have this longing to grow in my faith and fully live it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier on this semester, the campus bookstore was having a hallway sale. It was my break time, I had nothing better to do and the prices seemed cheap enough, so I went ahead and browsed for around half an hour. There were a couple of books that intrigued me but there was one book that kept me coming back to it. &amp;ldquo;Through the Narrow Gate: Life In and Out of the Convent&amp;rdquo; by Karen Armstrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>