<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 01:48:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LFTP Fatal Error: Certificate verification</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lftp-fatal-error-certificate-verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 01:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lftp-fatal-error-certificate-verification/</guid>
      <description>The error: ~$ git-ftp pull&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; ~$ cd: Fatal error: Certificate verification: certificate common name doesn&amp;rsquo;t match requested host name ‘ftp.mazohyst.org’&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; ~$ mirror: Fatal error: Certificate verification: certificate common name doesn&amp;rsquo;t match requested host name ‘ftp.mazohyst.org’
Solution: Edit ~/.lftp/rc so that it contains set ssl:check-hostname no. What this does is pretty self explanatory. If the hostname in the certificate does not match the hostname you&amp;rsquo;re attempting to connect to, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter because it won&amp;rsquo;t check for that in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking of Security</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/speaking-of-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 22:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/speaking-of-security/</guid>
      <description>My last post was about security by obscurity and I talked a little about trying to implement security techniques into my projects. This is really great timing.
Last week, various online services ran by my university were down. It was really inconvenient not having access to my e-mail but I took it in stride. I figured it was just the servers acting up or malware or something like that. It turns out that my university was dealing with a ransomware attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Years of Blogging</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/9-years-of-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 21:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/9-years-of-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I know that probably isn&amp;rsquo;t a lot compared to other bloggers out there but to me, that&amp;rsquo;s mind blowing. 9 years is around 40% of my life and that percentage will only keep on increasing. Assuming that I continue blogging. As long as I can type, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I would stop blogging. Sure, my blogging might be extremely sporadic but it&amp;rsquo;s still blogging to me.
Actually, I was going through my archive and I read a blog post that was from exactly six years and two days ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comics Aren’t Just Kids Stuff!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 01:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</guid>
      <description>I initially started writing this post in 2012. I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through and cleaning out my drafts and decided this one was worthy of continuing and actually publishing.
Comics are usually written off as being childish or something only nerds can enjoy. But, I&amp;rsquo;m not here to argue whether comics are legitimate literature or not. I&amp;rsquo;m here to point out some of my favourite web comics. I don&amp;rsquo;t know where it started but I got bored one day and eventually ended up on a web comics site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally Imported Those Old Posts</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 19:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</guid>
      <description>So now that I&amp;rsquo;ve moved hosts, I decided to do some spring cleaning (fall cleaning?). Right now, my databases are a mess. I have a lot of databases that aren&amp;rsquo;t used and databases that are waiting to be used. I still had my old blog database, back from when Brokenphrases was my main blog. So, I decided to to import all those pages and posts here.
Now my blog post archive is pretty much complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Moved Hosts to Network Panda</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-moved-hosts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 01:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-moved-hosts/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been with Three Words Hosting for a long time now. I can&amp;rsquo;t exactly pinpoint how long&amp;hellip; But I still had my first domain while I was with them. I remember when I had to jump from host to host because they kept disappearing. However, when I found Three Words, I felt like I could stay there forever. Honestly, I have nothing but praise for Misaki. She&amp;rsquo;s been an outstanding host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transition to Foundation: Successful?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/transition-to-foundation-successful/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 17:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/transition-to-foundation-successful/</guid>
      <description>Okay I&amp;rsquo;m so angry, I wrote this entire post out in the &amp;ldquo;Quick Draft&amp;rdquo; section of my dashboard, clicked &amp;ldquo;Save Draft&amp;rdquo; and then when I came back, what I wrote was erased. :( This happens a lot but not enough for me to remember to save entries locally before I publish&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best to recreate what I just wrote. I&amp;rsquo;m still really salty, haha.
In my previous post, I mentioned that I was moving from Bootstrap to Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link Dump #2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/link-dump-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 04:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/link-dump-2/</guid>
      <description>I only have one link today, that&amp;rsquo;s the blog Altair &amp;amp; Vega.
Altair &amp;amp; Vega is an extremely insightful blog that delves deep into the narrative and art of many popular anime and manga titles. They have a group of multiple authors and while their posts aren&amp;rsquo;t regular, when they do show up on my news feed, it&amp;rsquo;s a great treat.
I forget how I originally got to this site. I probably stumbled upon it through the post on the anime Hyouka, &amp;ldquo;And You Don&amp;rsquo;t Doubt Your Own?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/random-tumblr-posts-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 02:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/random-tumblr-posts-3/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Implied misogynistic content, alluding to the USBC shootings, and mentions of rape.
I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I&amp;rsquo;ve made on Tumblr.
 I was listening to an episode of the Internet Box, which was recorded around the time when Andrew got a Tumblr and started stirring the pot with the social justice fan community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/random-tumblr-posts-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/random-tumblr-posts-1/</guid>
      <description>Ugh I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible.
 I had a dream where I literally just lived out my entire day, down to sitting in lecture being bored and taking notes.
You don’t even know how disappointed I am when I woke up knowing that I had to do it all over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Approaching this Blog &amp; R.I.P hide</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/on-approaching-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 16:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/on-approaching-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Suicide content warning.
My philosophy with this blog has always been to approach in a very casual and informal way. I was inspired by a blog to do so, but I don&amp;rsquo;t quite remember what site it was exactly (I&amp;rsquo;m tempted to say it was 6birds, but I&amp;rsquo;m not entirely sure). I try to have this mindset whenever I need to write a blog post. Even so, I don&amp;rsquo;t entirely feel free in writing whatever I want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Started to Play TCGs Again</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-started-to-play-tcgs-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 05:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-started-to-play-tcgs-again/</guid>
      <description>Since I gave up Tumblr for Lent, I realized how much free time I had on my hands without Tumblr. I decided, why not get back into TCGs? And so I did.
TCG stands for &amp;ldquo;Trading Card Game.&amp;rdquo; There are TCGs around the Internet that you can join as long as you yourself have a bit of space on the Internet. The goal of the game is basically to collect all the cards that are available in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Monday After is Always the Worst</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/the-monday-after-is-always-the-worst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 23:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/the-monday-after-is-always-the-worst/</guid>
      <description>The Monday after reading week is always the worst, that is. I told my friend who is from the States that I had reading week and she had no idea what it is. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty much a Canadian/Commonwealth countries thing where we get a couple days off in the middle of the semester. I heard from the grapevine that reading week started because mid-semester is a period when too stressed out students tend to commit suicide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brokenphrases is Expiring Soon</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/brokenphrases-is-expiring-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 19:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/brokenphrases-is-expiring-soon/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, you heard that right. It&amp;rsquo;s expiring in a couple of months. I&amp;rsquo;ve had this domain for almost four years now. That&amp;rsquo;s so weird to think about! You can &amp;ldquo;see&amp;rdquo; Brokenphrases in it&amp;rsquo;s first reincarnation by going into the Wayback Archive. Reading those posts make me cringe. And I remember when I actually tried making money off of my posts. LOL. I earned like seven cents writing that one post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘Twas the Night Before the Last Final….</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/twas-the-night-before-the-last-final/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 05:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/twas-the-night-before-the-last-final/</guid>
      <description>And all though the house
Not a creature was stirring
Not even a certain university student who should be cramming.
Today was everything but studying. I had the intentions of doing so. I even planned out my day! Then things happened. Those things consist of: music and Ray. I spent most of my day hanging out on Last.fm. Then I went to make a quick tweet about how much I hate recursion, for when I actually decided to crack open my textbook for two seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prompt #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/prompt-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 04:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/prompt-1/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what to write about in my blog right now. At first I was like &amp;ldquo;post everyday!&amp;rdquo; but when I got to it, I drew a blank. Not to mention, the 500 words requirement overwhelms me. What can I write about for 500 words??That&amp;rsquo;s why I already missed more than four days of posting. A &amp;ldquo;blog post idea&amp;rdquo; list would be very hand right now. I gotta start writing down said ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Thoughts AKA Tweets I Have Tweeted or Would Like to Tweet</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/random-thoughts-aka-tweets-i-have-tweeted-or-would-like-to-tweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 00:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/random-thoughts-aka-tweets-i-have-tweeted-or-would-like-to-tweet/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a victim of the 140 characters. Okay, sometimes I like to say things that are more than 140 characters but you know what I mean, yeah? Tumblr (not Twitter) has conditioned me to want to share my thoughts every time they pop into my head. Fortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t have Tumblr anymore. Unfortunately, I do have a Twitter. Fortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to use my Twitter1 too much because I have only six followers who probably don&amp;rsquo;t care about me at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’ve Been a Bad Girl</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/ive-been-a-bad-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 04:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/ive-been-a-bad-girl/</guid>
      <description>I completely missed the last two posts entirely. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even start a draft or anything! I&amp;rsquo;m just really frustrated because this reading week has not be as busy as I would have liked it to be. I ended up watching an embarrassing amount of YouTube videos. I will try to list them all in somewhat order.
 Rose by Lee Hi
This kid was 16 years old when she made this song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link Dump #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/link-dump-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 19:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/link-dump-1/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I just want to dump links I find interesting and talk about them in a post and thus Link Dump was born. It is not a weekly feature but more of like a &amp;ldquo;whenever I feel like it feature.&amp;rdquo;
Cyanide Tea
I&amp;rsquo;m not entirely sure how I exactly came across this site but I&amp;rsquo;m sure glad I did. Cyanide Tea is a website of a team of two that creates games (mostly visual novels).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race Against Time</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/race-against-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 06:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/race-against-time/</guid>
      <description>I missed yesterday as well. I&amp;rsquo;m just not very good at this! But I am determined not to miss today. Today I read on Zen Habits that you should never miss doing something two days in a row. It&amp;rsquo;s a good philosophy and a great motivation hack for me. By the time two days have passed, it&amp;rsquo;s very likely that that task will never be accomplished.
So yes, it&amp;rsquo;s around 11:30pm and it takes me around half an hour to write at least 500 words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seriously Can’t Get Over “Gold”</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/seriously-cant-get-over-gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 06:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/seriously-cant-get-over-gold/</guid>
      <description>I have been listening to &amp;ldquo;Gold&amp;rdquo; by Jeff &amp;amp; Casey Lee Williams nonstop all day. I just love it. It makes me want to dance around and sing. It also makes me feel very warm and fuzzy inside. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve listened to a song that makes me that gushy. I just can&amp;rsquo;t get over the funky discos vibe. Those guitar licks and the strings and Casey&amp;rsquo;s voice&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s seriously too much to love!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Gold” and School</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/gold-and-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 06:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/gold-and-school/</guid>
      <description>Two posts in a row about Rooster Teeth. No regrets. I&amp;rsquo;ve been hanging around the Rooster Teeth website1 and just browsing around.
Now, Rooster Teeth has this original animated series called RWBY. Long story short, it&amp;rsquo;s about a group of exceptional warrior youths training to fight against creatures and terrorist groups. Cool, I know. One of the major strengths of the series is it&amp;rsquo;s soundtrack. The soundtrack is absolutely phenomenal. The producer of the series has stated that music is a big inspiration for his work and it totally shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BloWriMo &amp; Rooster Teeth Extra Life 2013 (Image Heavy)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blowrimo-and-rtextralife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 04:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blowrimo-and-rtextralife/</guid>
      <description>November is NaNoWriMo1. I know I will never be able to participate in NaNoWriMo. So I&amp;rsquo;m going to do BloWriMo: Blog Writing Month (which was technically last month, oops). Really lame, I know, but writing everyday is doable but at the same time, challenging. I&amp;rsquo;m aiming for at least 500 words everyday. Yesterday I only did around 440 words but that&amp;rsquo;s because I did not know that I was doing this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Far, So Good</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/so-far-so-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 03:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/so-far-so-good/</guid>
      <description>I am almost done my first month of my second year at university! It&amp;rsquo;s been an interesting year leading up to now. I got into university, turned 18, hated engineering with a passion, sucked at engineering with a passion, went to the Philippines, switched majors (in a transition major right now until I can switch into computer science please don&amp;rsquo;t ask me what it is), got a job as a cashier at Walmart over the summer (don&amp;rsquo;t ask me about that either please), got my courses for this semester dropped, went to fix my schedule, found out it wasn&amp;rsquo;t actually fixed and didn&amp;rsquo;t find out until a few days into the first week, and went to go fix it yet again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally Expired</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/finally-expired/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/finally-expired/</guid>
      <description>Goodbye Pure-Orenji Pure-Orenji.info expired. It was a good three year run. I&amp;rsquo;m sad to see it go but at the same time, it would have happened eventually, so why draw out the process? I guess I&amp;rsquo;m mostly sad over the fact that it was my first domain. I wanted to keep it forever but I grew out of it pretty quick. Hopefully the domains I have now will last me as long, or even longer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking of Letting Brokenphrases Go</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thinking-of-letting-brokenphrases-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 23:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thinking-of-letting-brokenphrases-go/</guid>
      <description>I let Pure-Orenji.info go because of money issues. This is not the case here. I don&amp;rsquo;t think anyone (except for maybe one or two people) followed Pure Orenji back when it was a blog. During that time I was going through a weird relationship thing. Also around that time I bought Brokenphrases.info. The name &amp;ldquo;Brokenphrases&amp;rdquo; was highly inspired by my (lack of) social skills and as much as I don&amp;rsquo;t like to admit it, a poem written by the other person in said relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Needs One Topic Blog Posts?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description>I quit Tumblr for Lent. It&amp;rsquo;s only been a couple of days, and I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated so many Tumblr blog posts in my mind and it&amp;rsquo;s kinda driving me crazy. So crazy to the point where a Tumblr and serious blog crossover is inevitable. Tumblr posts are mostly Twitter-like in nature, except ten times the sarcasm, ten times the ironic usage of poor grammar and spelling, and ten times that length.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Resolutions for 2013</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/13-resolutions-for-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 22:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/13-resolutions-for-2013/</guid>
      <description>A new year, a new set of resolutions, probably another year where said resolutions are never fulfilled. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t hurt to at least dream, yeah? Usually most people do these resolution posts on the first day of the year, but I do mine second! No, I was busy with the opening of my new blog, go check it out. On with the post!
1. Post more I hate how this has to be a resolution, but yes, I want to post more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Through It</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/getting-through-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 22:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/getting-through-it/</guid>
      <description>Christmas break is here and so is a new layout. It&amp;rsquo;s not my own, but I was just enamored by it&amp;rsquo;s simplicity. Enjoy! Whew, I finally made it through my very first semester in university. I must say, it was quite a ride. I&amp;rsquo;m glad I got through it. Finals are behind me and now I can just relax. Even though I do want to take this time to chill out and slow down the pace, I also want to be productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procrastination Nation</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/procrastination-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 20:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/procrastination-nation/</guid>
      <description>Two blog posts in a week?? Is this even possible? I&amp;rsquo;m probably dreaming but it&amp;rsquo;s happening. For real.
Whenever I first get on the computer, I find myself starting out pretty darn focused. I open up Blackboard, see what&amp;rsquo;s new, check my falling grades, cry, start on my assignments, etc. Then suddenly it&amp;rsquo;s 1 in the morning (I&amp;rsquo;m exaggerating, the latest I&amp;rsquo;ve started homework was like 10pm&amp;hellip; Still pretty bad though).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busy Weekends</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/busy-weekends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 21:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/busy-weekends/</guid>
      <description>I have a whole load of things to do this weekend. Not sure if I&amp;rsquo;ll actually get around to doing those said things. But at least my midterms are finally over! But finals start up in two weeks. Huh. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve made a list of things I need to, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t really seem like that much but considering my procrastination habits, it is quite a lot. Weekends are for relaxing, not for drowning myself in tears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Enjoy Being Lazy</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-enjoy-being-lazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 20:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-enjoy-being-lazy/</guid>
      <description>Currently I&amp;rsquo;m writing to you from my shiny new WordPress app on my iPod! I&amp;rsquo;m seriously grateful for the WordPress app. I do 90% of my blogging on my iPod anyway. The only mobile thing about the admin section of WordPress is the login page. Typing long things in Safari is a pain as well. It crashes way too often in Safari. Plus, this app is just distraction free. When you&amp;rsquo;re typing, it&amp;rsquo;s just that: you typing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Discoveries #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/youtube-discoveries-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 21:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/youtube-discoveries-1/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Sunadokei by L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel
Fave song atm: Somebody to Love by CLUBSODA
Fave musician(s) atm: Uhh&amp;hellip; I actually have no idea
 Just so you all know, I waded through 7000+ forums posts to find all the YouTube links I wanted to post here. Then I realized I could have used the search function. OTL Anyway, on to the post. Warning, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot here. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you&amp;rsquo;d want to read it all but yeah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Layout and Some Other Things</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/new-layout-and-some-other-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 20:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/new-layout-and-some-other-things/</guid>
      <description>Yes, after a couple of months, I&amp;rsquo;m somewhat back! And with a new layout as well. I rather like this one more than the previous one. They were both still extremely simple, but I&amp;rsquo;m not a talented designer. I just like writing a lot (I think). With Brokenphrases, I wanted the layouts to be similar to each other. As in, using certain elements (in this case, the logo and the broken two-coloured circle) but with a different structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last.FM Stats</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/last-fm-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 19:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/last-fm-stats/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Hit in the USA by Beat Crusaders
Fave song atm: Somebody to Love by CLUBSODA
Fave musician(s) atm: I actually have no idea
 My Last.FM stats as of July 2012. I use Last.FM a lot, without my knowledge basically. Whenever I open up iTunes, Last.FM secretly scrobbles my music as I listen. Also, whenever I plug my iPod in, I get a dialog box that asks if I want to scrobble everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lent is Over</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lent-is-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 06:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lent-is-over/</guid>
      <description>Lent is over. I haven&amp;rsquo;t visited Room 304 or Goodreads in over 40 days. Geez, I have a lot of catching up to do. I did read over those 40 days but definitely not a lot. I&amp;rsquo;ve been swamped with school work and going to sleep at midnight every night doesn&amp;rsquo;t leave much time for reading.
So, I&amp;rsquo;ve resorted to audiobooks. Yeah, yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;lazy way of reading&amp;rdquo; but I&amp;rsquo;ve been craving some sort of world that I can delve into and just absorb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>40 Days of No Internet</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/40-days-of-no-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 05:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/40-days-of-no-internet/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow marks the beginning of Lent. Last year I gave up Tumblr for Lent. This year I&amp;rsquo;m giving up using the Internet (minus school things). So for the next 40 days I won&amp;rsquo;t be posting, commenting, reading, e-mailing, Twittering, Facebooking or anything that has to do with the Internet. My poor Neopets are going to starve to almost death (that&amp;rsquo;s the the first thought that came to my mind, how sad).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Riddance</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/good-riddance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 21:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/good-riddance/</guid>
      <description>Finally, my final exams are over! I only wrote math and chemistry but I studied my butt off for both of them. Yesterday I had chemistry. It was mad hard but I have to admit that I studied math more than I did for chemistry. I did go to a diploma prep for chemistry which somewhat helped. Math was super easy but I&amp;rsquo;m still worried over it. Super easy could mean that it was really super easy or that I just thought it was easy when in reality, I did everything wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s December…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/its-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 02:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/its-december/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it is finally December!
The first day of December was okay. In math I got my last unit test back. 91%! But then I got my quiz back. 64%! My marks have such variety, don&amp;rsquo;t they? I felt like my math teacher was giving me disappointed looks all through class because I did so bad on this quiz. This unit we&amp;rsquo;re doing, permutations and combinations, is really weird for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Snow</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/hello-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 05:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/hello-snow/</guid>
      <description>Last Wednesday, the marching band (with a few concert bandies) hosted a workshop for the junior highs in the Catholic School District. It was mostly a ploy to get junior high kids to join marching band if and/or when they come to our school. Sadly, concert band wasn&amp;rsquo;t emphasized in any way (I&amp;rsquo;m part of concert and apparently I&amp;rsquo;m inferior to marching band kids HAH I beg to differ). It was fun regardless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me Gusta</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/me-gusta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 05:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/me-gusta/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my weekend in a nutshell: lazy and wonderful. I did almost nothing and I loved it. Too bad this is the last long weekend until Christmas break. Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll hold out until then. So, here&amp;rsquo;s a slightly more detailed view of my weekend.
Thursday:
Woke up early for my dentist appointment. My mom still makes me go to a pediatric dentist because I’m not yet an adult, haha. I was told that I have nice teeth yet I have cavities and I need my wisdom teeth pulled out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asenine</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/asenine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 02:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/asenine/</guid>
      <description>I usually don&amp;rsquo;t post on weekends, even though it&amp;rsquo;s when I have the most free time. Even with free time I&amp;rsquo;m usually wasting it, haha. Although today, I did something somewhat productive, which was retweak the layout! I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if you lot like it, but I do. The fancy @font-face works well, haha. As you can see, I used a font in several place. It&amp;rsquo;s called Asenine. I love this font, and that word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well, That’s Cute</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/well-thats-cute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 20:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/well-thats-cute/</guid>
      <description>I was browsing through some blogs yesterday and came across a blog dedicated to a cat. The blog, I Am Maru is ridiculously cute. It&amp;rsquo;s about a cat named Maru who lives in Japan. The owner likes to take pictures of Maru and put cute captions underneath it. I really think it&amp;rsquo;s adorable.
I love cats. They&amp;rsquo;re just so fluffy and moody (for some reason, that&amp;rsquo;s what I love about them).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confession</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/confession/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 16:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/confession/</guid>
      <description>Wow, it&amp;rsquo;s already August! I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it. Summer is half way done. No way. I wish summer break was longer. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to think about school yet. Although I&amp;rsquo;m extremely excited to start shopping for school supplies. That&amp;rsquo;s honestly my favourite part of going back to school. I&amp;rsquo;m in love with stationary. Notebooks and binders are something I go through very quickly&amp;hellip;
I have a confession to make. It looks like I haven&amp;rsquo;t blogged in a while, but I have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 06:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Blue and Yellow by The Used
Updates: Finally opened!
 Today Brokenphrases is officially open for business! If you want to know more about the site and myself, feel free to go here. So, I&amp;rsquo;ve finally opened Brokenphrases after a year of endless hiatuses and revamping. As you can see, I&amp;rsquo;ve imported as many of my old blog posts from Ueda&amp;hearts;Love, Pure Orenji, and old Brokenphrases that I could find.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back From The Dead</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/back-from-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 16:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/back-from-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>Yes, Pure Orenji is finally open! To all my previous affiliates, please note that this site is no longer my blog. In the future, Brokenphrases will be my blog. If you are willing to change your links, then do so. If you just want to stay affiliated with Pure Orenji, that&amp;rsquo;s fine as well.
I edited the network page. Everything is up except for the &amp;ldquo;Exits&amp;rdquo; page, which I will get around to eventually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First “Post”</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/the-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 04:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/the-first-post/</guid>
      <description>My first post on my new and shiny site! Hello Broken Phrases. =] To those who don’t know, I’m Edel Grace! Pleased to meet you.
A recent obsession of mine is K-Pop. Including Koyote! I first heard them on a plane to the Philippines a year ago. I just heard news of Baekka being sick. Poor Baekka. =[ I hope he recovers soon. What? You don’t know Baekka? D: Oh my goodness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving Up</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/moving-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 18:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/moving-forward/</guid>
      <description>I have exciting news I kinda forgot to tell all of you about!
I now have a domain name.
Pure Orenji
Please check it out! And no, I won&amp;rsquo;t be leaving Ueda Love. I would never do that! Pure Orenji is just a gateway of sorts to all of the sites I own. It&amp;rsquo;s currently under construction.
Oh, I have also a fanlisting collective I&amp;rsquo;ve set up. Be sure to check this out as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Just a Loner</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/im-just-a-l-o-n-e-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 20:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/im-just-a-l-o-n-e-r/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: You Rock My World &amp;#8211; Michael Jackson
Mood: Accomplished, bored.
Fanlisting for Outsider&amp;rsquo;s Loner is now open! Go check it out, and if you are a fan of the song, please join! Click here!
Ahh, I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing too much gaming lately. Even though I&amp;rsquo;m only about 20 hours in on Dissidia: Final Fantasy, I love it! Like Cloud always says, I never want the game to end! It takes a long time to finish the game anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kya! effect</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/kya-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 03:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/kya-effect/</guid>
      <description>The kya! effect is in progress&amp;hellip; kind of.
Ever since the new year started, I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking of changing the site name to &amp;ldquo;kya!&amp;rdquo; as &amp;ldquo;Ueda ♥ Love&amp;rdquo; can imply that it is just a fansite dedicated to Ueda Tatsuya.
I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten a new layout (hint: J-Rock FTW?) all ready. I&amp;rsquo;m working on the pages. With the &amp;ldquo;kya! effect&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m going to focus on my fandoms. Like fanlists, tribute pages, etc etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Before I Go To Sleep</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/before-i-go-to-sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 05:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/before-i-go-to-sleep/</guid>
      <description>I have a few layouts on my computer that I have to upload! Anyway, I should be doing homework. But it isn&amp;rsquo;t due until Wednesday. So I&amp;rsquo;ll do all of it tomorrow&amp;hellip;
This is an amazingly short post. Well, it&amp;rsquo;s better than nothing, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Day~!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/green-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/green-day/</guid>
      <description>Well I should be fixing up my speech. Haha. But I could just wing it. I could talk about Green Day with my eyes closed. Personally, I rather it was that way. I fail at speeches so I need the piece of paper in front of me to read off from!
So my homework of today consists of downloading Green Day songs, looking up lyrics, song meanings, watching interviews, music videos, and crazy random shit that they always seem to be doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Ain’t Bad! You ain’t nothing!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/you-aint-bad-you-aint-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2009 22:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/you-aint-bad-you-aint-nothing/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m glad the burial is coming up. All I can say is &amp;ldquo;FINALLY!&amp;rdquo; I love Michael Jackson. I&amp;rsquo;m still so sad. I love Michael! Did I already say that? Oh. Anyway. Everyone is saying that he&amp;rsquo;s gay, but I refuse to believe it because he is mine and I love him! Just kidding. Michael Jackson fans are crazy&amp;hellip; R.I.P Michael!
Today I went to the Balzack mall that just opened. It&amp;rsquo;s big but not that big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates…and Calling All Bookworms!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/updates-and-calling-all-bookworms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 22:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/updates-and-calling-all-bookworms/</guid>
      <description>Updates:
I finally have some content up! 22 new icons and 2 new layouts. Go check it out! (2011 note: these links do not work)
Calling All Bookworms:
Summer is almost over and I have read about 120 books. Whoot! It may seem impossible but it isn&amp;rsquo;t. Very few of the books I&amp;rsquo;ve read stand out in my mind. If you&amp;rsquo;re a bookworm, check out these books!
Snitch by Alison Van Diepen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryo…who?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/ryo-who/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 23:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/ryo-who/</guid>
      <description>Right now I&amp;rsquo;m working on a layout that features someone&amp;hellip; I know it&amp;rsquo;s Ryo, but a Ryo from what band? I don&amp;rsquo;t know anymore! I forgot! It&amp;rsquo;s not the Ryo from Maximum The Hormone or Ryo from JE. My friend told me a list of Japanese guys she thought was hot, and I went to find desktop backgrounds for her. Ryo was on the list&amp;hellip; Uwah! My memory is bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally! New Layout!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/finally-new-layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 01:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/finally-new-layout/</guid>
      <description>Yes! Haha. Michal Jackson time! I&amp;rsquo;m still pretty broken up about his death, but I just love looking at pictures of him! And videos&amp;hellip; Yesterday, I even bought a Michael Jackson concert CD (haha&amp;hellip;).
So, I just watched Up! It was really good. Except for my left ear that was blocked, and I forgot to bring glasses/put in my contacts. Ugh, my stupidness! It happens often&amp;hellip;My memory is bad, even though I&amp;rsquo;m still young.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Layout Trouble</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/layout-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 04:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/layout-trouble/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Olivia for pointing out my layout issue! I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice&amp;hellip;it looked fine when I first uploaded it. So I switched to the old one while I work out the kinks. Gah!
Anyway~ I just had a party. Marshmallow roasting, kids running around, drunk dads everywhere, you know the works!
AND I saw him today. The guy I have been liking on and off for three years now. Haha. I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen him since Father&amp;rsquo;s Day and I didn&amp;rsquo;t say anything to him back then&amp;hellip; Let&amp;rsquo;s call him&amp;hellip; Gunther.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Layout FTW!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/new-layout-ftw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 02:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/new-layout-ftw/</guid>
      <description>Alright, in my haste, I put up my new layout!
I&amp;rsquo;m trying to fix a bug so all the other pages except for the home page stayed the same (also, I&amp;rsquo;m in a haste&amp;hellip;haha).
Welcome a new affilate:
freaking riot lyts.
I&amp;rsquo;m in the process of at least adding her link on all the old pages so sorry if I miss a page (like I said, I&amp;rsquo;m in a haste, haha).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A thing called…gasp, Javascript!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/a-thing-called-gasp-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 04:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/a-thing-called-gasp-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to find ways to properly display my avatars and future graphics! I&amp;rsquo;m trying to setup Lightbox, but the thing is that the &amp;ldquo;white space&amp;rdquo; is too little. I put captions underneath and it&amp;rsquo;s all&amp;hellip;um. Weird!
Any ideas? I tried to increase the padding, but it did some weird stuff (the avatar wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the white space&amp;hellip;). Does it make sense? I hope it does&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;m working on all those projects below (see last entry) and my fanfic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Updates!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/some-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 01:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/some-updates/</guid>
      <description>Welcome our two new affies: Admins Area and Seventh Heaven. Finally, I added that Links and Affies part of the siderbar up! Haha. I also uploaded 5 new icons! Check them out here. I&amp;rsquo;m not confirmed yet by PAIN but I asked and I am waiting for his reply (rules state that his link be up first).
I need to make buttons for this site! How could I forget? TT_TT I&amp;rsquo;ll go make some now&amp;hellip; And I hope that next update, I&amp;rsquo;ll have the new layout!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Were There</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/we-where-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2009 18:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/we-where-there/</guid>
      <description>Some Updates:
 I&amp;rsquo;m working on a shrine for Green Day. The first project! Whoot! I&amp;rsquo;m almost done the icons for the MJ tribute! But I still have a lot to do&amp;hellip; Me and my friends are making a movie. I just might post it here. I&amp;rsquo;m making a new layout! This Ueda layout is a bit boring, haha.  Real Life:
&amp;ldquo;We Where There&amp;rdquo; by Yuki Obata is definitely THE love story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Opening!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/grand-opening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2009 17:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/grand-opening/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Edel! I&amp;rsquo;m so excited for the opening of my site. When I first got Olivia&amp;rsquo;s email, I was scared to open it. But when I eventually did, I first saw:
&amp;ldquo;Congratulations!
You have been accepted!&amp;rdquo;
And then I screamed&amp;hellip; I Twittered, Facebooked, and forum posted about it. No one really was as estatic as I was, but that was to be expected. I&amp;rsquo;m very excited for what this site can be turned into.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>