<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alexisonfire on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/alexisonfire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alexisonfire on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/alexisonfire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Concert Bucketlist</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/concert-bucketlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/concert-bucketlist/</guid>
      <description>So this year I went to a bunch of concerts. Two of those concerts (Alexisonfire and Coheed and Cambria) were big wish listers for me and this got me thinking. What other artists do I want to see live?
L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel I know for sure that I want to see L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel live in concert. L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel is a band I got into around junior high. Thanks to the power of the Internet, I know approximately the first time I fell in love with L&amp;rsquo;Arc~en~Ciel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week in Music #3: 2018/10/19 - 2018/10/26</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-3/</guid>
      <description>Last.fm is a website that can keep track of users and their listening habits. I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to music with Last.fm since 2010 and am slightly obsessive over my music stats. These stats are for my listening from the past week.
 My week for October 19, 2018 to October 26, 2018
Top 10 Artists   Top 10 Artists     Coheed and Cambria (-) Even though I&amp;rsquo;ve been making a conscious decision to not listen to as much Coheed and Cambria, I&amp;rsquo;m still listening to them quite a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Alexisonfire and Billy Talent</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-alexisonfire-and-billy-talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/thoughts-on-alexisonfire-and-billy-talent/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is not a concert review and this post contains swearing
One of the things on my 25 before 25 bucket list was to go see a concert. The last concert I went to when I made my bucket list was the Japanese band Lix at an anime convention back in 2012 (but that slipped my mind when I wrote it and I said the last concert I went to was a My Chemical Romance concert).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>