<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on edelgrace</title>
    <link>https://edelgrace.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on edelgrace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 23:25:12 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://edelgrace.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>360 Star Gazing</title>
      <link>https://edelgrace.github.io/project/360-star-gazing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 23:25:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edelgrace.github.io/project/360-star-gazing/</guid>
      <description>Sample screenshot    Source code Download How to Run  The &amp;ldquo;Problem&amp;rdquo; When was the last time you looked up at the stars? If you&amp;rsquo;re like me and live in a big city, you might not even remember when the last time you could properly see a star that wasn&amp;rsquo;t the sun. Of course there may be astronomy enthusiasts out there who make a hobby out of looking at the night sky but for the rest of us, we&amp;rsquo;re wannabe casual star gazers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Ring You</title>
      <link>https://edelgrace.github.io/project/i-ring-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 23:25:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edelgrace.github.io/project/i-ring-you/</guid>
      <description>Source code Download How to Run  The &amp;ldquo;Problem&amp;rdquo; In this day and age, instant communication is a given. This makes long distance relationships more feasible. Sometimes though, pulling out a phone or your web browser to log onto Facebook isn’t suitable for all situations when you want to send a quick message to your significant other. Additionally, instant communication can even become too routine and not carry a lot of weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kowther&#39;s Turtle Button</title>
      <link>https://edelgrace.github.io/project/kowthers-turtle-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 23:25:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edelgrace.github.io/project/kowthers-turtle-button/</guid>
      <description>Source code Download How to Run  The &amp;ldquo;Problem&amp;rdquo; The goal of this project was to design a button that would delight its user and respect some aspects of their personality. In this case, the user was a fellow classmate of mine. After some interviewing, I determined the following:
 She watches a lot of movies but no horror or rom coms please She has a double major in psychology and lingusitics She wants a pet box turtle and a cat named Aang (like from Avatar: The Last Airbender) She works a lot and enjoys it (just wishes she would get paid more) She listens to a lot of podcasts some which are movie related and some are DnD related (but she&amp;rsquo;s never played DnD before) She likes the X-men!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>