<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friends and Family on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/friends-and-family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friends and Family on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/friends-and-family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Weekend Penguins and Hacks</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/long-weekend-penguins-and-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/long-weekend-penguins-and-hacks/</guid>
      <description>Last week was the start of Reading Week. Reading Week is basically my university&amp;rsquo;s version of &amp;ldquo;midterm break&amp;rdquo; where we have a week off. I don&amp;rsquo;t have classes on Friday so my Reading Week started early.
Penguins On Friday, my boyfriend and I went to the zoo. We really wanted to see the penguins and the red pandas. Every day, the penguins take a walk around the zoo. It was adorable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productive Distractions</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/2017-09-24-productive-distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 19:06:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/2017-09-24-productive-distractions/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s my boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s birthday coming up soon. I wanted to make him a knitted or a crocheted item because I need something to keep my hands busy. Plus aren&amp;rsquo;t handmade things the sweetest thing you could get as a present??
On some level, I know he&amp;rsquo;s a little picky about what kind of things he would like to wear. To avoid spending a ton of time working on something that he might not ever wear, I sent him a couple links to patterns of scarves and toques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally Imported Those Old Posts</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 19:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</guid>
      <description>So now that I&amp;rsquo;ve moved hosts, I decided to do some spring cleaning (fall cleaning?). Right now, my databases are a mess. I have a lot of databases that aren&amp;rsquo;t used and databases that are waiting to be used. I still had my old blog database, back from when Brokenphrases was my main blog. So, I decided to to import all those pages and posts here.
Now my blog post archive is pretty much complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Straight From Canada</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/straight-from-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 05:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/straight-from-canada/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the Philippines for about five days now. We decided to take a family trip, because it&amp;rsquo;s been way too long since we&amp;rsquo;ve been here. It&amp;rsquo;s been good for the most part. Except it&amp;rsquo;s been an endless cycle of sleep, eat, sleep, eat, sleep with the rare outing. I thought I was going to lose weight here but I&amp;rsquo;m actually gaining, haha.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you want to see my Tumblr-ized version of the first two days of my trip (because I&amp;rsquo;m lazy and the heat makes me even lazier), here you go:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Needs One Topic Blog Posts?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/who-needs-one-topic-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description>I quit Tumblr for Lent. It&amp;rsquo;s only been a couple of days, and I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated so many Tumblr blog posts in my mind and it&amp;rsquo;s kinda driving me crazy. So crazy to the point where a Tumblr and serious blog crossover is inevitable. Tumblr posts are mostly Twitter-like in nature, except ten times the sarcasm, ten times the ironic usage of poor grammar and spelling, and ten times that length.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Resolutions for 2013</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/13-resolutions-for-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 22:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/13-resolutions-for-2013/</guid>
      <description>A new year, a new set of resolutions, probably another year where said resolutions are never fulfilled. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t hurt to at least dream, yeah? Usually most people do these resolution posts on the first day of the year, but I do mine second! No, I was busy with the opening of my new blog, go check it out. On with the post!
1. Post more I hate how this has to be a resolution, but yes, I want to post more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s That Time of Year Again</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/its-that-time-of-year-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 18:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/its-that-time-of-year-again/</guid>
      <description>Usually I bring a textbook with me on the train to study from but today I had only one lecture and I definitely forgot to bring one. So I decided it would be good to write a blog post for once because I really do miss writing these things.
Christmas is indeed in the air! Last week in the food court on campus, Christmas carols were playing and a Santa was walking around asking for donations for some charity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Layout and Some Other Things</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/new-layout-and-some-other-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 20:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/new-layout-and-some-other-things/</guid>
      <description>Yes, after a couple of months, I&amp;rsquo;m somewhat back! And with a new layout as well. I rather like this one more than the previous one. They were both still extremely simple, but I&amp;rsquo;m not a talented designer. I just like writing a lot (I think). With Brokenphrases, I wanted the layouts to be similar to each other. As in, using certain elements (in this case, the logo and the broken two-coloured circle) but with a different structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Remember You</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-remember-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 05:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-remember-you/</guid>
      <description>I meant to post last on the 15th but I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I should blog. It just didn&amp;rsquo;t feel right to do so. Even now, I&amp;rsquo;m not so comfortable posting this but I just need to get it out, which is why it&amp;rsquo;s private. Only three people have the password to my private posts so I guess it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad.
On the 15th I received a text from a friend asking about our mutual friend, T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Easter!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-easter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 22:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-easter-2/</guid>
      <description>Lent is finally over. :) My journey with no interent was&amp;hellip; Not very successful but I managed to go by with minimal (emphasis on minimal) internet. I mostly dedicated myself to YouTube on the &amp;ldquo;play all&amp;rdquo; function so that was interesting. It&amp;rsquo;s weird because I had the strongest urge to blog throughout the forty days. Very odd, I thought I would just forget about it but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t the case at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Know What Happens When You Dance</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/you-know-what-happens-when-you-danc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 18:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/you-know-what-happens-when-you-danc/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was my birthday. Yay birthdays! I&amp;rsquo;m now the golden age of 17 (this means I have to change all my ages on my websites, ack)! I kinda don&amp;rsquo;t feel any different (no one ever does, am I right?), not to mention that 17 is a weird number. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s because it&amp;rsquo;s odd. But 21 and 23 aren&amp;rsquo;t that weird of numbers either. I guess 17 is weird because it&amp;rsquo;s that age that&amp;rsquo;s in between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Weekend!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/long-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 06:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/long-weekend/</guid>
      <description>I understand that it is almost Thanksgiving in the States so others have long weekends as well. But our reasons for the long weekend are because of parent teacher interviews tomorrow and Rememberance day the after.
Speaking of Rememberance day, today was the Rememberance celebration at my school. Since I go to a Catholic school, the celebration is held at the church behind the school. It&amp;rsquo;s a short walk across the field and into the parking lot but it was chilly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screamfest</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/screamfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 02:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/screamfest/</guid>
      <description>EDIT: This was queued to be posted on Halloween. But I accidentally queued it for Halloween&amp;hellip; LAST YEAR. *facepalm* Better late than never.
My iPod&amp;rsquo;s broken. AHHHHHHHHH! I do most of my surfing, blog commenting, and posting on my iPod because I don&amp;rsquo;t have access to my laptop most days. My parents only give me the laptop when I can whole heartedly prove to them that I have homework to do on the laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belated Happy Thanksgiving!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/belated-happy-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 05:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/belated-happy-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was Thanksgiving in Canada land. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to post because of our super long but extremely satisfying dinner. Turkey, ham, and pasta for all! Not to mention that there was no school yesterday.
I said I was going to create passwords and give them out but that never really happened. It will happen sometime this week when I get around to it.
Today was rather interesting. Everyone was talking about post post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile for the Camera!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/smile-for-the-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 03:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/smile-for-the-camera/</guid>
      <description>So I have vowed to write at least something everyday for this school year to document my final year in high school. Some of it will be published, some not. I also know most people don&amp;rsquo;t like &amp;ldquo;this is what I did this whole entire day&amp;rdquo; kind of posts but it is my blog, and well, I&amp;rsquo;ll blog whatever I want. :]
To start things off, today was rather ordinary. I woke up painfully early at six in the morning (well, it&amp;rsquo;s early if you&amp;rsquo;ve been sleeping in until noon for two months) because I heard my mom cooking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confession</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/confession/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 16:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/confession/</guid>
      <description>Wow, it&amp;rsquo;s already August! I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it. Summer is half way done. No way. I wish summer break was longer. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to think about school yet. Although I&amp;rsquo;m extremely excited to start shopping for school supplies. That&amp;rsquo;s honestly my favourite part of going back to school. I&amp;rsquo;m in love with stationary. Notebooks and binders are something I go through very quickly&amp;hellip;
I have a confession to make. It looks like I haven&amp;rsquo;t blogged in a while, but I have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Week Down</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/one-week-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 20:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/one-week-down/</guid>
      <description>I have another week to go! I&amp;rsquo;m just ready for it all to be over. Today was a good day because during my 15 minute break, I met up with one of my friends in the hallway. He and the school marching band been in the US for a while and just came back last night so I had a good talk with him. For a moment, I forgot I had school until the bell rang for the end of the break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Canada Day!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-canada-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 16:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-canada-day/</guid>
      <description>Like the title says, happy Canada day! Today Prince William and Kate are in Canada as we speak celebrating with us. My family doesn&amp;rsquo;t really do anything special for Canada day except for wearing red all day. Last year I spent Canada day in the States actually because of marching band. We were practicing on a football field and on the large scaffolding where the band directors stood, we hung a huge Canadian flag on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnomnom</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-think-everybody-should-join-band/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 04:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-think-everybody-should-join-band/</guid>
      <description>Today was pretty fun!! I found out that I lost 13 pounds, that I fail at trying to bench press, and that I can jump! And a lot of band things happened today.
So today was Marina&amp;rsquo;s (colour guard and clarinet) 16th birthday! And Andrew Lumapas came!! He&amp;rsquo;s for sure my hero. His YouTube vids are EPICALLY AMAZING. So amazing that I have to use all caps. Go check out his YouTube account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apples to Apples</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/apples-to-apples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 23:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/apples-to-apples/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really pumped/hyped up/excited for the Kya! effect. Like no joke. Haha. The layout looks suweeeet. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking of adopting/renting a domain&amp;hellip; Kya~!
To focus on my offline life&amp;hellip; I just spent four hours at my friend&amp;rsquo;s house. Yummy chips, walks to fish creek park, picture taking, and girl talks.
I have to make sure my band teachers convince my mom about me going to California for our tour this summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Valentines Day~! &lt;3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-valentines-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2010 00:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/happy-valentines-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I&amp;rsquo;m all alone on this five day long weekend. My parents have banned me from going anywhere with my friends. Ahh great. I&amp;rsquo;ll be alone on Valentines day D:
Anyway, I keep saying I will do things but my parents want me off the computer more and more. =/ I&amp;rsquo;m currently downloading my homework (a worksheet posted on my school website&amp;hellip;haha).
So what&amp;rsquo;s up with everyone?
I&amp;rsquo;m really tired and bored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maayong Pasko!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/maayong-pasko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 18:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/maayong-pasko/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas, guys!! I hope all of you have an amazing Christmas! I&amp;rsquo;m getting an iPod Touch FTW! I&amp;rsquo;m excited. Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;m on my brother&amp;rsquo;s new PSP! It&amp;rsquo;s kinda hard to type on this thing&amp;hellip; &amp;gt;_&amp;lt; Soooo my birthday is coming up! I am also excited for that! sorry for the short post&amp;hellip; Everyone have a good day! =]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything At Once</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/give-me-everything-at-once/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 21:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/give-me-everything-at-once/</guid>
      <description>We have a new affiliate, Sute/Himitsu-Sasshi. I adore her website! I&amp;rsquo;m so glad she is an affiliate ^^
And I&amp;rsquo;m making a new layout! Whoot! It features BGHS Marching Band. Oh of course. Haha. It&amp;rsquo;s so colourful, I love it! I&amp;rsquo;m also putting band quotes in the background. Yay!
What else, what else? I have Hallelujah in my head. We have to learn a whole new song by next week for soe District anniversay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grey Cup!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/grey-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/grey-cup/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s watching the Grey Cup next week?
To those who don&amp;rsquo;t know.
Grey Cup: The championship of the CLF (Canadian Football League). The Grey Cup game is the centre of a larger week of festivities put on by the host cities, including concerts, gala events, and autograph sessions. Also an important part of the event in the halftime show which in recent years has included major Canadian and international musical acts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ear Syringes</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/ear-syringes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 02:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/ear-syringes/</guid>
      <description>I can hear again! I went into the walk-in clinic and they shot hot water in my ear. It felt like those jet hot tubs&amp;hellip;except in your ear. Haha. It kinda hurt but the main thing is, I CAN HEAR!
Anyway my best friend is in the US and I miss her! She&amp;rsquo;s missing out all the fun youth events at church. Like tomorrow is the Corn Maze! Yes, Corn Mazes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Parties, Food, School, and . . . Michael Jackson!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lake-parties-food-school-and-michael-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 02:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/lake-parties-food-school-and-michael-jackson/</guid>
      <description>Some updates&amp;hellip; Alright, I&amp;rsquo;ve got the basic Nav links up. Sadly, I forgot the Affies and Linkage&amp;hellip; links. TT_TT I&amp;rsquo;ll fix it later (read the last paragraph). I got my Twitter up, my stats counter, and a new C-BOX! What am I missing? Oh right, actual content! Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, I&amp;rsquo;m working on it&amp;hellip;
Now back to real life&amp;hellip; Yesterday I went to a party for the end of the year. Okay, it was more like a BBQ but it still counts, right?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>