<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Love on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/love/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Love on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/love/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Want to be In Love</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-want-to-be-in-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-want-to-be-in-love/</guid>
      <description>Tamen De Gushi, Chapter 124    I was scrolling through Tumblr when I saw that one of my friends had posted a comic strip from a Chinese comic that I used to follow. It&amp;rsquo;s called Tamen De Gushi or in English, Their Story. The comic follows two girls, Sun Jing and Qiu who fall in love and start dating. Overall, the comic is very sweet, uplifting, and wholesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be My Dearest, First on Earth</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/be-my-dearest-first-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 18:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/be-my-dearest-first-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>I’m still waiting to fall in love with a book. I want to open it and never want to put it down ever again. I want to find myself in it. I want it to drag out the dark from inside of me and then I want it to tell me that it’s okay and to list all the things that are good about me. I want to read it and never look at life and humanity the same way again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversations Over Text Messages</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/conversations-over-text-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/conversations-over-text-messages/</guid>
      <description>Long weird sappy feelings. So much sap and cheese and this sounded better in my head because I kinda read it in a certain way. Man, I just don’t know. Also, for the love of gulay, the end of a line does not mean &amp;ldquo;pause.&amp;rdquo; Punctuation means &amp;ldquo;pause.&amp;rdquo; Yes, you’re supposed to run out of breath (I&amp;rsquo;m kinda slightly asthmatic though, so).
i’m sorry,
but i won’t ever text you again</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Finals Down, One More to Go</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/2-finals-down-one-more-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 01:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/2-finals-down-one-more-to-go/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m done all the finals that I&amp;rsquo;m mostly concerned about. Ok, I&amp;rsquo;m also concerned about CPSC 231 but not as much as I was about the other two. The main reason why I&amp;rsquo;m concerned about it? I don&amp;rsquo;t want to let senpai down. Lame, I know. Super lame. But I don&amp;rsquo;t want to look like an idiot in front of him! It&amp;rsquo;s a super easy course and if I screw it up, it&amp;rsquo;s super embarrassing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not So Subtle</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/not-so-subtle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 07:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/not-so-subtle/</guid>
      <description>That moment when your TA is looking at you not so subtly. Or maybe I just have sucky peripheral vision. WOW I really hope the latter is not the case. Man, my heart is so doki doki when I think about him. Much dork. :(</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having an Off Day</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/having-an-off-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 06:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/having-an-off-day/</guid>
      <description>Today I do something new. This is my writing. I did not intend to post it on my blog but then I realized I released all of my feelings here. Feels good I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doki Doki Senpai</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/doki-doki-senpai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 04:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/doki-doki-senpai/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday1 I chatted a bit with my senpai. He was so adorable. :( Now I&amp;rsquo;m sure he does not have feelings for me which is both a relief and a disappointment at the same time. Relief because lol that could get too complicated and a disappointment because he&amp;rsquo;s so cute. D:
However, today I did talk to him. I asked him how his weekend was. Apparently it was bad. He spent the whole weekend writing an eleven page paper about network systems and stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doki Doki Goes the Heart</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/doki-doki-goes-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 02:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/doki-doki-goes-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>My heart hasn&amp;rsquo;t gone doki doki in a while. The last time I can remember is when I was in my freshman year of high school when I was crushing on my first boyfriend1. This was, of course, before last Friday.
On Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays I have my first class with three of my friends. We all have a break after the class so we eat together. Last Friday, we decided to eat in the ICT building.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>