<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Green Day on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/green-day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Green Day on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 08:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/green-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity Dreams</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/celebrity-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 08:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/celebrity-dreams/</guid>
      <description>I had a dream, that Gerard Way and Amy Lee were at my church and they fighting over who was a better singer. It was so weird. Then suddenly, Gerard got naked. One second he had clothes, the next he didn&amp;rsquo;t. He just magically got naked and strangely, Amy wasn&amp;rsquo;t bothered with it.
I also had a dream that Billie Joe Armstrong murdered someone and got into jail and went all crazy up in the mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bouncy</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/bouncy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/bouncy/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted in a while. For some reason I&amp;rsquo;ve been on Geek Stink breath a lot. I miss the old GSB, when there were more people there. I still love GSB though!
I have been working on my religion project for the past four days. I&amp;rsquo;m finally finished now. Thank goodness. Who knew that a simple powerpoint about a saint would be so much work? I guess I&amp;rsquo;m too much of a perfectionist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grade Niners</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/grade-niners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 23:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/grade-niners/</guid>
      <description>My locker&amp;rsquo;s right next to the band room, and grade niners are constantly standing around my locker. The grade niners like to listen to this guy play the drums every single lunch period. I was opening my locker, and the guy who plays the drums was looking at my locker. They saw my Billie Joe Armstrong poster (which unfortunately does not exist anymore because one of my friends tore it up).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>