<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gaming on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/gaming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gaming on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 02:14:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 02:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-3/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Implied misogynistic content, alluding to the USBC shootings, and mentions of rape.
I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I&amp;rsquo;ve made on Tumblr.
 I was listening to an episode of the Internet Box, which was recorded around the time when Andrew got a Tumblr and started stirring the pot with the social justice fan community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 02:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-2/</guid>
      <description>I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I&amp;rsquo;ve made on Tumblr.
 In Mass Effect 4 I just want to talk more. I want to learn more about their cultures and I want to do stuff for them, even if it’s just talking them through decisions and not going to the ends of the universe for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calgary Expo 2014</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/calgary-expo-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 23:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/calgary-expo-2014/</guid>
      <description>**WARNING: This post contains over 30 pictures. Open if you dare! An ableism trigger warning as well (possible slur).
ALSO: If you see your picture here and would like credit or for me to take it down, please leave a comment.**
This was my second year going to my local con. Last year I went all three days but this year I just went one day. It was a lot of fun but also soooo exhausting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Holidays 2013</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/christmas-holidays-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 18:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/christmas-holidays-2013/</guid>
      <description>My exams ended relatively early last semester. That meant more time for a break! I didn&amp;rsquo;t do terribly a lot over through break though. Definitely was not as productive as I would have liked to be.
Finished watching and reading Shingeki no Kyojin
Shingeki no Kyojin is an anime. The Internet has been basically exploding over it (my part of the Internet anyway). My friends in real life also freak out over it and so much so that I just had to see what they were on about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘Twas the Night Before the Last Final….</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/twas-the-night-before-the-last-final/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 05:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/twas-the-night-before-the-last-final/</guid>
      <description>And all though the house
Not a creature was stirring
Not even a certain university student who should be cramming.
Today was everything but studying. I had the intentions of doing so. I even planned out my day! Then things happened. Those things consist of: music and Ray. I spent most of my day hanging out on Last.fm. Then I went to make a quick tweet about how much I hate recursion, for when I actually decided to crack open my textbook for two seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Thoughts AKA Tweets I Have Tweeted or Would Like to Tweet</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-thoughts-aka-tweets-i-have-tweeted-or-would-like-to-tweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 00:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-thoughts-aka-tweets-i-have-tweeted-or-would-like-to-tweet/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a victim of the 140 characters. Okay, sometimes I like to say things that are more than 140 characters but you know what I mean, yeah? Tumblr (not Twitter) has conditioned me to want to share my thoughts every time they pop into my head. Fortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t have Tumblr anymore. Unfortunately, I do have a Twitter. Fortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to use my Twitter1 too much because I have only six followers who probably don&amp;rsquo;t care about me at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link Dump #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/link-dump-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 19:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/link-dump-1/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I just want to dump links I find interesting and talk about them in a post and thus Link Dump was born. It is not a weekly feature but more of like a &amp;ldquo;whenever I feel like it feature.&amp;rdquo;
Cyanide Tea
I&amp;rsquo;m not entirely sure how I exactly came across this site but I&amp;rsquo;m sure glad I did. Cyanide Tea is a website of a team of two that creates games (mostly visual novels).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>