<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Family on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Family on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:17:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Icing Charades</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/cookie-icing-charades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/cookie-icing-charades/</guid>
      <description>The Game
Take turns to ice an object or living being onto a cookie. Everyone guesses what that person iced onto the cookie. There are no winners, just a bunch of people having fun and joking around about their lack of (or possession of) artistic ability.
The Background
Over the holidays I was baking brownies and cookies with my cousins. The brownies had left over frosting so we decided to ice the cookies with cool designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost Happy Birthday</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/almost-happy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2007 22:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/almost-happy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>My birthday is in four days! I&amp;rsquo;ll finally be thirteen! I have had it with people staring at me and going, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re still twelve?&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s annoying. I&amp;rsquo;m not the only twelve year old in grade eight!
One of my friends is already fourteen! She can get her learner&amp;rsquo;s permit nd she cant get over the fact she&amp;rsquo;s two years older than me. At least I&amp;rsquo;m not like my one friend. HHe doesnt turn thirteen until February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bouncy</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/bouncy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/bouncy/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted in a while. For some reason I&amp;rsquo;ve been on Geek Stink breath a lot. I miss the old GSB, when there were more people there. I still love GSB though!
I have been working on my religion project for the past four days. I&amp;rsquo;m finally finished now. Thank goodness. Who knew that a simple powerpoint about a saint would be so much work? I guess I&amp;rsquo;m too much of a perfectionist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>