<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friends on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/friends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friends on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Stuffed</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/im-stuffed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/im-stuffed/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: These are my own opinions of these restaurants, this post is not sponsored!
This weekend was a very filling one. Each day I was eating something yummy, somewhere!
Friday My brother and my cousin went to Blue Fin Sushi. They have an all you can eat lunch pretty cheaply for $17.84 CAD. No limits or anything! I was supposed to go with them last week but I ended up missing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Work…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/back-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 03:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/back-to-work/</guid>
      <description>The holidays are officially over, for I went back to work today. It was a bit of a slow day. I got my internship extended, however they basically treated me as a new hire since my contract ended in December. So I&amp;rsquo;m starting from scratch, essentially. I had no laptop, no e-mail, no account to login into any computer connected to the company&amp;rsquo;s network&amp;#8230; Kinda rough.
However, I did manage to do some small tasks that didn&amp;rsquo;t require the use of a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost Happy Birthday</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/almost-happy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2007 22:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/almost-happy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>My birthday is in four days! I&amp;rsquo;ll finally be thirteen! I have had it with people staring at me and going, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re still twelve?&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s annoying. I&amp;rsquo;m not the only twelve year old in grade eight!
One of my friends is already fourteen! She can get her learner&amp;rsquo;s permit nd she cant get over the fact she&amp;rsquo;s two years older than me. At least I&amp;rsquo;m not like my one friend. HHe doesnt turn thirteen until February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Bank</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/food-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 08:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/food-bank/</guid>
      <description>Today, my TA went to the church across the street to help out with the food hampers. Our job was to bring all 200 something boxes from the basement to the main floor. Do you know how hard that is? It was definitely a workout for me. I got my friend pat to help me with over half of my boxes and he calls me lazy. There was this freight elevator, and we had to bring carts full of food with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TA</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/ta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2007 05:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/ta/</guid>
      <description>Three days ago, I started school, and I found out that we no longer have homerooms. Now we have TA I went to my TA in the band room and found three grade niners there, and I thought I was in the wrong homeroom, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Oh and guess who my teacher advisors are? The principal and the vice principal! This is going to be one great year.
I have three of my friends in my TA and I have to stick with my TA Until I finish junior high&amp;hellip; b=Vleh.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>