<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rwby on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/rwby/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rwby on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/rwby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Week in Music #3: 2018/10/19 - 2018/10/26</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-week-in-music-3/</guid>
      <description>Last.fm is a website that can keep track of users and their listening habits. I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to music with Last.fm since 2010 and am slightly obsessive over my music stats. These stats are for my listening from the past week.
 My week for October 19, 2018 to October 26, 2018
Top 10 Artists   Top 10 Artists     Coheed and Cambria (-) Even though I&amp;rsquo;ve been making a conscious decision to not listen to as much Coheed and Cambria, I&amp;rsquo;m still listening to them quite a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seriously Can’t Get Over “Gold”</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/seriously-cant-get-over-gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 06:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/seriously-cant-get-over-gold/</guid>
      <description>I have been listening to &amp;ldquo;Gold&amp;rdquo; by Jeff &amp;amp; Casey Lee Williams nonstop all day. I just love it. It makes me want to dance around and sing. It also makes me feel very warm and fuzzy inside. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve listened to a song that makes me that gushy. I just can&amp;rsquo;t get over the funky discos vibe. Those guitar licks and the strings and Casey&amp;rsquo;s voice&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s seriously too much to love!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Gold” and School</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/gold-and-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 06:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/gold-and-school/</guid>
      <description>Two posts in a row about Rooster Teeth. No regrets. I&amp;rsquo;ve been hanging around the Rooster Teeth website1 and just browsing around.
Now, Rooster Teeth has this original animated series called RWBY. Long story short, it&amp;rsquo;s about a group of exceptional warrior youths training to fight against creatures and terrorist groups. Cool, I know. One of the major strengths of the series is it&amp;rsquo;s soundtrack. The soundtrack is absolutely phenomenal. The producer of the series has stated that music is a big inspiration for his work and it totally shows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>