<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 20:26:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ending of Arrival</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/the-ending-of-arrival/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/the-ending-of-arrival/</guid>
      <description>I finally got to watch Arrival the other day. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t exactly everything that I expected but I think I wasn&amp;rsquo;t displeased with the twist.
The fist half of the movie follows Louise, a professor who specializes in languages and translations. She is recruited by the government to help translate the language of aliens who had touched down on earth. Together with a mathematician, Ian, they slowly learn the writing system of the aliens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Watched: Rogue One</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/i-saw-rogue-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 03:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/i-saw-rogue-one/</guid>
      <description>Spoilers, beware.
I am not a huge Star Wars fan. I watched the first trilogy very quickly, bits and pieces of the second trilogy, and The Force Awakens. Honestly, most of what I know about Star Wars is from the Lego video games and Family Guy. However, my lack of knowledge of the franchise didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me from going to the theaters and watching the latest installment.
When I first watched the Rogue One trailer, I was left wanting for a little more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Know What Happens When You Dance</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/you-know-what-happens-when-you-danc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 18:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/you-know-what-happens-when-you-danc/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was my birthday. Yay birthdays! I&amp;rsquo;m now the golden age of 17 (this means I have to change all my ages on my websites, ack)! I kinda don&amp;rsquo;t feel any different (no one ever does, am I right?), not to mention that 17 is a weird number. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s because it&amp;rsquo;s odd. But 21 and 23 aren&amp;rsquo;t that weird of numbers either. I guess 17 is weird because it&amp;rsquo;s that age that&amp;rsquo;s in between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He-Man Woman Haters</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/dear-darla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 00:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/dear-darla/</guid>
      <description>Right now, it&amp;rsquo;s commercial break and I&amp;rsquo;m watching The Little Rascals. This movie is such a classic. I would always watch it nonstop when I was younger. It&amp;rsquo;s almost kinda weird watching it now. I feel like a kid all over again! Except now, I can recite all the words to this movie.
My favourite lines?
_Dear Darla,
I hate your stinking guts.
You make me vomit.
You are scuuuum between my toes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovelie</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/lovelie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 18:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/lovelie/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday I got to see Alice in Wonderland! I absolutely loved it. Tim Burton makes amazing movies. Edward Scissorhands, Corpse Bride, The Nightmare Before Christmas&amp;hellip; Holy cheese he is a genious! And Helena Carter is such a great actress. She did the Red Queen so well! Johnny Depp, pssh. He was a good Hatter though.
After the movie, we went to Zellers! There was some toys on display and Cloud touched one of them and then it started to sing and dance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>