<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Knitting on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/knitting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Knitting on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/knitting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Knitting Sutra by Susan Gordon Lydon</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-the-knitting-sutra-by-susan-gordon-lydon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/book-review-the-knitting-sutra-by-susan-gordon-lydon/</guid>
      <description>The Knitting Sutra     When Susan Gordon Lydon was coping with a broken arm, her craft took on new significance. While knitting was essential to strengthening her hands, it also provided her with a newfound sense of peace and creativity. Immersed in brilliant colors, textures, and images of beautiful sweaters, Lydon found healing and enlightenment in a way she had never imagined. Capturing this journey of discovery, The Knitting Sutra recounts her remarkable membership in a community of craftswomen around the world, from sweater makers in Scotland to Navajo weavers, and the adventures that her craft led her on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kits and Knits</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/kits-and-knits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/kits-and-knits/</guid>
      <description>Last week was the end of final exams and on my last exam, I decided to take a well deserved day out. In celebration of Canada Day, Tim Hortons was bringing back Roll Up the Rim for a time. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to cut down on my coffee but I decided to get at least one cup, just to try my luck. Turns out that my luck isn&amp;rsquo;t that so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning How to Knit at STASH Needle Art Lounge #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/learning-how-to-knit-at-stash-needle-art-lounge-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 07:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/learning-how-to-knit-at-stash-needle-art-lounge-1/</guid>
      <description>Since I recently took up crochet, I have also been itching to start learning how to knit as well. I figure it would be advantageous to take up both of the more well known fiber art hobbies. So I signed up for lessons at one of my local yarn stores.
The store itself is very cozy and quaint. It&amp;rsquo;s literally a small house filled to the brim with yarn. The people at the front desk are extremely nice and while I was waiting for class to start, they offered me some tea.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>