<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2018 in Review</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/february-2018-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/february-2018-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Summary February felt so short! Shorter than usual. I suppose it always feels this short because February is short already. Also, Reading Week is a week where we have the entire week off so it&amp;rsquo;s inherently less productive due to the less hours.
I started using Todoist as my organizational system but we&amp;rsquo;ll see whether or not it sticks. So far I like it. But I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the premium version and I might have to pay for it soon&amp;hellip; Not looking forward to that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2018 in Review</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/january-2018-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/january-2018-in-review/</guid>
      <description>My 2018 started pretty quick. By the 2nd of January, I was back in class. I took a block week course and barely survived. My sleep schedule was terrible and waking up for an 8:00 AM class everyday was extremely jarring.
Expenses
Timeline  Jan 02: Started classes Jan 03: Dinner at Limericks Jan 06: Dinner at Seoul Korean BBQ Jan 07: Winded some yarn and started on a shawl (post) Jan 10: Went to the gym   Trying to run fast     Jan 16: Went to a Crochet and Knitting Meetup Jan 17: Went to the gym   My gym partner took forever to come so I spent over an hour on the treadmill     Jan 19: Went to BlueFin for all you can eat sushi (post) Jan 20: Celebrated my birthday with friends at Moon Korean BBW (post) Jan 21: Went to Taco Time with my cousin for discounted food (post) Jan 23: Tried Tango lessons Jan 24: Dinner at Sho Sushi Jan 31: Went to the gym   My gym partner didn&amp;#39;t show up but that&amp;#39;s okay I planned for this     Jan 31 (cont&amp;rsquo;d): Also went to Kilkenny&amp;rsquo;s for a charity event that my friend was hosting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Watched: Westworld</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-watched-westworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/i-watched-westworld/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This post contains spoilers, and mentions of death and sex. You have been warned!
This year my SO introduced me to Westworld, a TV series that recently had their first (and last?) season end. Westworld is a highly advanced Western theme park populated with extremely life-like robots that cater to every want of their guests. It is rife of violence, alcohol, sex, and whatever you could imagine in the wild West.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Stuffed</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/im-stuffed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/im-stuffed/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: These are my own opinions of these restaurants, this post is not sponsored!
This weekend was a very filling one. Each day I was eating something yummy, somewhere!
Friday My brother and my cousin went to Blue Fin Sushi. They have an all you can eat lunch pretty cheaply for $17.84 CAD. No limits or anything! I was supposed to go with them last week but I ended up missing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber Frugal Month January 2018: Day 1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/uber-frugal-month-january-2018-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/uber-frugal-month-january-2018-day-1/</guid>
      <description>This is a month-long challenge held over at Frugalwoods. Feel free to join whenever you can!
Today&amp;rsquo;s Mantra: Anything in life that’s worth doing takes effort.
Today&amp;rsquo;s Action: Write down why you’re participating in the Uber and answers to
The Homework Step 1: Establish your goals Why are you participating in this challenge?
I want to build good spending habits for when I move out. I currently still live with my parents and admittedly am still quite spoiled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2017</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-2017/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR/Highlights
I didn&amp;rsquo;t accomplish as much as I would have liked this year. However, this year was extremely eventful.
 Finished my internship and saved a lot of #MovingOut money Started and finished self-esteem group therapy Went to my first hackathon at Hack the North in Waterloo, Ontario Attended both the Calgary Expo and Calgary Expo Holiday Market Was a little more social this year Ate a lot of good food (AKA went to a ton of restaurants and pubs) Started crocheting and knitting  It&amp;rsquo;s been a wild year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Tinkering with My Productivity System</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/forever-tinkering-with-my-productivity-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 23:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/forever-tinkering-with-my-productivity-system/</guid>
      <description>I follow the blog baty.net in which Jack Baty continuously finds new tools and new ways to improve his productivity. While I usually scoff at people who are always changing things up, I will admit that I am the exact same way. It would be great to just stick to something tried and true and never have to think about changing but there is just so much out there that it&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to resist the temptation to not try everything I can see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m a Little Behind</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/im-a-little-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/im-a-little-behind/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I was behind on my granny squares for my temperature blanket. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know, temperature blankets consist of one square a day and each square represents the temperature of that day. Thankfully, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to catch up with temperature blankets! Even though I&amp;rsquo;m caught up with the squares, I still haven&amp;rsquo;t woven the ends in yet nor have I joined them. Eek!
Last week I was babysitting my little cousin and he was playing with my yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STASH Lounge Moving and Other Outings</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yesterday opened up at their new location across the street. I dragged my brother along with me to the opening.
It was absolutely lovely! They had a DJ play some music in the background, a coffee bar, and a table of yummy sweets in the back. They even had door prizes, which I suspect I didn&amp;rsquo;t win anything from but that&amp;rsquo;s totally okay.
In terms of the space, it&amp;rsquo;s great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Crocheting on a Road Trip</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 15:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went to Drumheller with the family. Up to this point I haven&amp;rsquo;t had a chance to go on a long road trip with my crochet. I started this ripple afghan a couple of days ago with Bernat Blanket Stripes yarn. This blanket is intended for my cousins&amp;rsquo;s newborn son. I guess he isn&amp;rsquo;t quite so newborn now but every baby could use a blanket regardless! I actually restarted this blanket once or twice but I finally got the hang of it while on this trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stampede Food</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/stampede-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/stampede-food/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, Stampede is synonymous with food for me. Stampede means free breakfasts for a week. Usually these breakfasts consists of pancakes and sausages. We ended up going to six of these breakfasts. Some of them were worth it, some of them weren&amp;rsquo;t. One of them actually ended up being $250 because my brother got fined for forgetting to validate his train ticket on the way to a breakfast. But still, a lot of pancakey goodness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Out in Pre-Stampede Rush</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</guid>
      <description>I went to the first pancake breakfast of the season with my family the other day. It was close to home which was a great bonus because my dad had the car for work. The breakfast wasn&amp;rsquo;t busy at all but maybe being fairly early was a factor. They only served pancakes and sausage patties but they were pretty good! There was also a Tim Hortons truck giving out free coffee and hot chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kits and Knits</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/kits-and-knits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/kits-and-knits/</guid>
      <description>Last week was the end of final exams and on my last exam, I decided to take a well deserved day out. In celebration of Canada Day, Tim Hortons was bringing back Roll Up the Rim for a time. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to cut down on my coffee but I decided to get at least one cup, just to try my luck. Turns out that my luck isn&amp;rsquo;t that so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Before 25: Update #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/25-before-25-update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 01:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/25-before-25-update-1/</guid>
      <description>I took a little break during the month of May. My mental health was honestly at an all time low and I found myself having a hard time picking myself back up to get motivated to actually do things. Since I am around 6 months into my 22nd year of living, I thought it would be a good time to pause and reflect how I&amp;rsquo;m doing with my 25 before 25.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #16</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/book-blogger-hop-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/book-blogger-hop-16/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Would you stop reading a book if an element of the plot strongly clashed with your personal beliefs, or would you continue reading until you finished the book?
 I would definitely finish the book. At least, that&amp;rsquo;s what I think and hope I would do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour at Cafe Blanca</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/an-hour-at-cafe-blanca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 09:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/an-hour-at-cafe-blanca/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a cool hip place at the edge of Calgary&amp;rsquo;s Chinatown and across Eau Claire Market called Cafe Blanca. They&amp;rsquo;re most known for their Siphon coffee which I unfortunately did not remember to try. Instead, I ordered a plain normal latte and a cheesecake.

Now, I&amp;rsquo;m not cheesecake expert but I&amp;rsquo;m definitely a cheesecake lover. I got myself a mint chocolate cheesecake. It was extremely delicious. It was a little more cake than I prefer (the base was an actual chocolate cake and yes, cake, not brownie) and not as much cheese as I&amp;rsquo;d like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paint Nite Calgary at Yuk Yuk’s Comedy Club</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/paint-nite-at-yuk-yuks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/paint-nite-at-yuk-yuks/</guid>
      <description>One of the interns at my workplace suggested going painting as an activity that we could all do together. It seemed fun so we decided to give it a try! Paint Nite is a series of painting events held at bars, each session hosted by different people.
That day we went to Yuk Yuk&amp;rsquo;s Comedy Club which is a few minutes walk from Victoria Park Stampede. We were really confused about the food since there was no (or incorrect) information on the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Bought a New Laptop</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/i-bought-a-new-laptop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/i-bought-a-new-laptop/</guid>
      <description>My SO and I have been playing an MMO called Blade and Soul recently. We were optmistic about it running on my laptop because the requirements didn&amp;rsquo;t seem too intensive and it even supported Windows 7.
It would crash at every single loading screen. Playing on the lowest settings in a 800&amp;#215;600 window lowered the number of crashes greatly but the loading times were still absolutely ridiculous. I even managed to finish crocheting a bag while waiting for the game to load.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art, Food, and Good Old Bowling</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/art-food-and-good-old-bowling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 09:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/art-food-and-good-old-bowling/</guid>
      <description>At the company where I&amp;rsquo;m doing an internship right now offered all the interns the opportunity to go to their downtown location and give us a tour of all the art. It seems a little weird to give art tours in an office environment but once we stepped into the building, it made sense. There was art on every single floor of the building (of which there are over ten floors) and almost every single wall has a piece of art hanging on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Can I Get Coffee After Five in this City?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/where-can-i-get-coffee-after-five-in-this-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 05:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/where-can-i-get-coffee-after-five-in-this-city/</guid>
      <description>I found myself in downtown with cancelled plans the other day. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to be home for another two hours so I decided to try a new coffee place. It was around five in the evening. I pulled up Google Maps and searched for coffee.
Scrolling through the list, I found that most of the coffee places closed at 5:00PM or 6:00PM. I needed a place to sit and blog hop for a little bit so that was no good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being Depressed in a Relationship</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/being-depressed-in-a-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 12:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/being-depressed-in-a-relationship/</guid>
      <description>Disclimer: This blog post does not give any advice.
What really irks me is when people say that those who are depressed don&amp;rsquo;t deserve or shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be in a relationship. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m depressed myself and in a relationship that it&amp;rsquo;s a touchy subject for me.
However , I can see some of the reasoning. In my own experience, dealing with depression while being in a relationship has its own set of challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Joined a Gym</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/i-joined-a-gym/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/i-joined-a-gym/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to do more things in my free time, I decided to join a gym. My original plan was to go to my university gym however since I am on co-op, I no longer have the discounted membership included in my tuition. Instead, I opted for my local Fit4Less. It is an extremely more convenient location, significantly cheaper, and a good &amp;ldquo;introductory&amp;rdquo; gym for those who are just starting out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #5.5</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-5-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-5-5/</guid>
      <description>I decided to post a work in progress. My SO picked this week&amp;rsquo;s picture and it was of a very pretty warrior girl. I started it and I really like how the face turned out. I quickly sketched out the rest of the body and I am already pretty proud of it. Compared to the original, my version looks a little less feminine. I just can&amp;rsquo;t draw lips right from the side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying Meetups.com</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/trying-meetups-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/trying-meetups-com/</guid>
      <description>Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling pretty down in the dumps. Ever since I started working, I realized that I have a lot of free time that I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do with. I even started to (I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I&amp;rsquo;m saying this) miss having homework. Okay, I actually have a lot of projects that I want to get working on but I also want to be a little more social.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #4</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 02:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-4/</guid>
      <description>I chose last week&amp;rsquo;s picture this time. I thought the picture of the duck statues wearing the kitty hats from the Women&amp;rsquo;s March was pretty cute and easy to do as well. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t that easy, unfortunately. I didn&amp;rsquo;t finish the sidewalk. Didn&amp;rsquo;t want to draw all those stones. My SO didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to get very far with it either unfortunately. But it was fun to draw!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Town Hall with the Prime Minister</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/town-hall-with-the-prime-minister/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 02:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/town-hall-with-the-prime-minister/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the Prime Minister stopped by our city to hold a quick Q &amp;amp; A with the general public. He spoke at my university and as such, university students had the first chance to get early admission to the event. I had left work a little bit early to get to the university. I grabbed a Carl&amp;rsquo;s Jr burger (which greatly upset my stomach) and ate in the Computer Science club room watching some people play fighting games and Magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/weekly-drawing-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 02:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/weekly-drawing-3/</guid>
      <description>Last week&amp;rsquo;s theme was fantasy. The original picture was a lot more ethereal and pretty. I had to redraw this one because I messed up the background. The background was definitely the hardest part because the original picture relied heavily on colour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Slowly Losing My Hair</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/im-slowly-losing-my-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/im-slowly-losing-my-hair/</guid>
      <description>One morning after we woke up, my SO wiped the bed and exclaimed, &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s so much of your hair!&amp;rdquo; We both laughed it off but I felt a sense of dread. I&amp;rsquo;m no stranger to hair loss. For years now I&amp;rsquo;ve notice more hair in the shower, on my pillow, on the floor, on my laptop, etc. When I go to my doctor every year, he reassures me it&amp;rsquo;s normal and gets me to do bloodwork that always comes back clean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 02:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week I wanted to draw a tree. The thought came to me while my SO and I were eating lunch at the Vietnamese restaurant. Behind him there was a large plastic palm tree and that was when I suggested trees. We ended up finding a picture of snowy winter trees on /r/pics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Icing Charades</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/cookie-icing-charades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/cookie-icing-charades/</guid>
      <description>The Game
Take turns to ice an object or living being onto a cookie. Everyone guesses what that person iced onto the cookie. There are no winners, just a bunch of people having fun and joking around about their lack of (or possession of) artistic ability.
The Background
Over the holidays I was baking brownies and cookies with my cousins. The brownies had left over frosting so we decided to ice the cookies with cool designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 02:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-1/</guid>
      <description>This week my SO and I decided to draw a bear. Er, rather, we decided to draw two bears! The picture we found was simply just a quick Google search. It was a rather cute picture! I kinda struggled with this one since bears are really fluffy while the previous week&amp;rsquo;s elephant had very simple lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Did Today Go?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/where-did-today-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 21:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/where-did-today-go/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s almost 3:00PM. So far today, I have done the following:
 Went to church Did my laundry Cooked and ate lunch Worked out for half an hour  I still have to:
 Read the rest of chapter 1 in my CCNA3 course Go through my to-do list in my bullet journal Update my monthly trackers in my bullet journal Work a little bit on my pomodoro app Reply to my pen pal  So much to do, so little time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnamese Food and Westworld</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/vietnamese-food-and-westworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 18:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/vietnamese-food-and-westworld/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I went out with my SO for Vietnamese food. There&amp;rsquo;s a decently sized restaurant called Bow River Vietnamese Restaurant that&amp;rsquo;s close by his house. I regret not taking pictures but their deep fried wontons were delicious. It had a good amount of meat and perfect crunchy crust. The sauce they provided it with was good as well.
For myself, I ordered a regular beef noodle soup. In the soup was tripe, brisket, and beef balls in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #0</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/weekly-drawing-0/</guid>
      <description>My SO suggested we start a weekly drawing. So we pick a picture of something to draw and at the end of the week we share it. Last week we drew elephants.
Here&amp;rsquo;s my elephant! I think I&amp;rsquo;m going to stick to pencil drawings. I&amp;rsquo;m not good at drawing by any means and this was pretty easy, honestly. It was fun drawing it though!

Versus what I was trying to draw&amp;#8230; I see clearly what I should have done differently now, haha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Work…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/back-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 03:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/back-to-work/</guid>
      <description>The holidays are officially over, for I went back to work today. It was a bit of a slow day. I got my internship extended, however they basically treated me as a new hire since my contract ended in December. So I&amp;rsquo;m starting from scratch, essentially. I had no laptop, no e-mail, no account to login into any computer connected to the company&amp;rsquo;s network&amp;#8230; Kinda rough.
However, I did manage to do some small tasks that didn&amp;rsquo;t require the use of a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Before 25</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/25-before-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 19:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/blog/25-before-25/</guid>
      <description>New Years Resolutions are no longer the in thing. I recently turned 22 and it feels like my life is whizzing by now. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about my goals but there are just too many that I have for one year and a couple that will go beyond 2017. So I figured a 25 before 25 would be appropriate.
1. Graduate from university
I&amp;rsquo;ve been in university since I was 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Week, New Me</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/new-week-new-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 04:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/new-week-new-me/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I had eaten two plates piled high with sweet American-Chinese prepared meats, a plate full of sweet desserts, and a take-out box of homemade cookies. On Friday I almost consumed an entire bag of buttery popcorn but the bag spilled into the aisle as it descended up the movie theatre steps. As I heard the small popped kernels tumble out of the bag, I felt both relief and disappointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 28</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-28/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 28: Rest Day Oh my goodness, today is the last day of the fitness calendar! I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I made it! I didn&amp;rsquo;t make this cookie (I haven&amp;rsquo;t made any of the rest day recipes) but like with the rest of the recipes, I would love to try this eventually!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 27</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 04:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-27/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 27: Total Body Today is the last day of the beginner&amp;rsquo;s workout calendar, not including the rest day tomorrow! I think I&amp;rsquo;ll make a blog post the day after rest day to talk about how the month went. As for today, today was a lot of sweat and groaning! A lot of cardio today, even if it isn&amp;rsquo;t intensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 26</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 05:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-26/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 26: Abs Video 1: Train Insane HIIT Workout  Video 2: Muffintop Shredder Workout I can&amp;rsquo;t remember anymore but I think I&amp;rsquo;ve done this video before. This video is really simple, there is just one move: the candlestick. I think I was doing it properly this time because I started to get tired and I could feel burning in my limbs and my core (I can&amp;rsquo;t be as technical as Cassey, what are my obliques?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 25</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 06:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-25/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 25: Lower Body Video 1: Far Burning Cardio Warmup I&amp;rsquo;ve done this video so many times that I&amp;rsquo;ve almost memorized everything Cassey said, haha! The moves in this video are easy and fun, as always.
 Video 2: Hips Butt &amp;#8216;n Thighs Super Shaper Workout   Hot Potato: This is a nice and easy move to start off the video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 24</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-24/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 24: Lower Body I&amp;rsquo;m still behind&amp;hellip; Oh well, I mostly caught up today. I still have one video to do for day 25 but it&amp;rsquo;s day 25 now and I have three hours left to do it! Today was pretty hard but that could be due to the fact I did two days in one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 23</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 07:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-23/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 23: Abs Okay I&amp;rsquo;m pretty behind. It&amp;rsquo;s now past midnight, I should be doing day 25 today. I&amp;rsquo;m waking up early tomorrow so I&amp;rsquo;ll have to skip out on catching up on day 24 until later in the day. Yesterday (two days ago?) I came home late with a huge head ache and immediately fell asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 22</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 07:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-22/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 22: Total Body I was so close to not doing today&amp;rsquo;s workout because I came home late from a volunteering gig with a raging head ache. I slept for about four hours and woke up around 10:30. It took me a while to get started with the workout, I didn&amp;rsquo;t start until 11:15 and I finished at 11:55!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 21</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 06:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-21/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 21: Rest Day Today was a much needed rest day. Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been having the tendency to fall asleep as soon as I get home, which sucks. So I decided to just sleep, haha! I didn&amp;rsquo;t try out the pizza. Maybe one day. Seriously, one day I will try all of her recipes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 20</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 05:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-20/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 19: Total Body I got home today after writing a midterm and I was so tired that I was tempted to just not do the workout today but then I realized tomorrow os rest day and who wants to work out on rest day? Not me. So I decided against it and got off my butt to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 19</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 02:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-19/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 19: Abs I loathe ab days. They&amp;rsquo;re really hard and not that fun, haha. But I really do feel the burn the most on these days. I need to work on this&amp;hellip;
Video 1: Fun Indoor Cardio Workout There are A LOT of kicks in this video. I did my workout in the morning today so I had to do some modifications, as always.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 18</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 06:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-18/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 18: Lower Body Because I had to make up day 17 today, I broke the two workouts up throughout the day. But near the end of the day, I just did the last two videos all at once. This day&amp;rsquo;s workout is surprisingly not that bad. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any trouble with the moves today which was&amp;hellip; Weird but satisfying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 17</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 04:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-17/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 17: Total Body Okay, this is the first time I have skipped a day and had to make it up. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel too guilty about skipping yesterday because I had spin class, which is two (maybe even three) times as long and 234204398 times harder than these workouts. I enjoy spin class though, don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 16</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 06:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-16/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 16: Abs Okay, this is the first day that I technically did not do on the right day. I started this one a little after midnight because I was working on an assignment and then I looked at the time&amp;hellip; Whoops, the day went by fast! Today&amp;rsquo;s videos were okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 15</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 06:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-15/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 15: Total Body My body issues seem to have improved, minus the random headaches. I tried my best to stay active and not give into my pain. I might have to go to the doctor tomorrow though, if it gets any worse. Both videos today contained moves that were not named so I&amp;rsquo;m not going to bother with going through each move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 14</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 04:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-14/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 14: Rest Day Ummm, what?? It&amp;rsquo;s rest day already?? I do not believe it. I&amp;rsquo;ve been at this for two weeks now! I feel proud of myself, I never thought I would be able to make it this far. I&amp;rsquo;m officially halfway through the calendar! I decided not to do a workout video today because I&amp;rsquo;ve been so tired and lethargic lately and all of my limbs feel sore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 06:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-13/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 13: Total Body Video 1: 5 Minute Fat Burner &amp;ldquo;Five minutes? Easy peasey.&amp;rdquo; I was so wrong! Cassey wasn&amp;rsquo;t lying when she said it would be tough. This was a hard video, with lots of suffering included (guaranteed).
  Star Jump: These were really hard to do quietly. I definitely started sweating immediately with this move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-12/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 12: Abs Ab workouts are so brutal&amp;hellip; And, of course, that&amp;rsquo;s what everyone wants to workout. Cue the suffering.
Video 1: Ab &amp;amp; Butt Workout I seriously cannot get over how cute Rosanna is! She is absolutely adorable and when she struggles, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m not alone in ab hell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 11</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 14:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-11/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 11: Lower Body Another day, another week almost finished (I&amp;rsquo;m talking in terms of the weekday week and not the Blogilates week)! I keep mixing up the &amp;ldquo;Wake up and &amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; preambles at the start of each day&amp;hellip;. Yesterday I did 30 second planks on each side instead of just 1 minute of planking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 10</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calenday-2-0-day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 06:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calenday-2-0-day-10/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 10: Abs The day starts off with two thirty second planks on each side. How I hate planks&amp;hellip; But I did it anyway, even if I cheated for a couple seconds on each. There&amp;rsquo;s only one new video today and I decided that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t list all the moves for the other videos again in the interest of time and because I don&amp;rsquo;t really have anything to say about specific moves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 9</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 06:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-9/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 9: Abs Video 1: Total Body Workout I&amp;rsquo;m not going to list the moves for this video again because my comments are mostly the same from the last time I did this video. I really am progressing with those pull ups. Not once did I have to grab my legs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 8</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 06:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-8/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 8: Total Body After my &amp;ldquo;rest day&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve been missing Cassey a little. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that it&amp;rsquo;s already the second week! It doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like it&amp;rsquo;s been that long&amp;hellip;
Video 1: Indoor Cardio Workout I wish I had more time to do workouts in the morning because when it comes to the cardio videos, I just can&amp;rsquo;t do them 100% without making a bunch of noise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 7</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 06:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-7/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 7: Rest Day Thank goodness for the rest day. Technically there is 30 minutes left of day 7 and I feel like I should be doing something. So I&amp;rsquo;m searching for some quick videos to do before midnight hits. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I&amp;rsquo;ve done a week of this already! Here&amp;rsquo;s to four more weeks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 6</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 01:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 6: Total Body &amp;ldquo;Wake up and do 15 crunches.&amp;rdquo; I did four roll ups instead. And I never do these when I wake up, usually it&amp;rsquo;s the last thing I do before bed. Not today though!
Video 1: Cardio Warmup I&amp;rsquo;m really glad Cassey puts some cardio videos because most of her workouts are focusing on toning and my main goal is to burn fat and not really &amp;ldquo;bulk&amp;rdquo; up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 5</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 07:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 5: Abs Okay I switched up the preambles in the calendar because apparently I can&amp;rsquo;t read. Day three I was supposed to plank for 30 seconds, yesterday I was supposed to do the burpees, and today I was supposed to drink an 8 oz of water. Whoops! So I compensated today by not only drinking the water but also doing the plank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Years of Blogging</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/9-years-of-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 21:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/9-years-of-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I know that probably isn&amp;rsquo;t a lot compared to other bloggers out there but to me, that&amp;rsquo;s mind blowing. 9 years is around 40% of my life and that percentage will only keep on increasing. Assuming that I continue blogging. As long as I can type, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I would stop blogging. Sure, my blogging might be extremely sporadic but it&amp;rsquo;s still blogging to me.
Actually, I was going through my archive and I read a blog post that was from exactly six years and two days ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 4</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 06:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 4: Lower Body The little preamble for today in the calendar simply said to drink a glass of 8 oz of water. I have no idea what 8 oz looks like. Or how much any other measurements of liquids look like for that matter. So I just drank a regular glass of water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 2: Abs Today&amp;rsquo;s workout is split into two videos. Both target your abs however they vary in difficulty. It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that spot reduction (focusing on working out a specific part of your body to lose fat in that one specific area) is a myth. It&amp;rsquo;s only when your overall body fat percentage lowers that will you see results and they will be present around your whole body and not in just one area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 07:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.
My first post of 2016! This year I resolved to get healthier. That is, eat healthier and be more active! I&amp;rsquo;ve been hanging out on the /r/xxfitness: Fitness for Women subreddit a lot lately. Since I&amp;rsquo;m hesitant to go to the gym, someone suggested I try Blogilates, ran by Cassey Ho. I browsed the site a bit and decided to try the Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Workout Calendar which lasts for four weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 16:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-14/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
I came to school on a reading day because I have a group project to work on. The meeting doesn’t start for another hour so I’m just going over my AI notes because I need to catch up on the material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wanting to Write</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/wanting-to-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 02:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/wanting-to-write/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to document my life in a journal. There is something awfully romantic about keeping an account of your day to day life. I just read a book, Fairyland by Alysia Abbott, about a woman who grew up with a single gay father in the &amp;lsquo;80s. She reconstructed both her and her father&amp;rsquo;s life through his journals and their letters to each other. I find it so beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 02:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-13/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
Team messy notes 2015. My mind was blown away during this lecture. Honestly, some of the algorithm solutions for simple problems like finding the two closest points in a plane, are extremely interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 15:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-12/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
It’s early morning and I’m trying to do some of my assignment that I should have started over the weekend but I was working on a group project instead. I really should learn to manage my time better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally Imported Those Old Posts</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 19:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</guid>
      <description>So now that I&amp;rsquo;ve moved hosts, I decided to do some spring cleaning (fall cleaning?). Right now, my databases are a mess. I have a lot of databases that aren&amp;rsquo;t used and databases that are waiting to be used. I still had my old blog database, back from when Brokenphrases was my main blog. So, I decided to to import all those pages and posts here.
Now my blog post archive is pretty much complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 15:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-11/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
I came to school three hours early today (I start at 10) so I can get a head start on the exercises we’re doing today in tutorial. It’s just so awkward when the TA asks for the answer and no one speaks up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 02:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-10/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
Finished making presentation index cards. I’m really bad when it comes to public speaking so I need to prep a lot. Most group presentations I‘ve had involved “just winging it” and that never goes well for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 03:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-9/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
I’m feeling super down for some reason right now and I can’t really pinpoint what it is. It feels like there’s a dark cloud looming over my head. I tried to make my notes look extra neat, neater than usual, as that usually helps me calm down whenever I do feel like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post:</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 03:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-8/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
My super messy notes (right) vs the rewritten version (left). During a lecture, neat and legible notes are the last things on my mind. Okay, sometimes I zone out and look down at my paper and think, “Wow, this looks horrible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: My DIY Planner</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 00:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-7/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
Some pictures of my diy planner, taken with a potato. I borrowed inspiration from diyfish inserts. Whenever I open it up, I can see my whole month and reoccurring tasks right in front of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: The Rebel</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 06:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-6/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
In bed with Camus. A penpal recommended this book to me and he expects a nice, long essay about it. Okay, I think (and hope) that was a joke but I really want to be able to understand this so we can have a meaningful conversation about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incoming Mail #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/incoming-mail-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 21:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/incoming-mail-1/</guid>
      <description>This is a new segment, where I post the things that I received in the mail! Since the beginning of the year, I&amp;rsquo;ve acquired some penpals and started buying more things online. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I&amp;rsquo;ll separate the things I buy from my penpal letters but I don&amp;rsquo;t think I buy that much to warrant it. Today, I only have purchases to show you. On to the post!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transition to Foundation: Successful?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/transition-to-foundation-successful/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 17:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/transition-to-foundation-successful/</guid>
      <description>Okay I&amp;rsquo;m so angry, I wrote this entire post out in the &amp;ldquo;Quick Draft&amp;rdquo; section of my dashboard, clicked &amp;ldquo;Save Draft&amp;rdquo; and then when I came back, what I wrote was erased. :( This happens a lot but not enough for me to remember to save entries locally before I publish&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best to recreate what I just wrote. I&amp;rsquo;m still really salty, haha.
In my previous post, I mentioned that I was moving from Bootstrap to Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Switching to Foundation</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 01:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-5/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
I’m taking a “zero day” from studying but that doesn’t mean you have to stop learning! I decided to work on my blog and switch frameworks from Bootstrap to Foundation, mostly because Boostrap has the potential to get really bloated and I find that Foundation is more intuitive and their documentation is great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: School Supplies Haul</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 20:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-4/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
Here’s a picture of all the school supplies I bought for this year (and hopefully years to come). I didn’t spend a lot compared to previous years and I’m so happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Convolutions, Please…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 06:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-3/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
I’m in the middle of trying out studyign{.tumblelog}’s method of taking textbook notes for my algorithm design class.
This was seriously a hard section to wrap my head around. Each step of computing a convolution makes sense but the big picture escapes me right now, especially since it involves complex numbers, which I haven’t touched those in years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Lunch Food</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post-2/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
Lunch break with cantaloupes and warm pandesal with cheese. I usually don’t like eating at my desk when it comes to breads, especially crumbly breads like pandesal but I was totally craving it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Scientific Papers</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 03:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/tumblr-post/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
 
I forgot where I heard this tip but it’s good to read papers that are in your field in your spare time. I spent like an hour looking for PDFs that I didn’t have to pay to read when I remembered that my university library provides free access to databases and databases of papers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Post: Using Staedtler Triplus Fineliners</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/using-staedtler-triplus-fineliners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/using-staedtler-triplus-fineliners/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is a cross post from my Tumblr blog, Study, Scattered Me!. As well, any products mentioned in this post are not in any way sponsored (unless stated) and my views on those products are my own.
 
My Staedtler Triplus Fineliners always ran out quickly so I stopped using them. Seeing how popular Staedtler is, I gave them another chance and they look awesome. Except I’m still worried they might run out fast on me again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1/? Favourite Pages From My Notebooks</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/1-favourite-pages-from-my-notebooks-on-the-left-is-a-list-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 23:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/1-favourite-pages-from-my-notebooks-on-the-left-is-a-list-of/</guid>
      <description>1/? Favourite pages from my notebooks
On the left is a list of options courses I can pick from for my concentration and my schedule for the next two semesters. On the right is all of the course requirements for my degree and the courses I’m taking to fulfil them. I can’t believe I’m already halfway through my degree! Also, I love writing in monochrome. Boring, I know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Planner for 2015</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/diy-planner-for-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 02:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/diy-planner-for-2015/</guid>
      <description>2015.08.12 &amp;#8211; Working on my DIY planner while watching my brother playing GTAV in the living room. This time, I’m not using my Filofax because I can’t dedicate that much time to cutting up that much paper. As always, my pages are heavily inspired by DIYfish’s Life Mapping System inserts. I just love being able to see my monthly view and (half of) my weekly view at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #6</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 02:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-6/</guid>
      <description>I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I’m sorry. I’ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I’ve made on Tumblr.
Warning: Mild The Fault in Our Stars spoilers (Disclaimer: I didn&amp;rsquo;t like the movie)
 I saw The Fault in Our Stars yesterday and I knew Gus was a jock but it never really occurred to me HOW MUCH of a jock he was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #5</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 02:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-5/</guid>
      <description>I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I’m sorry. I’ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I’ve made on Tumblr.
 I was listening to an episode of a certain podcast yesterday, which was recorded around the time when Andy got a tumblr and started stirring the pot with the SJ fan community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Week of Half-Way Year</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/first-week-of-half-way-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 04:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/first-week-of-half-way-year/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m now in my third year of university. That&amp;rsquo;s an extremely scary thought for me, haha. High school seems like it was just yesterday (to be fair, it was only two years ago). Despite this being my third year, this is technically my middle year. I switched majors which added year to my degree. I&amp;rsquo;ve already done two years and after I finish this year, I have two more years to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #4</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 02:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-4/</guid>
      <description>I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I’m sorry. I’ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I’ve made on Tumblr.
 I was mailing out letters one day and there&amp;rsquo;s this guy at the mall who works at a knives store. He has a sweet mohawk. I was sitting nearby putting stamps on envelopes and an old lady asked him if she could touch his hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 02:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-3/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Implied misogynistic content, alluding to the USBC shootings, and mentions of rape.
I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I&amp;rsquo;ve made on Tumblr.
 I was listening to an episode of the Internet Box, which was recorded around the time when Andrew got a Tumblr and started stirring the pot with the social justice fan community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 02:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-2/</guid>
      <description>I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I&amp;rsquo;ve made on Tumblr.
 In Mass Effect 4 I just want to talk more. I want to learn more about their cultures and I want to do stuff for them, even if it’s just talking them through decisions and not going to the ends of the universe for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-tumblr-posts-1/</guid>
      <description>Ugh I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make this as painless as possible.
 I had a dream where I literally just lived out my entire day, down to sitting in lecture being bored and taking notes.
You don’t even know how disappointed I am when I woke up knowing that I had to do it all over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Had a Dream About War</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/i-had-a-dream-about-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 05:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/i-had-a-dream-about-war/</guid>
      <description>I was awakened in the middle of the night by bursts of light penetrating my closed eyelids. As I opened my eyes, I saw what looked like a meteor shower. For a second, it looked beautiful. But as my lids rose up,a light followed it. Up. Why is that light going up? The skyline glowed with golden orbs and light shot out from them. The lights curled and twisted. And instead of end shortly with a boom like a firework or fading with a fizzle like a sparkler, the kept going up into the sky until my head couldn&amp;rsquo;t look any higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be My Dearest, First on Earth</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/be-my-dearest-first-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 18:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/be-my-dearest-first-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>I’m still waiting to fall in love with a book. I want to open it and never want to put it down ever again. I want to find myself in it. I want it to drag out the dark from inside of me and then I want it to tell me that it’s okay and to list all the things that are good about me. I want to read it and never look at life and humanity the same way again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calgary Expo 2014</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/calgary-expo-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 23:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/calgary-expo-2014/</guid>
      <description>**WARNING: This post contains over 30 pictures. Open if you dare! An ableism trigger warning as well (possible slur).
ALSO: If you see your picture here and would like credit or for me to take it down, please leave a comment.**
This was my second year going to my local con. Last year I went all three days but this year I just went one day. It was a lot of fun but also soooo exhausting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solid Day (AKA Ramen Run #2)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/solid-day-aka-ramen-run-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 06:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/solid-day-aka-ramen-run-2/</guid>
      <description>I went out with some friends today. It&amp;rsquo;s funny because every time we go to this ramen place, our local anime convention has an event. Last time it was their mini winter com and this time they were having a trading pin party up at the university.
But yeah we went to eat ramen. It was yummy. And then we bought candy. That was yummy as well.
But my friends also gave me presents which was really weird wow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Holidays 2013</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/christmas-holidays-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 18:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/christmas-holidays-2013/</guid>
      <description>My exams ended relatively early last semester. That meant more time for a break! I didn&amp;rsquo;t do terribly a lot over through break though. Definitely was not as productive as I would have liked to be.
Finished watching and reading Shingeki no Kyojin
Shingeki no Kyojin is an anime. The Internet has been basically exploding over it (my part of the Internet anyway). My friends in real life also freak out over it and so much so that I just had to see what they were on about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 Resolutions</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/2014-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 06:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/2014-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>Write a blog post every week
Writing a blog post every day is pretty much impossible for me. However, I still want to post regularly. Posting weekly sounds pretty doable for me. There are 168 hours in a week. If I can&amp;rsquo;t fit in at least one blog post in there, I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to rethink my current time management system.
Spend less than 30 minutes on YouTube everyday</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not So Subtle</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/not-so-subtle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 07:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/not-so-subtle/</guid>
      <description>That moment when your TA is looking at you not so subtly. Or maybe I just have sucky peripheral vision. WOW I really hope the latter is not the case. Man, my heart is so doki doki when I think about him. Much dork. :(</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2013 Semester in Review</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/fall-2013-semester-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 06:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/fall-2013-semester-in-review/</guid>
      <description>This semester went by really quickly. I never once thought, &amp;ldquo;wow I want this semester to be over.&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m not joking, really! I really enjoyed it. Then again, it could be due to the fact that I only took three courses this semester: introduction to Python, Russian literature in translation, and linear algebra. They were all pretty fair courses. I already had some programming experience (once you are exposed one programming language, it&amp;rsquo;s easier to read other languages), my Russian professor was quite easy, and I knew most of the content in linear algebra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasons Why I Don’t Wear Makeup</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/reasons-why-i-dont-wear-makeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 05:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/reasons-why-i-dont-wear-makeup/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;m lazy.  It&amp;rsquo;s expensive. Out of the three times I&amp;rsquo;ve worn makeup in my life, I felt more self conscious with makeup than without. I feel like a clown. It physically feels weird on my face. If y&amp;rsquo;all don&amp;rsquo;t love me without the makeup but love me with it, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;d want to wear it in the first place.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Do I Go?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/where-do-i-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 09:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/where-do-i-go/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t miss people much. Usually when I&amp;rsquo;m away from people, I feel relieved. Relaxed. At peace. Almost happy.
However, when things go bad, there&amp;rsquo;s one person I long for.
Then I realize I can&amp;rsquo;t text him. I can&amp;rsquo;t pull up Facebook and chat with him.
What I&amp;rsquo;m feeling is selfish. So selfish.
I wish he was here so he could help me and I could talk to him about everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having an Off Day</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/having-an-off-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 06:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/having-an-off-day/</guid>
      <description>Today I do something new. This is my writing. I did not intend to post it on my blog but then I realized I released all of my feelings here. Feels good I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doki Doki Senpai</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/doki-doki-senpai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 04:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/doki-doki-senpai/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday1 I chatted a bit with my senpai. He was so adorable. :( Now I&amp;rsquo;m sure he does not have feelings for me which is both a relief and a disappointment at the same time. Relief because lol that could get too complicated and a disappointment because he&amp;rsquo;s so cute. D:
However, today I did talk to him. I asked him how his weekend was. Apparently it was bad. He spent the whole weekend writing an eleven page paper about network systems and stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muku</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/muku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 18:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/muku/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday I went out with my friends to go eat lunch. I wish I took pictures but I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize my outing could be a potential blog post until yesterday, when I was writing yesterday&amp;rsquo;s blog post. I usually don&amp;rsquo;t make a habit of taking pictures of my food either. People who do that to post them on Twitter and Instagram annoy me. Sorry to everyone I just offended. I just want to eat your food okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doki Doki Goes the Heart</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/doki-doki-goes-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 02:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/doki-doki-goes-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>My heart hasn&amp;rsquo;t gone doki doki in a while. The last time I can remember is when I was in my freshman year of high school when I was crushing on my first boyfriend1. This was, of course, before last Friday.
On Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays I have my first class with three of my friends. We all have a break after the class so we eat together. Last Friday, we decided to eat in the ICT building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But Seriously Though. AJ is perfect.</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/but-seriously-though-aj-is-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 19:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/but-seriously-though-aj-is-perfect/</guid>
      <description>AJ reminds me of Kemal. As much as I&amp;rsquo;d hate to say it, that&amp;rsquo;s the number one reason why I find AJ so attractive. He&amp;rsquo;s like the Korean version of Kemal. Also, I&amp;rsquo;d rather fangirl over AJ than be madly crushing on a guy who probably thinks I&amp;rsquo;m an idiot and who I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in almost a year.
However, I saw Kemal on campus a while ago and I realized how much they don&amp;rsquo;t really look like each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scarf</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/the-scarf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 23:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/the-scarf/</guid>
      <description>The sun cleared up his eyes and I was instantly lost.
Even when his head turned towards mine
I could not and would not tear mine away from his.
That colour!
I had never experienced it before.
Warm and clear.
I could see forever in his eyes.
I could feel his disappointment
when he looked into mine: an endless dirt pit.
But he smiled at me then, a sweet crooked grin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prompt #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/prompt-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 04:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/prompt-1/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what to write about in my blog right now. At first I was like &amp;ldquo;post everyday!&amp;rdquo; but when I got to it, I drew a blank. Not to mention, the 500 words requirement overwhelms me. What can I write about for 500 words??That&amp;rsquo;s why I already missed more than four days of posting. A &amp;ldquo;blog post idea&amp;rdquo; list would be very hand right now. I gotta start writing down said ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Thoughts AKA Tweets I Have Tweeted or Would Like to Tweet</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-thoughts-aka-tweets-i-have-tweeted-or-would-like-to-tweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 00:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/random-thoughts-aka-tweets-i-have-tweeted-or-would-like-to-tweet/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a victim of the 140 characters. Okay, sometimes I like to say things that are more than 140 characters but you know what I mean, yeah? Tumblr (not Twitter) has conditioned me to want to share my thoughts every time they pop into my head. Fortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t have Tumblr anymore. Unfortunately, I do have a Twitter. Fortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to use my Twitter1 too much because I have only six followers who probably don&amp;rsquo;t care about me at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race Against Time</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/race-against-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 06:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/race-against-time/</guid>
      <description>I missed yesterday as well. I&amp;rsquo;m just not very good at this! But I am determined not to miss today. Today I read on Zen Habits that you should never miss doing something two days in a row. It&amp;rsquo;s a good philosophy and a great motivation hack for me. By the time two days have passed, it&amp;rsquo;s very likely that that task will never be accomplished.
So yes, it&amp;rsquo;s around 11:30pm and it takes me around half an hour to write at least 500 words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missed a Day</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/missed-a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 00:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/missed-a-day/</guid>
      <description>Even though yesterday technically has a post, I did not post it until today. Therefore, I missed a day. Being the procrastinator that I am, I usually leave these blog posts until around 11:00pm at night, when I&amp;rsquo;m lying in bed. However, last night I was not lying in bed. Instead, I was seated in front of my brother&amp;rsquo;s laptop, trying to finish an essay. My essay was not due today but I ended up staying up until 3:30 in the morning working on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just a Review #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/just-a-review-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 02:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/just-a-review-1/</guid>
      <description>I said before that I&amp;rsquo;m finding it slightly hard to come up with blog topics. Therefore, I am creating a new feature for my blog: Just a Review. It&amp;rsquo;s basically what it seems like: just a review of my day. It&amp;rsquo;s not necessarily a review review but more like a summary. If I rated my days it would be very depressing to look at all the low scores1
So, from the beginning!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Library #2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/at-the-library-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 13:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/at-the-library-2/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that Room 304 is now officially a book log/archive with minimal blog posts. This calls for a redesign that will emphasize the fact. Why the change? It was always my intention to have Room 304 solely as a book log. But as I heard about book blogging, I decided I would give it a chance. It overshadowed the logging aspect of the site, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I wanted to update the site anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Week (AKA I’m Reading Week)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/reading-week-aka-im-reading-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 06:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/reading-week-aka-im-reading-week/</guid>
      <description>I went to the library last Saturday! Quite fitting because it is reading week at university. I&amp;rsquo;m probably the only one who takes the &amp;ldquo;reading&amp;rdquo; in reading week seriously&amp;hellip; Anyway, here is my library haul this week in order of the books I remember first:
 French Milk by Lucy Knisley
I&amp;rsquo;m always a sucker for personal memoir-like graphic novels. The cover is just too charming to not want to read it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with YA Author Graeme Ing</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/interview-with-ya-author-grame-ing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 15:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/interview-with-ya-author-grame-ing/</guid>
      <description>When I let my friends know that I want to be a librarian after I exhaust my career as a software engineer, one of them laughed at me and said, &amp;ldquo;A librarian with an engineering degree? Are you doing to make houses out of books?&amp;rdquo; I just smiled and responded with a witty comment but inside I wondered, &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s wrong with that?&amp;rdquo;
While surfing the web, I stumbled upon Graeme Ing, a YA author and a former game developer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making the Almost Switch to Tumblr</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/making-the-almost-switch-to-tumblr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 06:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/making-the-almost-switch-to-tumblr/</guid>
      <description>I love WordPress. It&amp;rsquo;s the best content management system for me and extremely flexible. Anything is possible in WordPress. However, lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been noticing a lack in the number of blogs from undergrads and grads alike. I searched high and low on WordpPess, Blogger, etc. Then I remembered: Tumblr. Not surprisingly, the student blogging community is thriving on Tumblr. 
Tumblr is less of a blogging platform, but more of a social media website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Textbooks</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/reading-textbooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 02:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/reading-textbooks/</guid>
      <description>I have a hard time reading textbooks. I can&amp;rsquo;t read blocks of text. Yes, regular old books are blocks of text but textbooks aren&amp;rsquo;t meant to be read the same way regular books are; they&amp;rsquo;re meant to be skimmed. Even so, I still have trouble. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s only the university level textbooks that are causing me trouble. but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean they should be any less readable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suggested Reading: Project Gutenberg</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/suggested-reading-project-gutenberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 05:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/suggested-reading-project-gutenberg/</guid>
      <description>Suggested Reading is a weekly feature that runs every, you guessed it, Wednesday. In this feature, a website, blog, or article is showcased for further reading. One of the best things about the Internet is the ability to share. So why not take advantage of that and share some of my favourite things to read on the web? This week’s SR is a website that features e-books for download, Project Gutenberg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Thing About Being 18</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/the-best-thing-about-being-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 05:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/the-best-thing-about-being-18/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip; Is getting an adult library card. I&amp;rsquo;m not even joking. I detested the teen library card. It was too &amp;ldquo;hip&amp;rdquo; for me. So I rather like my simplistic and pretty white adult library card. The bad thing is that I have to memorize a new card number. Although the number for my new card has bits and pieces of my address and home phone number so I reckon it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suggested Reading: The Common Librarian</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/suggested-reading-the-common-librarian/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 02:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/suggested-reading-the-common-librarian/</guid>
      <description>Suggested Reading is a weekly feature that runs every, you guessed it, Wednesday. In this feature, a website, blog, or article is showcased for further reading. One of the best things about the Internet is the ability to share. So why not take advantage of that and share some of my favourite things to read on the web? This week&amp;rsquo;s SR is a multimedia blog hosted on Tumblr, The Common Librarian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Losing Weight</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/im-losing-weight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 23:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/im-losing-weight/</guid>
      <description>They say that one of the easiest ways to lose weight is to keep track of what you&amp;rsquo;re eating. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to apply this to my own life in order to lose some weight. I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about the physical kind of weight but the dead weight that everyone carries around and hinders them in some way. This blog, The Librarian Code, will help me to lose some of that dead weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow Friday #8</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/follow-friday-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 04:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/follow-friday-8/</guid>
      <description>Follow Friday is a weekly book meme hosted by Parajunkee and Alison Can Read. In this meme, us bloggers are asked a question to which we respond to by posting on our blogs. Other bloggers can see our answers, comment, and follow!  This week&#39;s question is: What’s the most unique character name you’ve come across?  In the spin-off novel of the popular manga and anime series of Death Note, Death Note: Another Note by NISIOSIN, there are a whole load of crazy names.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Library #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/at-the-library-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/at-the-library-1/</guid>
      <description>Technically this is the second trip to the library this year but this is the first post about it.
Right after I finished my chemistry diploma exam on Thursday, my dad drove me to the library. I felt at home, how sad, haha. Usually I go upstairs to the teen section, but oh ho, not this time! I went straight to the adult comics section. I&amp;rsquo;m quite the rebel, I know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost Happy Birthday</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/almost-happy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2007 22:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/almost-happy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>My birthday is in four days! I&amp;rsquo;ll finally be thirteen! I have had it with people staring at me and going, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re still twelve?&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s annoying. I&amp;rsquo;m not the only twelve year old in grade eight!
One of my friends is already fourteen! She can get her learner&amp;rsquo;s permit nd she cant get over the fact she&amp;rsquo;s two years older than me. At least I&amp;rsquo;m not like my one friend. HHe doesnt turn thirteen until February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Late Pizza</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/late-pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 01:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/late-pizza/</guid>
      <description>Today is the last day of school for winter break! Yay! We were supposed to have pizza but it never came&amp;hellip; We also watched a movie that I have watched too many times: The Polar Express. Then my camera ran out of batteries after I just took one picture of my friends. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t a great day, but I&amp;rsquo;m glad it&amp;rsquo;s just over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Bank</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/food-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 08:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/food-bank/</guid>
      <description>Today, my TA went to the church across the street to help out with the food hampers. Our job was to bring all 200 something boxes from the basement to the main floor. Do you know how hard that is? It was definitely a workout for me. I got my friend pat to help me with over half of my boxes and he calls me lazy. There was this freight elevator, and we had to bring carts full of food with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TA</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/ta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2007 05:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/ta/</guid>
      <description>Three days ago, I started school, and I found out that we no longer have homerooms. Now we have TA I went to my TA in the band room and found three grade niners there, and I thought I was in the wrong homeroom, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Oh and guess who my teacher advisors are? The principal and the vice principal! This is going to be one great year.
I have three of my friends in my TA and I have to stick with my TA Until I finish junior high&amp;hellip; b=Vleh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beauti</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/beauti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2007 16:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/beauti/</guid>
      <description>Beauti is a pretty good band. Right now, they&amp;rsquo;re on tour with this thing called Absolute. They travel all across Canada to high schools. Which really doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense because I&amp;rsquo;m in junior high. Anyway, they played four songs (actually three, but they played one song while the kids went into the gym). I forget what one song was, but the two songs they played was Forever Love, and Don&amp;rsquo;t Watch Me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bouncy</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/bouncy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/bouncy/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted in a while. For some reason I&amp;rsquo;ve been on Geek Stink breath a lot. I miss the old GSB, when there were more people there. I still love GSB though!
I have been working on my religion project for the past four days. I&amp;rsquo;m finally finished now. Thank goodness. Who knew that a simple powerpoint about a saint would be so much work? I guess I&amp;rsquo;m too much of a perfectionist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grade Niners</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/grade-niners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 23:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/grade-niners/</guid>
      <description>My locker&amp;rsquo;s right next to the band room, and grade niners are constantly standing around my locker. The grade niners like to listen to this guy play the drums every single lunch period. I was opening my locker, and the guy who plays the drums was looking at my locker. They saw my Billie Joe Armstrong poster (which unfortunately does not exist anymore because one of my friends tore it up).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>