<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weekly Drawing on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/weekly-drawing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weekly Drawing on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 02:38:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/weekly-drawing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #5.5</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-5-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-5-5/</guid>
      <description>I decided to post a work in progress. My SO picked this week&amp;rsquo;s picture and it was of a very pretty warrior girl. I started it and I really like how the face turned out. I quickly sketched out the rest of the body and I am already pretty proud of it. Compared to the original, my version looks a little less feminine. I just can&amp;rsquo;t draw lips right from the side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #4</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 02:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-4/</guid>
      <description>I chose last week&amp;rsquo;s picture this time. I thought the picture of the duck statues wearing the kitty hats from the Women&amp;rsquo;s March was pretty cute and easy to do as well. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t that easy, unfortunately. I didn&amp;rsquo;t finish the sidewalk. Didn&amp;rsquo;t want to draw all those stones. My SO didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to get very far with it either unfortunately. But it was fun to draw!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 02:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-3/</guid>
      <description>Last week&amp;rsquo;s theme was fantasy. The original picture was a lot more ethereal and pretty. I had to redraw this one because I messed up the background. The background was definitely the hardest part because the original picture relied heavily on colour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 02:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week I wanted to draw a tree. The thought came to me while my SO and I were eating lunch at the Vietnamese restaurant. Behind him there was a large plastic palm tree and that was when I suggested trees. We ended up finding a picture of snowy winter trees on /r/pics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 02:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-1/</guid>
      <description>This week my SO and I decided to draw a bear. Er, rather, we decided to draw two bears! The picture we found was simply just a quick Google search. It was a rather cute picture! I kinda struggled with this one since bears are really fluffy while the previous week&amp;rsquo;s elephant had very simple lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #0</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/weekly-drawing-0/</guid>
      <description>My SO suggested we start a weekly drawing. So we pick a picture of something to draw and at the end of the week we share it. Last week we drew elephants.
Here&amp;rsquo;s my elephant! I think I&amp;rsquo;m going to stick to pencil drawings. I&amp;rsquo;m not good at drawing by any means and this was pretty easy, honestly. It was fun drawing it though!

Versus what I was trying to draw&amp;#8230; I see clearly what I should have done differently now, haha.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>