<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friends on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/friends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friends on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 23:07:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Calgary Expo 2014</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/calgary-expo-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 23:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/calgary-expo-2014/</guid>
      <description>**WARNING: This post contains over 30 pictures. Open if you dare! An ableism trigger warning as well (possible slur).
ALSO: If you see your picture here and would like credit or for me to take it down, please leave a comment.**
This was my second year going to my local con. Last year I went all three days but this year I just went one day. It was a lot of fun but also soooo exhausting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solid Day (AKA Ramen Run #2)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/solid-day-aka-ramen-run-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 06:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/solid-day-aka-ramen-run-2/</guid>
      <description>I went out with some friends today. It&amp;rsquo;s funny because every time we go to this ramen place, our local anime convention has an event. Last time it was their mini winter com and this time they were having a trading pin party up at the university.
But yeah we went to eat ramen. It was yummy. And then we bought candy. That was yummy as well.
But my friends also gave me presents which was really weird wow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Holidays 2013</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/christmas-holidays-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 18:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/christmas-holidays-2013/</guid>
      <description>My exams ended relatively early last semester. That meant more time for a break! I didn&amp;rsquo;t do terribly a lot over through break though. Definitely was not as productive as I would have liked to be.
Finished watching and reading Shingeki no Kyojin
Shingeki no Kyojin is an anime. The Internet has been basically exploding over it (my part of the Internet anyway). My friends in real life also freak out over it and so much so that I just had to see what they were on about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muku</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/muku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 18:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/muku/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday I went out with my friends to go eat lunch. I wish I took pictures but I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize my outing could be a potential blog post until yesterday, when I was writing yesterday&amp;rsquo;s blog post. I usually don&amp;rsquo;t make a habit of taking pictures of my food either. People who do that to post them on Twitter and Instagram annoy me. Sorry to everyone I just offended. I just want to eat your food okay.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>