<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video Games on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/video-games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video Games on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/video-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Is Strange: The Tragedy of Rachel Amber</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life-is-strange-the-tragedy-of-rachel-amber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life-is-strange-the-tragedy-of-rachel-amber/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Spoilers for both Life is Strange Season 1 and *Life is Strange: Before the Storm*
In Life is Strange Season 1, Racher Amber is a mystery. If you walk around and talk to the locals, everyone (including those with less than stellar personalities) has nothing to say but praises about Rachel. Throughout the game, Rachel is built up to be perfect to everyone you speak to. The artists loved to try to capture her essence, the nerds enjoyed her intellectual prowess, and the popular kids enjoyed partying it up with her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Hour of Path of Exile as a Non-Gamer</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/one-hour-of-path-of-exile-as-a-non-gamer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 19:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/one-hour-of-path-of-exile-as-a-non-gamer/</guid>
      <description>Now I know that one hour is not enough to fully judge a game, especially for an online game which is supposed to be an extremely huge time sink. However, being someone who is not exactly the ideal demographic for this genre (I prefer turn based games like Fire Emblem, walking simulators like Life is Strange, open sandboxes like Minecraft, and RPGs like Mass Effect), one hour is just enough for me to have an idea of whether or not I would like the game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>